H
H
[Music]
[Música]
ch
ch
k
k
[Music]
[Música]
H Oh
H Oh
y [
y
Music] [Music]
[Música]
Good
buenas
night Good night family How
noches Buenas noches familia Qué tal
are you? Forgive me for this, well, with
estáis perdonadme con este bueno con
this strange and abrupt start,
este comienzo tan raro y tan abrupto
but something's wrong, something's wrong and things aren't working
pero pasa algo pasa algo y no funcionan
well today and I don't think it's
bien las cosas hoy y creo que no es
my fault or my computer's or anything like that
culpa mía ni de mi ordenador ni nada por
as you can see, neither the viewers nor the nor the chat appear in the chat
estilo como veis no aparece en el chat
and no, no reason There's no reason,
chat y no no hay motivo No hay motivo la
really I mean, no, no reason, everything's
verdad O sea no no hay motivo está todo
fine, everything's configured There's no
bien está todo configurado No hay motivo
apparent reason why it shouldn't appear
aparente por el que no debería apcer
So I don't know I mean, the chat doesn't even appear
Entonces no sé O sea no aparece ni el
on the screen and that really bothers me eh you
chat en pantalla y eso me raya mucho eh
know what now let's see, we're going to be,
u sabéis que ahora a ver vamos a estar
no, we're not going to leave, but it makes me uncomfortable eh It makes
no no nos vamos a ir pero me incomoda eh
me uncomfortable, maybe it's going to seem
Me incomoda os va a parecer a lo mejor a
silly to you all but it makes me uncomfortable, it makes me uncomfortable, it makes me uncomfortable, it makes me uncomfortable
ustedes una tontería pero es que me
eh And the thing is, I do
incomoda me incomoda me incomoda eh Y es
n't know Why the  The truth is I don't
que no sé el Por qué la verdad es que no
know why Of course I have the feeling that the
sé el Por qué Claro intuyo que las
alerts are not going to appear either because yes
alertas tampoco van a salir pues si lo
what I find strange is that this appears
lo que me resulta raro es que salga esto
and the members If this appears and the
y los miembros Si salen esto y los
members If they appear but of course the
miembros Si salen pero claro los
steel markers and this aero then I have the
marcadores acero y esto aero entonces
feeling that the alerts the
intuyo que la que las alertas los
superchat And that well they are not going to appear
superchat Y eso pues no van a salir
either
tampoco
So we are going to be here a little
Entonces vamos a estar aquí un poco a
blind I don't even know how many people are there the chat I'm
ciegas no sé ni cuánta gente hay el chat
going to see it on this screen
lo voy a ver en esta pantalla no pasa
nothing happens okay man it bothers me because I would
nada vale me hombre me molesta porque me
like it to appear on the
gustaría que apareciera en
screen well no the alerts do not appear
pantalla pues no no aparecen las alertas
Look over there pieces you have only given away
Mira por ahí pedazos solo has regalado
five members and no and they do not
cinco miembros y no y no
appear [ __ ] Thanks piece sun by the
aparecen [__] Gracias pedazo sol por
way Rey well they do not appear man they do not
cierto Rey pues no aparecen tío no
appear what do we do man do we do the
aparecen qué hacemos tío hacemos el
live or do we leave today this This could
directo o nos vamos hoy esto Esto puede
be a sign of Chaos eh be On Fire
ser una señal de Caos eh estate On Fire
Javi No no this could be a sign of
Javi No no esto podría ser una señal de
Chaos eh
Caos eh
Well hey we can be a little there
Bueno oye podemos estar un poco ahí a
blind not without knowing the Super chat Well
siegas no sin saber los Super chat Bueno
super chat yes I am going to know them because I
super chat si los voy a saber porque lo
see it there in the chat they do not appear here on
veo ahí en el chat no aparecen aquí en
the screen but well I see them and I read
la pantalla pero bueno yo los veo y yo
them but we do not know the viewers that's
los leo pero no sabemos los espectadores
it  that was the loser's double chin oh my goodness we
ya está eso ha sido la papada del
'll see about it later don't
pringao madre mía luego lo veremos eso
forget it please Jose Luis
no se me olvide porfa José Luis
remind me let's not leave today without seeing the
recuérdamelo no nos vayamos hoy sin ver
loser's thing because it's ab pass ab pass it
lo del pringao porque
's
abdominales pase abdominales está de
[ __ ] awesome gundam seriously
[__] madre gundam en serio
gundam
gundam
gundan [ __ ] man
gundan [__]
we threw gundam out this afternoon I
tío lo hemos echado esta tarde a gundam
don't know if any of you were at the
no sé si habéis estado alguno en el
salsa bar live this afternoon but gundan is a
salsería de esta tarde pero gundan es un
kid that we threw out this afternoon
chiquillo que lo hemos echado esta tarde
from the salsa bar live because
del directo de la salsería porque
all his comments were more
todo todos sus comentarios eran así más
or less like that and and and picking a snag on everything
o menos y y y poniendo pega a todo lo
that you remember is there someone who was at
que os acordáis hay alguien que haya
the salsa bar live this afternoon
estado esta tarde en el directo de la
that we went on
salsería que nos hemos metido luego en
Twitter later and it turns out that he was there
en Twitter y resulta ser que estaba ahí
What I don't understand Of course well I
Yo lo que no entiendo Claro pues
understand that this is a kid not that he's in
entiendo que esto es un niño no que está
bad shape no I don't know the
fatal no no sé la
truth do you remember this one
verdad os acordáis de
but of course that was we're
este pero claro eso ha sido hace estamos
talking about 4 in the afternoon that was
hablando de las 4 de la tarde eso ha
5 hours ago I mean that
sido hace 5 horas O sea ese
kid is no longer here he's not even perfect See you
niño ya no está no hay ni perfecto Hasta
later Gan but of course this kid What's he wearing
luego Gan pero claro este niño Qué lleva
6  7 hours on the computer wherever he is
6 7 horas en el ordenador en donde
and he has
esté y tiene activadas las
notifications enabled for all channels,
notificaciones de todos los canales
all tweets, we've entered before
todos los twit hemos entrado antes
because he was being a pain in the ass in the chat.
porque estaba dando por culo en el chat
Note that there were 3 or 4000 people, I don't
Fíjate que había 3 o 4000 personas no me
remember how many there were, I don't know how many there were
acuerdo Cuántas había no sé cuántas
today, but well, two or 3000 people
había hoy pero bueno dos o 3000 personas
for sure, and he was there, hitting you, hitting
seguro y y estaba ahí dale que te pego
you, hitting you, hitting you and and being a pain in the
Dale que te pego Dale que te pego y y
ass, hitting you. Of course, but there
dando por culo dando por culo Claro pero
comes a time, of course. I understand
ya llega un momento claro Yo entiendo
that in the chat, you make better comments,
que en el chat ya comentarios mejores
worse comments, and some that
comentarios peores no y algunos que no
are not right, but of course it was like
tenen la razón pero claro era como un
the typical nonsense that those
los típicas tonterías que dicen los
channels say, not the ones he follows,
canales esos no a los que él sigue
and there comes a time when you
y y ya llega un momento que te
lose focus on what you're doing.
desconcentras de lo que estás haciendo
You're live watching a video and you're
Estás en directo viendo un vídeo y estás
there, the spam. Pin Pin Pin Pin, you know. And
ahí el spam Pin Pin Pin Pin sabes Y
then we just got on Twitter and
entonces Justo nos metemos en Twitter y
we saw his Twitter account, which was
hemos visto su cuenta de Twitter que se
called Herdal, he suffered a lot, with every
llamaba herdal ha sufrio mucho a cada
tweet that I posted, posting a
tweet que yo ponía poniendo un
comment, he'd been doing it for days, has been doing it for days. Of course,
comentario llevaba días lleva días Claro
what's the life of this, this little
que Cuál es la vida de esta de esta
person,
personilla
little thing,
cosilla
eh  little thing little thing Hey, well it bothers me
eh cosilla cosilla Oye pues me molesta
a lot, eh, the fact that the chat doesn't appear
un montón eh lo de que no aparezca el
bothers me a lot, but oh well,
chat me molesta un montón pero bueno
let's
vamos a
try, let's try so that it doesn't go
intentar vamos a intentar que no pase
unnoticed.
desapercibir
Well, man, Julio, it will surely be
bueno Sí hombre Julio seguramente será
from those channels, of course, which one, if not from
de esos canales claro de cuál si no de
here, from here, from the Cotio del Arrosito, it
aquí de de aquí del cotio del arrosito
will not come, surely that will be from
no va a venir seguramente eso será de
the K youtubers,
los youtubers K
of course, and the parents of these creatures,
claro y los padres de estas criaturas
man, no. Let's see, you can do it, for
hombre no A ver tú le puedes tú yo por
example, with Leo, I sometimes let him have
ejemplo a Leo sí que le dejo algunas
the tablet with videos of
veces la tablet con vídeos de juegos de
animal games and things like that, but of course, I know,
animales y esas cosas no pero claro son
the child has been on the tablet for 6 or 7 hours, I do
ya se 6 7 horas lleva el niño con la
n't
tablet no lo
understand, these are things that I don't see. Well,
entiendo son cosas que no veo bueno qu
how are you, man? How are you, family? I'm
Cómo estáis tío Cómo estáis familia Yo
a little tired today, right? I
hoy un poco cansado verdad que hoy rompí
finally broke my schedule. As much as I want
el horario al final Por más que quiera
the job and what we do, well,
el trabajo y a lo que nos dedicamos pues
obviously it's inevitable that one
evidentemente es inevitable que algún
day you will have to break it. This is
día lo tengas que romper esto funciona
how it works, and as much as I want it, it would be
así y por más que yo quiera muy
very complicated, no, it would be very complicated,
complicado sería que no muy complicado
no, unless you don't care a
sería que no a no ser que te dé igual un
little, no, but of course yesterday I gave
poco no pero claro el día de ayer yo di
a very big exclusive at the
una exclusiva muy tocha en en la
salsera that  by the way speaking of the
salsería que por cierto hablando de la
very huge exclusive
exclusiva muy tocha
let's go to Lily's Twitter well not
vamos al Twitter de Lily bueno no el
Lily's Twitter not
Twitter de Lily no primero el
mine first I mean yesterday we gave a super
mío O sea ayer dimos una exclusiva super
huge exclusive I think it's the biggest exclusive
tocha Yo creo que es la la exclusiva más
of any gossip channel of
de de cualquier canal de salseo de de
kids in a long time eh I
chavalería de de hace mucho tiempo eh o
mean and I think the previous ones have been
sea y creo que las anteriores han sido
mine Also okay but yesterday we gave a huge
mías Igualmente vale pero ayer dimos una
exclusive ima Okay and what happened
exclusiva tochs ima Okay y y lo que pasó
was well because I had to do a
fue que bueno porque tuve que hace un
live broadcast at noon giving the exclusive
directo al mediodía dando la exclusiva
okay as you can see H it's no small thing the
vale como veis H no es poca cosa la
bomb the tweet alone the tweet has
bomba el twit solamente el twit tiene un
6 million views okay It's no small
6 millones de visitas vale No es poca
thing the bomb was a pretty
cosa la bomba era una noticia bastante
pretty huge news the truth is quite
bastante tocha la verdad bastante
quite strong and a very well
bastante fuerte e un matrimonio muy
known couple in the world of kids
conocido en el mundo de la chavalería
okay of the salsera and And well then there we
vale de la salsería y Y bueno pues ahí
go with the with the exclusive Okay
ahí tiramos con la con la exclusiva Vale
so last night I had to stay
entonces anoche me tuve que quedar
awake
despierto
to wait for them to
para para esperar que ellos e
confirm the exclusive And that's how it was
confirmaran la exclusiva Y así fue Se
The exclusive was confirmed Uh it wasn't it wasn't
confirmó la exclusiva Eh no era no eran
bad informants what I had okay And
malos informantes lo que tenía vale Y
as you can see that's what I'm telling you I mean
como veis que es lo que os digo o sea
this is not this is  a bomb okay I mean
esto no es esto es una bomba vale o sea
this isn't some [ __ ] news
esto no es una chorrada de noticias
you know so I had to stay at I don't know
sabes entonces tenía que quedarme a no
what time I posted this tweet 4 in the
sé a qué hora puse este tweet 4 de la
morning Look at 4 in the morning they already
mañana Mira a las 4 de la mañana ya
released this pom pom I left this tweet
sacaron esto pom pom dejé yo este tweet
calmly Okay and
tranquilamente Vale y ya
I already and I already and I went to sleep but
me y ya me y ya me fui a dormir pero
of course I've already broken the schedule today yes it's
claro ya he roto el horario hoy sí que
true that I didn't have the gym in the
es verdad que no tenía gimnasio por la
morning because the trainer had
mañana porque el el entrenador tenía
things to do So I did
cosillas que hacer Entonces yo sí que
have an appointment with him to
tenía una cita con con el con el para
give the dog a vaccine but I
ponerle una vacuna al perro pero la he
let it go because I had to sleep and I
dejado tirar porque tenía que dormir y
'm a little I'm a little tired Me
estoy un poco estoy un poco cansad Yo
today Okay then Today I'm going to be on
hoy Vale entonces Hoy voy a estar en
telesalseo until today it's going to be on
telesalseo hasta que hoy va a estar en
tes salseo until the editor tells me
tes salseo hasta que me avise el editor
that he has the video the main one okay I
de que tiene el vídeo el principal vale
understand it will be a couple of hours and a half or
entiendo será un par de horas y media o
three So we're going to be here for a couple
tres Entonces vamos a estar aquí un par
of hours and a half surely or three as long as it
de horas y media seguramente o tres las
takes until from here we
que hagan falta hasta que de aquí nos
go to the premiere of the main Channel
vayamos al estreno del Canal principal
okay we're going to make a video today on the
vale vamos a hacer un vídeo hoy en el
main channel that I think is
canal principal que yo creo que que es
one of the ones that you like cinema okay
uno de los que os gusta cine vale cine
fantastic cinema  and and after that to sleep to
fantástico y y ya después de eso a mimir
sleep and tomorrow Friday we'll see Let's
a mimir y mañana viernes ya veremos A
see Today is a very important day in
ver no Hoy es un día muy importante en
my life family
mi vida familia
eh Because
eh Porque
among other
entre otras
things among other things no and so much
cosas entre otras cosas no y tantas
news so many exclusives eh Well
noticias tantas exclusivas eh Bueno pues
today it's been 14 years A day like me 14
hoy hace 14 años Un día como yo hace 14
years ago as I put it Here I discovered what
años como bien puse Aquí descubrí lo que
unconditional love was okay
era el amor incondicional okay
eem I still haven't assumed This is okay I mean
eem Todavía no he asumido Esto vale o
yes it's true
sea sí que es verdad
that there's the congratulations no and
que que ahí está la felicitación no y
so on
demás
[Music]
[Música]
By the way I have an album from this
Por cierto tengo un álbum este de este
trip the album is
viaje el álbum es una
beautiful okay I mean it's amazing I'm going to
preciosidad vale o sea una pasada voy a
upload some photos later Although people are
subir alguna foto luego Aunque la gente
going to realize that they're not
se va a dar cuenta que no son
current because because I don't have tattoos
actuales porque porque no tengo tatuajes
on my arms okay but but there are some
en los brazos vale pero pero hay alguna
really cool photos that of course back
foto chulísimas que claro yo aquí en
then I didn't use social media as much maybe I
aquel entonces no usaba las redes tanto
'm talking to you about
a lo mejor esto estoy hablándote del
2012 or
2012 o
2013 well maybe 14 I don't know maybe 14 I do
2013 bueno quizás 14 No lo sé quizás 14
n't know here she would have been four
No lo sé aquí tendría ella cuatro
rings no and and I have this it's a
añillos no y y tengo esto es un álbum
brutal album I mean I have her Blanca's dress it
brutal O sea la tengo la vesti de Blanca
was a week the trip the dress of  Snow
fue una semana el viaje la vesti de
White the vti of Mary Popping the
blancanieve la vti de Mary popping la
well I have it of all the here she
bueno la tengo de de tod la aquí se
paints her
pinta la
face but she fooled me they fooled me they
cara pero me enga me engañaron me
fooled me 14 years old
engañaron 14 años
wow 14 years old at what point did I get stuck with
guo 14 años en qué momento me encajé con
a 14 year old daughter no and well Well
una hija de 14 años no y bueno Pues nada
here I have put the but yes it is true
aquí he puesto el pero sí que es verdad
that
que
today has been very thoughtful this has been
hoy ha sido muy reflexivo esto ha sido
very thoughtful this because it is like
muy reflexivo esto porque es como
[ __ ] 14 years old I was already in Let's see not going
hostias 14 años ya estaba yo en A ver no
out obviously or anything but
saliendo evidentemente ni nada pero
man you were already starting to go out with your
hombre ya empezabas a bajar con los
friends no and so on don't feel very or
amigotes no y demás no siéntete muy or
Lorena and you are wonderful parents
Lorena y tú son maravillosos padres
well Thank you very much thank you very much Well
bueno Muchas gracias muchas gracias Pues
yes let's see I have said it many times and it
sí a ver lo he dicho muchas veces y no
is not a lie that I am very
es ninguna mentida que tengo mucha
lucky I am very lucky my daughter is
suerte tengo mucha suerte mi hija es
wonderful a great student also
maravillosa estupenda estudiante además
Well she told me that she is not going to get a
Bueno me ha dicho que no se va a echar
boyfriend until she is 30 years old then
novio hasta que tenga 30 años entonces
Divine No apart from being very beautiful very nice very
Divino No aparte guapísima lindísima muy
good girl an incredible heart no and my
buena niña un corazón increíble no y mi
son the same I mean my son is very
hijo igual o sea mi hijo es es muy
little but But well I mean
chiquitillo pero Pero bueno o sea
Simply yes if you see the love she has
Simplemente si si veis el amor que tiene
for animals
por los animales
eh there already  you get a little idea of the
eh ahí ya os hacéis una pequeña idea del
character no but yes yes yes I mean I already
personaje que no pero sí sí sí O sea yo
won I already won Although people haven't found
ya gané yo ya gané Aunque la gente no se
out yet I I have already
ha enterado todavía yo yo ya hace tiempo
won for a long time I have already won My
Que gané yo ya hace tiempo Que gané mi
grandson won Hey but I'm seeing that a lot of
nieto Oye pero estoy viendo que mucha
people are putting me today that it's also your
gente me estáis poniendo hoy que también
birthday What a coincidence
cumplís año Qué casualidad
no What a coincidence no
no Qué casualidad no
Elena I was I was
Elena Yo es que tenía es que te estoy
reading you a little late now because
leyendo un poco con retraso ya porque no
the chat doesn't appear on the screen I'm
aparece el chat en pantalla lo estoy
seeing it here next to it my sister
viendo aquí al lado yo es que mi hermana
when she was a girl I have to upload a
cuando chica eso tengo que subir una
photo it's just that I couldn't fit it better call
foto es que no me ha cabido llam más
But my sister when she was a girl in
vale Pero mi hermana cuando chica en la
kindergarten did a very pretty
guardería hiciera un baile muy bonito de
Mary Popping dance but in a super elaborate way I mean
Mary popping pero en plan super currado
not in a way Well an outfit to
O sea no en plan Bueno un traje para
get by no no no no a
salir del paso no no no no un traje de
Mary Poppin outfit wait I'm going to put it
Mary poppin espérate lo voy a poner
censoring the girl's face wait a
censurando la cara de la niña espera un
moment because it's worthy of B I mean it
momento porque es que es digno de B sea
's to show off also eh it
es que es para presumirlo además eh es
's worthy of B this outfit was made by my
que es digno de B este traje lo hizo mi
grandmother and and This was this of course this This
abuela y y Esto fue esto claro esto Esto
cost me my life that my  sister
me costó la vida que mi hermana me lo
let me have it because of course this is an outfit
dejara porque claro esto es un traje de
my sister wore when my sister was little
mi hermana cuando mi hermana era chica
in kindergarten but of course
en la guardería pero pero claro eso
my sister had it saved like
tenía lo tiene mi hermana guardado como
gold and I told her
como como oro en paño no Y yo le dije
sister let me put it on the
hermana déjamelo que se lo ponga a la
girl because she's going to grow up the girl wo
niña que que que va a crecer la niña ya
n't be able to wear it anymore let me
no se lo va a poder poner nunca déjamelo
put it on her and I'll take pictures of her
que se lo ponga y que le haga yo fotos
at Disney with the outfit
en Disney con el traje
because you know, I mean well no
porque a ver sabes o sea bueno no en
actually I don't think it was that hard for me eh
realidad creo que no me costó tanto eh
Actually I think she said yes but it
En realidad creo que me dijo que sí pero
's true that she said it was a big
sí que es verdad que me dijo como mucho
rush to ask her because it was something very you
apuro pedírselo porque era algo muy
know [ __ ] very valuable very valuable
sabes [__] muy valioso muy valioso
also that this is not an outfit that you
además que que esto no es un traje que
buy Eh This took and I think the
se compre Eh Esto cogió y creo que la
kindergarten the kindergarten teachers
guardería las profesoras de la guardería
sent the patterns and they had to
mandaron los patrones y lo tenían que
make it let's say this is handmade
hacer vamos que esto está hecho a mano
Look you're going to freak out
Mira Vais a
we're talking about
flipar esto estamos hablando que sería
year 14 so I'm talking
el año 14 entonces estoy hablando
Look you're going to freak out with the
yo Mira vas Vais a flipar con la
princess obviously I'm going
princesa evidentemente voy
to of course I have to censor
a claro evidentemente tengo que censurar
the face for a moment
la cara un momento
let's see baby baby I don't care
a ver de bebé de bebé no me importa
having uploaded some images but  as a baby
haber subido alguna imagen pero de bebé
but of course here here what happens
pero claro ya aquí ya aquí lo que pasa
is that it is recognizable at least
es que s es reconocible por lo menos
to me eh Maybe for me eh
para mí eh A lo mejor para mí eh A lo
Maybe for me Maybe for me that maybe it is
mejor para mí A lo mejor para mí que a
not recognizable but at
lo mejor no es reconocible pero por lo
least for me okay
menos para mí vale
eh look at the
eh mirar el
outfit okay I mean e
traje vale o sea
This is handmade with some
e Esto está hecho a mano con unos
patterns and everything and and and they were stopping us they
patrones y demás y y y nos iban parando
were stopping everyone for the
nos iban parando todo el mundo por el
outfit that the
traje que llevaba la
girl was wearing because also the girls
niña porque es que además las niñas se
sell several princess outfits not in
venden varios trajes de princesa no en
the Disney stores but that outfit is not available that one there is not that one
la tiendas Disney pero ese traje no lo
my grandmother made it I
hay ese no lo hay ese lo hizo mi abuela
love it crazy eh crazy and her
amo una locura eh una locura y su
umbrella Her heels you
paragua Sus tacones
know crazy
sabes una locura
eh they were stopping us they were stopping us
eh nos iban parando nos iban parando
this they were stopping us and and they asked for
esto nos iban parando y y le pedían
photos of the they asked me permission
fotos a la a la me pedían permiso me
can I take a photo please with the
puedo hacer una foto por favor con la
girl but but a lot of people And
niña pero pero un montón de gente Y
of course there are some photos that I am going to
claro hay alguna foto que sí voy a
publish but mine uh from this trip
publicar pero mía eh de de este viaje
because I was around here
porque estaba por aquí
snooping around and and there is a photo that I
bicheando y y hay una foto que que he
said wow look at the gentleman wait and
dicho [__] Mira el caballero espérate
see if let's see if in Central
a ver si a ver si en el central
Plaza  Okay,
Plaza bueno esta
wait for this photo, I'm going to censor it and
foto espérate la voy a censurar y os la
show it to you. Listen to me, Elena. Look at this photo, it's
enseño escúchame Elena Mira esta foto es
crazy. Look at
de loco eh mira
this photo. What is it? Look,
esta foto Qué es
and this costume also has its
mira y este traje también tiene su
story. Look at this costume
historia Mira este traje
and in the in the in the
e en
Los Arcos shopping center in
el en los arc en el centro comercial de
Seville, Los Arcos okay, I'm
Sevilla los arcos vale que en estoy
talking 14 years ago 14 years ago there
hablando hace 14 años hace 14 años no
weren't as many shopping centers
había tantísimos centros comerciales
as there are now in Seville. I mean, I
como ahora en Sevilla o sea yo me
remember that in my neighborhood, near my
acuerdo que de mi barrio cerca de mi
neighborhood, it was good on one side, Los
barrio estaba bueno por un lado los
Arcos on the other side, nervous Elena, and
arcos por otro lado nervión Elena y
listen to me, Elena,
escúchame
stop counting.
elenea para de contar
No, I mean, shopping centers, I was
no O sea centros comerciales estaba en
nervous, there were Los Arcos. Also, I
nervios estaban los arcos que además me
remember when Los Arcos, when I was a
acuerdo cuando los arcos cuando yo era
kid, it was new, it was like new. I mean,
chico era nuevo era como nuevo o sea
shopping centers in
centros comerciales en
Seville that had like that, a lot of
Sevilla que tuvieran así un montón de
big stores and and so on, a little more, uh, a
tiendas grande y y demás poco más eh
little more. Talking 14 years ago, a little
poco más t hablando hace 14 años poco
more, a little more, it seems to me that, stop
más poco más me parece que para de
counting. No, no, yes, yes, no, a little more, well, And
contar No no sí sí no poco más bueno Y
then Los Arcos was so crowded back
entonces los arcos era tan concurrido en
then that there was a
aquel entonces que había una tienda
Disney store, a Disney store, but now there are
Disney una tienda Disney que ahora hay
very few. I don't know why, the truth is, there
muy pocas no sé el Por qué la verdad
was that  time when they opened several in
hubo esa época de que abrieron varias
various parts of Eh well I don't know
por por varias partes de Eh bueno no sé
if in Europe or in the world okay I
si de Europa o de o del mundo vale
understand that in the world of the
entiendo que del mundo de las ciudades
most important cities or whatever okay but
más importantes o lo que sea vale pero
here in Spain there weren't many I mean I understand that there would be
aquí en España había no muchas o sea
Maybe in Madrid
entiendo que habría A lo mejor en Madrid
here in Seville one I think in
aquí en Sevilla una creo que en
Barcelona there was another okay But well the
Barcelona había otra vale Pero bueno la
Disney store I had a thing with the
tienda Disney yo tenía una cosa con la
Disney store that was let's go as a
tienda Disney que era el vamos yo iba de
tourist to the Disney store to go in or
turismo a la tienda Disney para entrar o
rather because it's like the stores I don't
sea porque la es como las tiendas yo no
know if you have come to
sé si ustedes la habéis llegado a
know it but it was like they are like the
conocer pero era como son como las
stores that are in the park in Seville
tiendas que hay en el parque en Sevilla
okay the store with exclusive
vale la tienda con cosas exclusivas de
Disney things that aren't available anywhere else Okay
Disney que no hay en otro lado Ok
so there were the typical
entonces estaban los los típicos
dresses not of the princesses and I
vestidos no de las princesas y a mí este
was in love with this dress man because it was I
vestido me tenía enamorado tío porque es
had it let's say I have it saved that I do
que tenía es vamos lo tengo guardado que
n't know if it's on
no sé si está a
hand It's that it's not going to be on hand
mano Es que es que no va a estar a mano
if I didn't show it to you but it's
si no os lo enseñaba pero es
like I mean with a lot of quality I mean it was
como o sea con mucha calidad o sea era
with a lot of quality like with with with the
con mucha idad como con con con el el
velvet this navy blue
terciopelo este azul marino tenía
also had some what's it
también unos cómo se
called It's not embroidered
llama No es bordado
it's what's it called damn when it has a
es cómo se llama [__] cuando tiene
drawing but no no
dibujo pero no no
stitching  you know how to tell you what
costura sabéis Cómo os
it's called not embroidered brocade
eso no bordado
not brocade not printed not printed
brocado no brocado no estampado no
printed
estampado estampado
No yes like a relief but not embroidered
No sí como un relieve pero no bordado
printed I would say I would say
estampado yo diría yo diría que
printed brocade are you calling it
estampado brocado lo estáis llamando por
brocade out there I've never heard of it
ahí alguno brocado No lo escuchado yo
but you know what I mean no
nunca pero sabéis a lo que me refiero no
way it's not sewn nor is it like a relief
sea no es cosido ni es como un relieve
within the same fabric that is like
dentro de la misma tela que es así como
a third hair okay the navy blue and
un tercio pelillo vale lo azul marino y
then the yellow that apart from having the
luego el amarillo que aparte de tener la
skirt part of the dress had another
parte de la falda del vestido tenía otra
skirt that was the the fabric is
falda que era la la telita esta
transparent and such or it was of very high
transparente y tal o sea era con mucha
quality the dress if you see it beautiful
calidad el vestido si lo veis precioso
the dress okay And I fate your my thing
el vestido vale Y yo fate tú la cosa mía
super Freaky okay I would have the girl let's say
super Freaky vale tendría la niña vamos
two options I'm speaking from memory
dos opciones estoy hablando de memoria
eh either the girl was months old or she hadn't been
eh o la niña tenía meses o no había
born but I already knew it was a girl
nacido pero yo ya sabía que era una niña
probably she hadn't been born but I already
probablemente no había nacido pero yo ya
knew it was a girl I bought the dress
sabía que era una niña compré el vestido
to have it
para tenerlo
saved I bought the dress to have it
guardado compré el vestido para tenerlo
saved and you know what happens that when when it
guardado y sabéis qué pasa que ya cuando
was when we went
ya cuando fue ya cuando fuimos
m No, that dress is no longer available they
m No ya ese vestido no lo hay no lo
hadn't sold the Snow White dress but they
había venden vestido de Blanc nieve pero
are not the same they are like more shabby that
no son iguales son como más cutre ese
dress no  there is
vestido no lo
one they were like more tacky like
hay tiene uno eran como más cutre como
more of less quality and trust you that is I
más de menos calidad y fíate tú que es
bought it for her because I was in
Se lo compré porque es que estaba
love with the suit I say this I
enamorado del traje digo yo esto a mi
have to put it on my little girl with the little girl
niña se lo tengo que poner con la niña
unborn or unborn or just born like
sin nacer o sin nacer o recién nacía en
just born you know and I say well I'll
plan recién nacida sabes y digo pueso se
buy it for her and she'll
lo compro y ya se lo
put it on her damn and there I had it
pondrá [__] y ahí lo tenía yo
one day when she's of legal age let her
un día ya cuando ella sea mayor de edad
show you show you the photo
que os enseñe que os enseñen la foto
so you can see how beautiful how beautiful she
para que veáis lo bonito que lo bonita
was that she
que era
was And it is that she was and it is because she is
que que era Y es que era y es porque es
very pretty But anyway family back to the
lindísima Pero bueno familia volviendo
topic of yesterday's exclusive
al tema de la de la exclusiva de ayer
okay back to the topic of
vale volviendo al tema de la exclusiva
yesterday's exclusive it
de ayer
turns out that they sent me What does my
resulta que me mandan Qué dice mi
Elena say Let's go to Disney Let's go let's go
Elena Vámonos a Disney Vámonos
I wanted to go yeah I wanted to go a
vamos yo quise ir es yo quise ir hace un
couple of weeks ago where did we go the [ __ ]
par de seman hace a donde fuimos [__]
when we went what was this thing
cuando fuimos a qué es lo que fue esto
in Granada was the last thing no to Granada no
de Granada fue lo último no a Granada no
that the little girl wanted to go somewhere else I don't
que la niña quería irse a otro lado no
know what I didn't want to go out anymore I
sé qué yo ya no quería salir más yo le
told her I love Disney and also with my car
dije amo Disney y además con mi coche
that I really want to go  with my
que tengo muchas ganas de ir con mi
car I mean like you know what, the
coche o sea en plan sabes es que yo
planes is that I get lazy with
losos aviones es que yo me da una pereza
planes the plane thing I go with my
los aviones el tema aviones yo con mi
car wherever you tell me go to the car I've
coche voy donde tú me digas iga al coche
gone everywhere this year
he ido a todos lados en este mismo año
the car won I think I did
ganó el coche creo que he hecho
Barcelona well Barcelona was
Barcelona bueno Barcelona fue lo del año
last year I say this year but I don't I don't
pasado digo este mismo año pero no me no
realize how time flies but
me doy cuenta cómo pasa el tiempo pero
we're in September we're entering
estamos en septiembre estamos entrando
October it was November But anyway
en octubre fue noviembre Pero bueno
[Music]
[Música]
Barcelona Santander
Barcelona Santander
Urias Vigo or Porto Madrid I don't even know how
Urias vigo o Porto madrido ya no sé ni
many times I go with the car wherever you
las veces yo con el coche donde tú
want What's happening that Paris is a little
quieras Qué pasa que París está un poco
further I have to stay and sleep along
más lejos me tengo que qued a dormir por
the way I
el camino me
stay but I'm going with me I
quedo pero yo me voy con m yo con mi
go better with my car damn the [ __ ] [ __ ] of the
coche voy mejor [__] la [__] [__] del
plane you know you have to be if it
avión sabes que tienes que estar que si
goes through here or if it goes through there You're going to
pasa por aquí que si pasa por allá Vas a
get on they make you take off your seatbelt then put it back on
montarte te hacen quitarte el cinturón
take off all
luego volvértelo a poner quitarte todas
the bracelets then put it back on
las pulseras luego volvértelo a poner
now then If you get it right or if you don't get it right
ahora luego Si aciertas o si no aciertas
last time I had to
la última vez tuve que
buy I bought this
comprar compré este
This was here I was already on YouTube I
Esto fue aquí estaba yo ya en YouTube
bought the stuffed animal and I bought the Mickey
compré el peluche y compré el Mickey
this  from here okay imagine what I had to do to
este de aquí vale imaginaros la que tuve
bring that
que liar yo para traerme
imagine what I
eso imaginaros la que tuve que la que
had to do
tuve que liar
to bring that when you go in your
yo para traerme eso cuando tú vas en tu
car it moves you whenever you want
coche te mueve a la hora que te da la
wherever you want and you and you and
gana por donde te da la gana y te y te y
you fit whatever you want and it comes to you
te cabe lo que tú quieras y te viene
wherever you want and Paris I see it as
donde tú quieras y París yo lo veo
accessible I think it's how many there are Paris
accesible creo que son cuántos son París
20 hours more or less I don't know Okay so much
20 horas más o menos no sé Bueno tanto
No look wait I'm going to look I'm going to
No miral espérate lo voy a mirar voy a
look how much it would be to Disney
mira cuánto sería a Disney
okay it would be let's hope this year already
vale sería peramos yo este año ya yo
this year I don't think I'm going to go anywhere
este año creo que no voy a ir a ningún
else eh damn look I have it in the
lado más eh [__] mira lo tengo en el
search engine that I went to look at it a little while ago
buscador de que lo fui a mirar hace poco
16 hours 16 hours but that 16 hours
16 horillas 16 horas pero eso 16 horas
What is 16 hours is that I leave at
Qué es 16 horas es que salgo a las 12 de
midnight and arrive at 4 in the afternoon I'll
la noche y llego a las 4 de la tarde eso
do that I'll do that
lo hago yo eso lo hago
Hey Concha sir it won't be the one from
yo Oye Concha caballer no será la de
yesterday no well Of course because if it were laer it would
ayer no bueno Claro porque si fuera laer
n't be sir it would be Miss miss
no sería caballer sería
eh Please
Señorita señorita eh Por favor
miss 16 hours
señorita 16 horas lo hago
I'll do it how good is it  I gave Lorena the
yo qué bueno es le puse a Lorena la
call from yesterday eh You think it's not You
llamada de ayer eh Te crees que no Tú te
think it's normal
crees que es es normal
kid You think it could be
chiquillo te crees que puede ser
that Anyway they sent me this dude
eso Total que que me mandan esto tío
this screenshot that I said
esta captura que dicho
Look you can't have this sense you have to
yo Mira tú no puedes tener este sen hay
have a little bit of common sense ridiculous
que tener un poquito de sentio ridículo
many times or rather this is like when
muchas veces o sea esto es como cuando
Tania did it she did this same thing
lo hizo Tania hizo esto mismo
with this writer who
con con lo del escritor este que le
called the queen a [ __ ] okay do you remember
decía zorra a la reina vale os acordáis
Exactly the same let's see if you
Exactamente lo mismo vamos ver si tú
have an obsession with a person and
tienes una obsesión con una persona y
a very strange thing
una cosita muy extraña
okay don't show it in public And if you
vale no lo demuestres en público Y si tú
're trying to boycott because
estás intentando hacer un boicot porque
you've tried to boycott not the
tú has intentado hacer un boicot no lo
same as always no what's going on well
mismo de siempre no qué es lo que pasa
in the magazine lectura yesterday they
pues que en la revista lectura ayer
published an article Franco Cuesta takes a
sacan un artículo Franco cuesta toma
stand and comes out in defense serves
partido y sale en defensa sirve a
bronchalo I don't know what I don't know how much and they put
bronchalo no sé qué no sé cuánto y ponen
My video let's see you put Jai
Mi vídeo vamos a ver tú pones Jai
Oliveira in Google news and you
oliveira en Google en noticias y te
get a ton of news okay either
salen un montón de noticias vale o bien
a video of mine from Daniel Sancho or an
un vídeo mío de Daniel Sancho o bien una
exclusive of mine from I don't know who or I don't know
exclusiva mía de no sé quién o no sé
how much it's very normal it's  very normal Tania
cuánto es muy normal es muy normal Tania
You think that based on Twitch you're going to
Tú te crees a base de Twitch tú vas a
get me not to be shown in any
conseguir que no me saquen en ningún
media Tania the expert youtuber on the
medio Tania el youtuber experto en el
subject The one who has worked hard Since nobody is
tema El que se lo ha currado Como nadie
called trium don't get
se llama trium no se
confused apart from that don't do this in
confundan aparte esto no lo hagas en
public we're all watching T
público que estamos viendo el T todo el
Tania Tania This is not an obsession something
Tania Tania Esto no es obsesión una cosa
that doesn't even concern you it's from Daniel
que no va ni contigo que es de Daniel
Sancho de Franco this because they're
Sancho de Franco esta porque están
writing an article about one of my videos if I
haciendo un artículo de un vídeo mío si
go out almost every
salgo casi tod todos los
day But you don't mind putting it in
días Pero tú no te da cosilla ponerlo en
public where
público que lo ve la
people see it Well of course triun is the
gente Pues claro que triun es el el
best youtuber of trine that's why he comes
youtuber mejor de trine por eso viene
here he does it so that it can be seen so that it can be
aquí lo hace eso para que se la vea para
seen that Mimi making a
que se la vea que Mimi haciendo el
fool of herself no so that she can be seen making a
ridículo no para que se la vea haciendo
fool of herself no and here Lili has put
el ridículo no y aquí Lili le ha puesto
a sasc case that has been good These are
un sasc caso que ha sido bueno Estos son
exclusives from
exclusivas de del mes
last month of those that came out
pasado de las que salieron en todas
everywhere, I mean on all the televisions they
partes o sea en todas las televisiones
even came out with my exclusives from the
incluso salieron las exclusivas mías del
year Uy from last year
año Uy del año pasado las exclusivas
my exclusives from last month the interview [ __ ]
mías del mes pasado la entrevista zorra
Uy [ __ ]  the fox interview with
Uy zorra la entrevista zorro a
sape when I arrive look
sape cuando llego mira
francoa welcomes Javi
francoa le da la bienvenida a Javi
oliveira in her own way You're an [ __ ]
oliveira a su manera Eres un cabrón vale
okay I mean trust yourself by publishing an article about
o sea fíate tú sacando un artículo marca
my arrival in
de mi llegada a
Thailand You think Tania that based
Tailandia Tú te crees Tania que a base
on tweets you're going to tell the media that
de twit tú le vas a decir a los medios a
jav is going to silence him don't talk
jav le voy a ir a silenciarlo no hablis
about
de
him you know what's going on
él sabes qué pasa
Tania that you only loved me you
Tania que me queríais solo me queríais
only loved me you also wanted me without
solo me queríais aparte me queríais sin
work you wanted me without channels and you don't
trabajo me queríais sin canales y no os
realize that no that I already won I've already
enterais que eso no que yo ya gané Ya lo
said it In total today
dicho Total que hoy se han hecho eco de
all the Spanish
de la noticia todos los medios españoles
and Latin American media have echoed the news eh jav oliveira
y latinoamericano eh jav oliveira en
exclusively comments on the breakup and
exclusiva comenta la ruptura y el
divorce of Juan guarnizo and ar gameplay
divorcio de Juan guarnizo y ar gameplay
in a lot okay in all of these Look at
en un montón vale en todos estos Mira
Los 40 Principales as Mexico marks half
Los 40 Principales as México marca medio
in everything eh in everything everything all all the
en todo eh en todo todo tod todos los
media in all the media in addition they have also
medios en todos los medios además se han
put my tweets and they put my
además se ponen mis tweet y ponen mis
clicks and and they give credit that you want it
clicks y y dan crédito que eso quieras
or not to me as long as they give credit it's worth it I
que no a mí con que den crédito me vale
mean when I give  a news look you see it
o sea cuando yo doy una noticia mira lo
abc abc news Mexico eh as for me they
abc abc noticias México eh a mí mientras
give perfect credit I mean as
que a mí que den crédito perfecto o sea
long as they give credit look at it eh
mientras que den crédito míralo eh
exclusive by Javi Oliveira damn it
exclusiva de Javi oliveira [__] madre no
's not what there is
es lo que hay
or no
o no
Elena we did it we did it again we
Elena lo hicimos lo hicimos otra
did it
vez lo hicimos de
again but it's just a matter of
nuevo pero es que es ya cuestión de de
making a fool of yourself and let's see it's like a
hacer ridículo y y a ver es como
tantrum it's already ridiculous And a tantrum
pataleta es ya es el ridículo Y pataleta
you know
sabes
why you put that up that everyone
para qué te pones a poner eso que todo
sees it man the exclusive was big eh
ve hombre la exclusiva era gorda eh
Elena this exclusive was big big
Elena esta exclusiva era gorda gorda
big says Javi if the very foreigners know you
gorda dice Javi si te conocen los muy
yes Mara de la Cruz little by
extranjeros sí María de la cruz poco a
little little by little before the foreigners knew me
poco poco a poco antes me conocían los
those who were a little bit
extranjeros los que eran un poquito
foreign but those who are very very
extranjeros pero ya los que son muy muy
very foreign already freak out with me they
muy extranjeros eso ya lo flipan conmigo
are learning the language today we are going to
están aprendiendo el idioma hoy vamos a
watch a very foreign video
ver un vídeo muy extranjero
eh today we are going to see today we are going to watch a
eh hoy vamos a ver hoy vamos a ver un un
very foreign video the
vídeo muy extranjero la
truth What does my
verdad Qué dice mi
alanne say but
alanne pero
Mimi let's see
Mimi a ver
This is like this I mean it depends on the
Esto es así O sea depende de de las
things that there are and the topics that there are maybe next
cosas que haya y de los temas que haya a
month Well
lo mejor el mes que viene Pues de
suddenly there is no  a lot of news I know
repente no hay muchas noticias yo que sé
but the problem is
pero el problema es
the problem is that they wanted me alone they
que el problema es que me querían solo
wanted me isolated they wanted me
me querían aislado me querían
Eh they wanted me to leave to leave
Eh me querían que me fuera que me fuera
Oh and don't you see it and don't you
Ay y no lo ven y no lo
see it by the way dude we
ven por cierto tío tenemos que ver
also have to look at things about the very foreigners
también cosas de los muy extranjeros
okay I'm going to try a little bit of chimillo
vale voy a tratar un poquito el chimillo
first we have to spend a while we have to spend a
primero tenemos para rato tenemos para
while and we're going there watching the gossip
rato y vamos ahí viendo el chismecito
first and then we'll go to the geeks
primero y y después iremos a los frikis
a little to see what they say and and we
un poquito a ver qué se cuentan y y
also have a little thing there that I don't
también tenemos ahí una cosilla que no
know if I'm going to be able to translate because it's very very
sé si la voy a poder Traducir porque es
very
muy muy muy
foreign it's very
extranjera es muy
foreign By the way the counter doesn't appear
extranjera Por cierto que no aparece el
and the chat I'm here a little blind
contador y y el chat estoy aquí un poco
man and they still want it well that they
tío y lo siguen queriendo bueno que
continue their fight and their cause no the people
sigan su lucha y su causa no la gente
need a cause eh people always
necesita una causa eh la gente siempre
need a
necesita una
cause for which they
causa por la que
fight here here in
lucha aquí qui en
rosaca 1439 that Elena the people that there are
rosaca 1439 que Elena la gente que hay
100 people here today who believe
100 personas hay aquí hoy que se creen
that I had undressed or what
que me había desnudado o qué
like there are 14 people
como hay 14 personas
here so early Well don't listen to me Don't
aquí tan temprano Bueno no escúchame No
believe it's
te creas son las
9 don't be 10 Yes
9 no sea las 10 Sí
yes and what what  we do Today
sí y qué que hacemos Hoy
then Hey I love it when they
entonces Oye a mí me encantan cuando
call like that I mean they're things that
llaman así o sea son cosas que que
only happen here eh if you
solamente pasan aquí eh si os dais
notice they're things that only happen here I mean the thing that
cuenta son cosas que solo pasan aquí o
suddenly but it's not
lo de que de repente pero no es de
sudden let's see yesterday I was talking not
repente a ver ayer yo estaba hablando no
reacting to things and then he
reaccionando a las cosas y entonces
got on the donkey he was on the donkey saying
subió al asne estuvo al asne diciendo
his things Well while I was on the
sus cosas Bueno pues mientras que estaba
donkey while I was online
al asne mientras que estaba lne no
the lady kept calling but she was
paraba la señora de llamar pero en plan
really annoying and of course I was like she would
super pesada y claro yo me quía que
be some monkey from these
sería cualquier monillo de eso de los
channels you know and come on call and come on
canales estos sabes y venga llam y venga
call and come on call and I'm like p
llam y venga llam y venga llam yo así p
p silencing the phone and there was one where I
p silenciando el móvil y ya hubo una que
said come on let's pick it up and let him say whatever he
digo venga vamos a cogerlo y que diga lo
wants and be funny and he hangs up
que quiera y haga la gracia y le cuelga
but of course the last thing I expected was that it
pero claro lo que menos me esperaba es
was a super angry lady eh
que era una señora super enfadada eh
but don't tell me those things aren't
pero no me digáis que esas cosas no son
fantasy in reality I mean they're things
fantasía en realidad o sea son cosas
like
como de
suddenly don't tell me that my Carmen
repente no me digas que mi Carmen la ha
saw it Don't tell me that my Carmen
visto No me digas que mi Carmen la ha
saw the
visto la
call and it's that I'm completely I've been doing it
llamada y es que estoy completamente
for 6
completamente hace 6
hours and I  that's how we go you see It already
horas y yo es que así vamos ves A mí ya
starts to start for me with this thing of Look, man Look, I don't
me empieza con lo de Mira macho Mira no
know what, come on, let's put on the call We
sé qué venga vamos a poner la llamada La
listen to Carmen or what, let's laugh for a
escuchamos a la Carmen o qué que nos
while We listen to Carmen or let's
rato la escuchamos a la Carmen o vamos
gossip, we're not in a
al chisme ya
hurry today, eh, I don't know about you,
no tenemos prisa hoy eh yo no sé ustedes
but we're not in a hurry today I'm going H here Today I'm
pero no tenemos prisa hoy voy H aquí Hoy
not going to go to the salsera today from here to the
no me voy a ir a la salsería hoy de aquí
video to the main page when the
al vídeo para el principal cuando est el
premiere is on and then stop and then stop to
estreno y después para y después para
bed Carmen is in bad shape and we
para la camita vem mal la Carmen y nos
have a laugh or
echamos una risa o
what Yes, no, I don't have the patience that
qué Sí no Yo no tengo esta paciencia que
Javichi has, no way, come on, let's
tiene javichi ni de coña venga vamos a
put on the call please, eh How funny I'm
poner la llamada por favor eh Qué risa
going to put on a little
Le voy a poner un poco
bit of speed but I'm cracking up I'm
de un poco de velocidad pero yo me parto
cracking up with the call what a moment How
me parto con la llamada qué momento Qué
funny and also These are the things that you do
risa y además Estas son las cosas que no
n't prepare and it comes out Not the call
que no preparas y sale No la llamada
because Javi, yes, Javi Or it's that they don't
porque Javi si que Javi O es que no le
normally call him Of course because
llaman normalmente Claro porque
normally he doesn't take calls or it's that
normalmente no es que coja llamadas o es
normally they don't call him, come on, let's
que normalmente no le llaman venga vamos
see about the call and the patience, let's
a ver lo de la llamada y la paciencia a
see how it can be done I always
ver como poder se puede Yo siempre lo
say if you want to send an audio, yes  do
digo si queréis mandar un audio si
you want to call or something okay what I don't
queréis llamar o algo vale lo que no
want is the the talking the a blote on
quiero es el el el hablar el a blote por
WhatsApp That's not that the a bloto pi pi No
WhatsApp Eso no eso el a bloto pi pi No
because I'm not going to sit here reading the
porque no me voy a poner aquí a leer
message You know what I'm telling you but if
mensaje Sabes lo que te digo pero si
someone has to call to do an
alguien tiene que llamar para hacer una
intervention like this it can always be done
intervención como esta siempre se puede
you understand a no I know that one day
me entiendes a no s que un día se pongan
28 people start calling and they don't let us have
a llamar 28 personas y no nos dejan haer
content you
contenido
know but the but the truth is that yes
sabes pero la pero la verdad que sí
man you can call I've always
hombre se puede llamar yo siempre lo he
said it but it happens that many times I say
dicho pero pasa que muchas veces digo
come on send some audio and nobody sends it How
venga manda unos audio y no lo manda
funny come on Who is it Look I'll
nadie Qué risa venga Quién es Mira te
explain let's see Look dude you've got me fed up with it you see Now I'm
explico vamos a ver Mira macho me tienes
starting with that Look dude Look I don't know
empieza con lo de Mira macho Mira no sé
what And then I say like this
qué Y ya ahí le digo así
eh respect respect because I start
eh respeta respeta porque empiezo Yo
Here with the machine gun and let's go but there
aquí con la metralleta y vamos pero ahí
Javi had Ah there he had art he had art you the and
Javi tuvo Ah ahí tuvo arte tuvo arte tú
all of you okay me I me okay
la y todos vosotros vale yo yo yo vale
I in person have lymphoma and cancer
Yo en persona tengo un linfoma y cáncer
kid
chaval
you
vosotros
Hello you the bne and the other and the one of the other and
Hola tú la bne y la otra y la de la otra
the one of the other Look at a but what's
y la de la otra Mira a a pero qué culpa
our fault  us but if the one who
tenemos nosotros pero si la que se lo ha
made it up was the other lady,
inventado ha sido la otra señora
complain to her or talk about lies this one who
reclámele a ella o hablar de [__] este
was telling people hey
que le iba diciendo a la gente oye que
Loli doesn't have anything that Loli is not
Loli no tiene nada que Loli no está
sick or has anything that she
enferma ni tiene nada que se la ha
made it up well and
inventado pues
I was because cancer is very
y me estaba porque el cáncer es muy
serious I've had cancer I don't know what And it is
serio yo he tenido cáncer no sé qué Y es
very serious and it is like clear precisely
muy serio y es como claro precisamente
That is the importance that we
Esa es la importancia que nosotros le
give to cancer when things happen like
damos al cáncer cuando pasan cosas como
what happened with Olih Huerta like the mockery they
lo del olih Huerta como las burlas que
made of Pilar like the 240 Of course yes yes that
le hicieron a Pilar como lo de los 240
is precisely why
Claro si si es por eso precisamente por
that subject is tremendously serious of
lo tremendamente serio que es ese tema
course I don't understand
claroo no entiendo
anything he is the best there can be there the
nada es el mejor que puede haber ahí el
best already with that already with that the woman is
mejor ya con eso ya con eso la mujer ya
no longer the best eh the best of all
ya no es el mejor eh el mejor de todos
already with that well each one has their
ya con eso bueno cada uno tiene sus
these of course Well a man is not like
estas claro Bueno un hombre no es como
you no no we agree look yes yes yes
tú no no estamos De acuerdo mira sí sí
no Of course we agree
sí no Claro que estamos de acuerdo
kid who do you think you are It's that it's that
chaval tú quién te crees que eres Es que
I don't know you I have an idea that's
es que yo no sé tú tengo una idea que
crazy eh restraining order how do you
flipas eh orden de alejamiento como se
say that So but it was me or rather
diga eso Entonces pero fui yo o sea lo
what  I can't I can say here ah take off
que no puedo Yo aquí decir ah se quita
the camera they attack me and look for me when it was
la cámara me atacan y me buscan cuando
me what happened to Marta I have an idea that's
yo lo de Marta fui yo tengo una idea que
crazy fam I was on the couch Saturday I don't do
flipas fam estaba en el sofá sábado no
direct I looked for her mouth with an
hago directo le busqué la boca con
insult well abnormal I put it and such
insulto bueno anormal le puse y tal
Thanks imaculada Valenzuela who has
Gracias imaculada Valenzuela que ha
renewed membership already because she's
renovado membresía ya porque está
smoking she does
fumando
n't take off the camera because she's
no se quita la cámara porque está
No my coach sends me a WhatsApp he takes
No mi entrenador me manda un WhatsApp
off the camera because he's smoking
se quita la cámara porque está fumando
no then we go that
no luego nos pasamos que se me ha
an idea occurred to me let's see if it
ocurrio una illa a ver si
comes out believe that you are a shitty man Damn
sale creer que eres un de hombre miesa
you think you are you clown
[__] Te crees que eres tu payaso
tattoo artist what a pair is that you are a clown
tatuador que par es que eres un payaso
tattoo artist but he says it as an insult tattoo artist tattoo artist
tatuador pero lo dice como un insulto
because I am tattooed
tatuador tatuador porque estoy tatuado
tattoo artist for her they must have a lot of that
tatuador para ella deben tener muy eso
bad tattoo artists or something tattoo tattoo artist
malo los tatuadores o algo tatu tatuador
tattoo artist
tatuador
dude it could be I couldn't do it is that you are
tío podría ser no podría hac es que eres
maybe the complaint of Pablo that
a lo mejor la denuncia del Pablo que
buddy of mine I didn't understand this what
coleguita mío esto no lo entendí lo que
gave me here I didn't understand that Pablo was a buddy
me dio aquí ya no entendí que Pablo era
rooster countryman is not countryman countryman
coleguita gallo paisano no es paisano
It's true  he confused the word
paisano Es verdad confundió la palabra
countryman with that wait that wait with
paisano con esa espera esa espera con
Gallego no I don't agree I
Gallego no no estoy de acuerdo estoy de
agree Gallego Gallego is
acuerd Gallego Gallego es
Gallego I agree it's that he's a lawyer that I'll
Gallego de acuerdo es que es abogado que
still find out calm let's see what his
todavía me enteraré tranquilo a veré
face is I'll find out because the lady already
cara tiene me enteraré pues la señora ya
why would you have found out with
para que se hubiese enterado usted con
all the time we've known that
todo el tiempo que llevamos sabiendo que
Pablo says he's a lawyer already why would you have found out of
Pablo dice que es abogado ya para que
course here we have to call now
enterado claro aquí hay que llamar ya
with the information already I'll find out yes
con la información ya ya me enteraré si
to lawyer come on I'll just tell you one
pa abogado venga yo solo te digo una
thing let's see Just one the word cancer in
cosa a ver Solo una la palabra cáncer en
your mouth is disgusting that lady the one who
vuestra boca es asqueroso la señora esa
ends up talking to you that she's uglier
la que acaba haar contigo que es más fea
al lasne ugly eh alas ugly I'm sure
al lasne fea eh alas fea seguro que
Conchi must be let's go a beauty There
conchi debe ser vamos una preciosura
are no ugly
Aquí no hay feaes salseo
ones here no one is ugly here she puts cream on me that's why
nadie aquí no hay fea me echa crema por
I'm rowing it's not to show off her
eso estoy remando no es para enseñar los
arms laa
brazos laa
it's the parco video it's
es el víde de parco es
disgusting the beltrana
asqueroso la beltrana
laana likes it because she messed with her
laana gusta porque se ha metido con su
boy the ass and no G
niño el tras y no G
Say something Say something say something damn I
Di algo Di algo que dile algo [__] yo
know that she's telling everyone
que sé que le está diciendo a todro el
Tell her something too no  No, I can't
mundo Dile a esa también algo no no no
stand a lost pesetera, a
soporto pesetera perdida pesetera
lost pesetera, a lost pesetera. No,
perdida pesetera perdida No la sopa la
Peppa's soup, calling Peppa and the
Peppa llamarle pesetera a la Peppa y a
Trojans a pesetera, no,
las de Troya no que ha intentado
Elena has also tried to do it live, the other
tambén hace directo Elena la otra
stupid one whose name I don't know is
estúpida que no sé cómo se llama es la
Elena, not all lost pesetera, eh, the
Elena no todos peseteros perdidos eh el
troll is not a lost pesetera, the troll
trolla no es pesetero perdido el trolla
is here for the love of art, for the
está aquí por amor al arte
love of the audiovisual medium,
por amor a la hecho el medio audiovisual
man, when for love, he has
hombre cuando por amor A eso le ha hecho
sucked up to Loli, for the love of that, he has
la pelota a la Loli por amor a eso ha
betrayed Peppa, for the love of art, he has
traicionado a la Peppa por amor al arte
done everything he has done, he
ha hecho todo lo que ha hecho le ha
told Gusi Gusi that Loli has
dicho a gusi gusi que la Loli no tiene
nothing, she's making it up and when I
nada que se lo está inventando y cuando
told him, eh, they make it yellow for me too,
le decía eh A mí también me lo ponen
the troll doesn't do it live, the
amarillo el trollo no hace directo el
flight of [ __ ], it's the flight of [ __ ], the
vuelo de [__] es el vuelo de [__] el
flight of [ __ ], that thing. I was
vuelo de [__] ese cosa Yo hace o meses
diagnosed with lymphoma months ago and you do
que me detectaron un linfoma y vosotros
n't know what happens, mm months, no,
no sabéis lo que se pasa mm meses no
ma'am, you or tell it to Loli, she's the one
Señora usted o dígaselo a la Loli que es
who's making up
que la que se está inventando
diseases, it's that we don't know
enfermedades es que no saos sabemos
perfectly well what it is.  Tell
perfectamente lo que es dígaselo a la
Loli who is making it up and
Loli que se está que se lo está
those who cover for her today
inventando ya los que la tapan hoy
Carmen was already there, those who cover for her in
Carmen estaba ya los que la tapan en una
such a serious and serious thing knowing that it
cosa tan grave y tan seria sabiendo que
is a lie, that's who you have to
es mentira es a quién se lo tiene usted
tell it to, not Javi or Lasne or
que decir no a Javi ni a lasne ni a
Elena or anyone you tell it eh to
Elena ni a nadie dígaselo usted eh a
these to the one who made it up and to
estos a la que se lo ha inventado y a
those who cover for her knowing that she
los que la tapan sabiendo que se lo ha
made it up and deceives her community to
inventado y engaña a su comunidad a
you For example that she is going through
usted Por ejemplo que está pasando por
something so so serious, of course as
una cosa tan tan grave claro como dices
you say when not There are six and for example six
tú cuando no Son seis y por ejemplo seis
sessions of chemo eh thank God I
sesiones de quimio eh gracias a Dios me
am
estoy
recovering I am glad no Of course but
recuperando me alegro no Claro pero
leave that word already says Javi I am glad
dejar esa palabra ya dice Javi me alegro
And it even makes her angry that Javi tells her
Y es que le da hasta rabia que le diga
that he is glad that she is
Javi que se alegra de que se esté
recovering he stands there
recuperando se pone ahí
like of course the [ __ ] he is telling her I am
como claro [__] le está diciendo Me
glad that she is and he gets angry too that is why he
alegro que se est y se enfada también
[ __ ] with everything I want it is not
por eso se se fag con todo quier no es
a game it is not the flu you know what happens
un juego no es una grip sabes qué pasa
sir it is not a fungus no madam no
señor no es un hongo no señora no
miss you do not care you know what happens
señorita no te importa sabes qué pasa
miss Miss miss if you do not  It
señorita Señorita señorita si no te
matters, come on, I used the wrong
importa venga que me he equivocado de
word, miss. Sorry, how could I
palabra señorita Perdón Cómo que te
mistake you? I meant to say biosa. Ah
equivoco que yo quería decir biosa ah
biosa, yes, yes, sorry, I used the wrong
biosa sí sí perdona eh equivocado
word. Look, they also told it to me.
palabra Mira también me la dicieron a mí
You know, they also told it to me because
sabes también me la dijeron a mí porque
I never counted, deita. I expected
yo no contaba jamás deita yo esperaba
that I was going to have cancer. You heard of
que yo iba a tener un cáncer oíste de
some [ __ ] about a pimple, right? And they
una [__] de un grano bien y me
did a visa here next to the
hicieron una viosa aquí al lado de la
orja and it turned out to be a report. You know, they already
orja y me resultó un infoma sabes Ya me
did two pet jobs yesterday. V about doing one
hicieron dos pets de ayer V de hacer uno
of viic and everything is [ __ ] great.
de viic y está todo de [__] madre
Much is I
much es
hope it makes her mad that Javi
espero es que le da rabia que Javi le
tells her that he's glad that she's okay. It seems
diga que se alegra de que esté
like, But because the
como Pero porque el
last one. Well, because that would be the
último Bueno pues porque ya sería lo
last thing, I mean, I'm calling you, I'm
último o sea Te estoy llamando te estoy
insulting you. I'm calling you everything,
insultando Te estoy llamando de todo a
the ugly line, the other one, I don't know what, your
la lne fea a la otra no sé qué que tu
filthy mouth, what a brat what she says, man, it would be
sucia boca que niñato que dice hombre es
the last straw, you guys
que ya sería el colmo que vosotros
play with that word like it's a
jugáis con esa palabra como si fuera un
headache, kid, but you
dolor de cabeza chaval pero vosotros
know what happens, you know what
sabéis lo que se pasa sabéis lo que se
happens with this disease, [ __ ]. But
pasa con esta enfermedad [__] Pero eso
tell that to Loli, of course, and to her idol,
cuéntese usted a Loli claro y a su ídolo
her idol.  who lies to people and goes
a su ídolo que miente a la gente y va
behind their backs telling others is that he
por detrás contándolo a otros es que no
has nothing Don't think he doesn't have
tiene nada No te creas que no tiene
cancer or anything that he
cáncer ni tiene nada que se la ha
made it up he's fine man like the
inventado ya está bien hombre como la
other one that up the ass I don't know who says
otra que le por el culo no sé quién dice
what nonsense you talk about not
que qué tonterías habláis no youtub
normal youtubers like charism like the one I
normales como es carism como es el que
told you like charisman has put karis
dije como es carisman ha metido karis
among the
entre los youtubers
normal youtubers k
normales k
and how is he a a per Aaron who is
y cómo es el a a per Aarón quién es
the brother of The brother of est The one from
el hermano de El hermano de est El de
the buet chip Boys this Aaron this who is
los buet chip Boys este Aarón este quién
Aaron Aaron Carter Oh Aaron auron Play
Aarón Aaron Carter Ay Aaron auron Play
no Aaron clear like
no Aaron claro como
Aaron people all of them are youtubers No
Aaron gente toda ellos son youtubers No
neither you nor the other nor the other eh For me
ni tú ni el otro ni el otro eh Para mí
he's a great guy defend him indefensible he's
es un tío genial defiéndelo indefendible
more he defends both her and
es más las defiende tanto a ella como a
vrana and they still give him an ass on top of the
la vrana y aún le dan por culo encima al
poor guy
pobre
on top of the poor guy Well you know poor
encima el pobre Bueno pues ti se pobre
he loves a lot of people Eh and he's doing
le encanta muchísima gente Eh y le va de
great Look it's better to have 300
[__] madre Mira es mejor tener 300
people worth in one of his live shows than
personas vale en un directo de él que
3000 of yours because you because  what I
3000 la tuya por porque tú por qué yo
prefer 3 right But let's see I prefer let's
prefo 3 verdad Pero a ver yo prefiero a
see Wait wait I prefer Why did you
ver Espera espera yo prefiero Por qué me
tell me that it's better to have 300 than to
has dicho que es mejor tener 300 que
have 3000 I prefer 3000 of course let's
tener 3000 yo prefiero 3000 claro vamos
see that it's better 300 than 3000 but just
a ver que mejor 300 que 3000 pero por la
because Oh
cara porque
really really it's
sí Ay de verdad de verdad
like if I gave no no I
es que es como si me di no no yo
prefer to charge 500 to
prefiero cobrar 500 a
10000 that's why or rather it's that I didn't
10000 per eso por qué o sea es que no lo
understand the truth look I respect
entendí la verdad mira que yo respeto su
your arguments we have it we have it we have it we have the
sus argumentaciones lo tenemos lo
loser wait I'm going to write you
pringado espera le voy a escribir una
something I'm going to write you something that has
cosa le voy a escribir una cosa que se
made echoes I've made
ha hecho ecoes
people bigger that I have a
agrando a la gente que yo tengo un
dark criminal past or something like that no
pasado oscuro criminal o algo así no
how long then that's why I would tell you
cuánto tiempo entonces por eso te diría
Marta I would like
Marta me gustaría que
one
un
minute a question miss let's see
minuto una pregunta señorita vamos a ver
you told me that it's better I'm
me ha dicho usted que es mejor estoy
asking a question miss 3000 me
haciendo una pregunta señorita 3000 yo
to put 300 I pee the
para ponerme 300 meo la
basket silly kid silly you are silly
cesta tonto chaval tonto tú eres tonto
kid please
chaval por favor
conchi but uh well it's that I'm not
conchi pero est pues es que no lo estoy
denying is offending and I don't
negando es que ofendiendo y yo no lo
deny it Hey listen because if you like to
niego Oye escucha porque si te gusta
live the way you live you live a [ __ ] homeless person
vivir como vives viv un [__] indigente
but you have to the homeless people Yes son I
pero tiene cont los indigentes Sí hijo
know yes yes what What did you do to my hair did you go
sé sí sí qué Qué me hiciste en el pelo
put
te fuiste tú a poner
hair on your hair too what did you do to my
pelo el pelo también qué te me hiciste
hair she says she doesn't like it at all nothing she doesn't
en el pelo dice no le gusta nada nada no
like it at all Noa a toupee you idiot no no I didn't
le gusta nada Noa un peluquín imbécil no
put it on but man It's that the lady
no me lo puse pero tío Es que la señora
is a big lady Excuse me Miss miss she's
es una mbra señorita Perdón Señorita
rude and see this she
señorita es una maleducada y ve yo esto
already calls me such and such And I'm already in trouble Caro I'm already in trouble I'm already
ya me llama tal Y ya la lío Caro ya la
getting started I'm changing my
lío ya me pongo me se me cambia el
toupee my toupee is changing too and I'm
peluquín a mí también se me cambia el
in trouble brown you know what to
peluquín y lío parda tú sabes lo que
tell me what she wanted to tell me was that
decirme lo que quiso decirme fue que
then if we doubt Loli about
entonces si nosotros dudamos de Loli de
her operation she could also
su operación que también ella podría
doubt if I got hair or lied to
dudar de si yo me puse pelo o mentí a la
people and I put on a toupee as if I
gente y me puse un peluquín como si
had the same seriousness in case I
tuviera eso la misma seriedad en el caso
have deceived you imagine I have
de que os haya engañado imagínate me he
put on a  toupee instead instead of hair
puesto un peluquín en vez en vez de pelo
okay Well you're an idiot son if
vale Bueno pues eres gilipolla hijo si
you lied about that what do you want me to
has mentido en eso qué quieres que te
tell you But it's not the same as playing with
diga Pero no es lo mismo que jugar con
a dog to blame the others you
un can para culpar a los otros me
understand I mean it has nothing to do with it I
entiendes O sea no tiene nada que ver me
put it on damn my head turned purple
lo puse [__] se me puso la cabeza morada
put
puso
Of course apart I come out here with filters and
Claro aparte yo salé aquí con filtros y
all the roll Why didn't you take the
todo el rollo Por qué no sacaste al
borro and show it if I showed it Ah you
borro y lo enseñaste si lo enseñé Ah lo
showed it that we have it we have it
enseñaste qu lo tenemos lo
period and that's what there is
tenemos punto y es lo que
And yes I defend it Because I believe in it I
hay Y si lo defiendo Porque creo en eso
'm not here for Lolly
Yo no estoy aquí para para que Lolly
werta to fill my pocket with money
werta me llene el bolsillo de dinero
Like they've filled it for others who
Como se lo han llenado a otros que ahora
are now very broke because one because they've
están muy reventados porque uno porque
filled their pocket with
le han llenado el dinero el bolsillo de
money and they don't have it anymore and others because they've
dinero y ya no lo tienen y otros porque
never seen it like you but it
no lo han visto nunca có tú pero le
went wrong no no conchi it went wrong I don't
salió mal no no conchi le salió mal no
hear all the calls but she
le escucho todas la llamada pero le que
put it on her like her friend says that she
se la envain como dice su amiga que se
put it on her yesterday many things went wrong for her it
envain ayer le salieron muchas cosas mal
wasn't just that one but yesterday we also
no fue esa sola pero ayer también
apparently have the lady with her
tenemos por lo visto a la señora bien
hair done  the one from Seville the one who is going to
peinada la de Sevilla la que me va a
sue me for right the honor the
demandar por derecha el honor la
privacy and all that story eh
intimidad y toda esa historia eh
talking about me
hablando de mí
insulting me then now we will see a
insultándome entonces ahora veremos un
clip where it
clip donde
says according to them you confirmed that Loli did
dice según ellos tú confirmaste que Loli
not have cancer car 90 I have said
no tenía cáncer car 90 yo he dicho
publicly Lolly werta does not have
públicamente Lolly werta no tiene
cancer I have
cáncer lo he
said it I put on my channel the audio that I
dicho yo puse en mi canal el audio que
sent to
le mandé a
gusi you understand that thanks zama What what
gusi vosotros entendéis que gracias zama
You have already passed zama 50 Thank you very much
qué Ya te has pasado zama 50 Muchísimas
but daughter I could not do the
gracias pero hija no podía hacer la de
five by five that people stay
cinco en cinco que la gente se queda
here I am banned it does not happen
aquí estoy baneado no pasa Muchísimas
Thank you very much he has not ignored me because nobody
gracias no me ha ignorado porque nadie
has spoken well Ana chamizo Carmen sq
ha hablado bueno Ana chamizo Carmen sq
is not the one from the flight Ah
no es la del vuelo Ah
esan says I can't hear it it is
esan dice yo no puedo escucharlo es
superior to m to m I pass you ig te Rosaura
superior a m a m me pas ig te Rosaura
Manuel
Manuel
in Car Nieto Santa Pina otara
en Car Nieto Santa Pina otara
dalira Alicia Look zama is not due
dalira Alicia Mira a zama no le toca
you are only missing 15 for the 500 I think it will
solo te faltan 15 para los 500 yo creo
be if it is not there they will be almost
que ya estará si no está estarán casi
zama
zama Muchísimas
Thank you very much of course hidden with chiay Manuela
gracias claro oculto con chiay Manuela
jart soledad
jart soledad
Garca noito there it has gone too far Ah  take 50
García noito ahí se ha pasado Ah toma 50
in one fell swoop with two balls lollipop is
de un golpe con dos [__] piruleta es
the key
la clave
Maria J is going to gain two subscribers
María J va ganar dos suscriptores este
today m Mr. Patricia but a kiss my girl
hoy m Sr Patricia pero un beso mi niña
we have to wait a minute but in the
tenemos que esperar un minuto pero de
meantime we wait eh you
mientras que esperamos eh habéis dado
all gave A Like How many likes are there let's
todo el mundo A Like Cuántos likes hay a
see here are there likes so I can do this what am I
ver aquí hay like para que yo haga esto
going to do or
que voy a hacer o
not Here are likes or what Well if there are no
no Aquí hay likes o qué Pues si no hay
likes I'll pass
like paso
Eh how many likes are there what How many
Eh cuántos likes hay cuá Cuántos
but of course this one will have banned
pero claro este habrá baneado hasta la
even the lollipop you'll
hasta la piruleta ya
see 804 likes I'm going to sleep eh
veréis 804 likes yo me voy a dormir eh
I'm not staying here like this eh I'm going with
yo así no me quedo aquí eh Me voy con
the kids Hey you know the
los chavales Oye tú sabes que los
kids have reached almost 6000
chavales han llegado casi a 6000
members already
miembros ya
family that doesn't empathize people who say they've been through it
familia que no empatice gente que dice
and the other who has a
que lo ha pasado y la otra que tiene un
very close relative going through it okay Yeah Well they
familiar muy cercano pasándolo vale Ya
're the same people who
Bueno pues son las mismas personas que
say that everything the whole
dicen que todo la toda la enfermedad de
cancer disease They go through it the same all the
cáncer Lo pasan igual todos los
treatments are the same and all the
tratamientos son iguales y todos los
results are the same that's the
resultados son iguales eso esa es la
people that's the people but well now
gente esa es la gente pero bueno ahora
that you're listening to me Mr. Oliveira I
que me está escuchando Señor oliveira yo
never  I leaked my audio hotel watch mate the
jamás filtré mi audio htel mirar mate el
live don't stay with the cli watch
directo no te quedes con el cli mírate
the live okay let's see at what moment
el directo vale a ver en qué momento
I leaked my
filtré yo mi
audio By the way, that complaint is in
audio Por cierto esa denuncia está en el
court Ah okay No, you didn't say that
juzgado Ah vale No no decías que no me
the civil guard is not going to listen to me because it
va a hacer caso la guardia civil pues
is in the court of Ah okay waiting for
está en el juzgado del Ah vale esperando
me to give my phone number and
a que yo de teléfono y
name so they are waiting for him watch it watch it maybe
nombre así que le están esperando
the subject will refresh itself the same as I went through with the subject of
el tema lo mismo que pasé por el tema de
gusy and Loli do not hurt them with this
gusy y Loli no hacerles daño con este
subject of the let it go it may be that it does
tema de la dejarlo pasar puede ser que
not come out no like that
no sale no
well but nothing has come out of my mouth
así que bueno pero que de mi boca no ha
and a leaked audio comes
salido nada y a mí un audio filtrado me
out and it is private Let's see, I don't have to
sale y que es privado A ver no tengo que
give explanations is that clear to you because I
dar explicaciones te queda claro pues
hope
espero que
so if I said that to Gus it would be for something and
sí si yo dije eso a Gus sería por algo y
if I stopped thinking about it that way it
si dejé de pensar en eso de esa manera
would be for something else not for the money that it
sería por otro algo no por el dinero que
brings me or any of these thieving people
traiga ni ninguna de esta gente ladrona
from the book very good
de libro muy buenas
night to say he is banned the lollipop is
noches decir tiene baneado la piruleta
also still there Of course because you can
también sigue Claro porque podéis
put him in the chat that he comes we
ponerle en el chat que que venga que
make a call and  today he
hagamos una llamada y hoy te
tells you that J is writing to me that we should make
dice que me está escribiendo J que que
a call he is writing to me
hagamos una llamada me está escribiendo
where he is writing to me where to the
dónde me está escribiendo a dónde al
big book of ptt write Okay let's
libro gordo de ptt escriba Bueno vamos a
listen yes he has given him an
escuchando sí que le ha dado una una
ethnicity of de iato right now that you show
etnia de de iato ahora mismo que enseñes
debate knowing that I do not debate nobody That is what
debate saber que yo no debato nadie Eso
he would like 15
es lo que él quisiera se necesitan 15
volunteers are needed There is what
voluntarias Ahí está lo que me está
the police is investigating me okay so
investigando la policía a mí vale o sea
show it publicly I give you
que lo enseñes públicamente te doy
permission to make a
permiso ha una
call a paper that says caris in
llamada un papel que pone caris en el
2015 Look tell Javi if he is not
2015 Mira decirle a Javi si no me está
watching me that I do not enter anyone's channels
viendo que yo no entro a los canales de
to debate I do not allow anyone to
nadie a debatir No permito que nadie
enter my channel or to debate or
entre en mi canal ni a debatir ni
phone call or anything at all he
llamada de teléfono ni nada de nada
said to me he is not going to confuse me like a
decía a m no me va a liar como una
pumpkin with your prepared clip that I already know you
calabaza con tu clip preparado que ya te
kid and second I program the live shows
chaval y segundo yo los directos me los
then I follow the pause of my the Schedule
programo entonces sigo la pausa de mi la
of my live show the one that I
Pauta de mi directo la que yo me
program inside my head And then I
programa dentro de mi cabeza Y luego ya
improvise if it seems good to me You
voy improvisando si me parece bien
need content let's see if
Necesitas contenido a ver si viene ya
Marina ennal comes now or Marta calls  I risk
Marina ennal o llama Marta riesco que te
telling you town
cuente pueblo
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
cagado
the phone
cagado el teléfono
What is the phone what is the phone does he
Cuál es el teléfono cuál es el teléfono
have a phone on I give you permission
tiene un teléfono puesto te doy permiso
to show it I mean don't say
para que lo enseñes O sea no digas
show because the other person has to
enseñar porque la otra persona tiene que
give permission total coward eh you show it
dar permiso cagona total eh lo enseñas
publicly wait wait yomi says
públicamente espérate espera yomi dice
but the problem is not that you leaked it it's what you
pero el problema no es que lo filtras es
said in her that
que lo es lo que dijiste en ella que
you knew that she was lying and you played along
ustedes saban que ella mentía y le
So you're
siguieron el juego Entonces estás
saying that you didn't leak has a
diciendo que tú no filtr tiene un
phone what is the leaked phone
teléfono cuál es el teléfono filtrado
no messages
ningún mensaje
irobi says PayPal but doesn't put a
irobi pone PayPal pero no pone un
phone Ah there is a phone audio aus because there is
teléfon Ah hay un telé audio aus porque
a phone a phone
ha un téfono un teléfono
wait gy sent it to Loli Loli
espera gy se lo envió a Loli Loli lo
put it in her live and when they
puso en su directo y yo cuando me lo
told me I went into her live I didn't
dijeron Entré en su directo no me di
realize to remove the
cuenta de de quitar la captura de
screenshot and a bit of the audio was heard
pantalla y se escuchó un poco del audio
but I didn't leak
pero yo no filtré
anything cageta if yours 90 to me I don't care
nada cageta si la suya 90 a m me da
my mother But how much are you going to get
igual madre mía Pero cuánto Vais a
in from
entrar de
there are you really bored
allí estáis aburrido de verdad en
seriously that's so bad Why And I'm not saying it
serio eso tan malo Por qué Y no lo digo
because  you I say this because the other channel the
por ti Lo digo porque el otro canal el
flight echoes fake news
vuelo se hacen eco de noticias falsas
Okay and they blow it up do you understand So
Vale y lo agrandan me entiendes Entonces
I'm not going to allow it to be said on the
yo no voy a permitir que se diga en
internet that the police are hanging around me
internet que a mí me está pendo la
and that a man who doesn't understand me
policía y que un señor que mej no se
has my number he hasn't lost it he has it he has
tiene mi número no la ha perdido lo
my number but I'm not going to
tiene tiene mi número pero no lo voy a
pick it What's his name that he has my
[__] Cómo se llama que que que tiene mi
number I haven't lost it as if
número no lo he perdido como si lo
I had ever had it in my life
hubiera tenido alguna vez yo en la vida
e Okay here We have reached something
e Bueno aquí Hemos llegado a una cosa
that I had forgotten 61 the man from
que se me había olvidado 61 el señor de
the flight 61 years old Peppa Beltrn well
del vuelo 61 añitos Peppa Beltrán bueno
Peppa Beltrn corrected herself then she said 62 I
Peppa Beltrán corrigió luego dijo 62
think in this same live in the
creo que en este mismo directo en el
chat that she is 62 that is to say pppa beltral
chat que tiene 62 es decir pppa beltral
has been there 3 years and the man says that eh he should be
lleva 3 años y el señor dice que eh está
put in a nursing home but not now
para meter en un asilo pero ya no ahora
eh it's been 8 years since he was not worth it
eh hace 8 años que él no le iba
Well that's a Trojan horse family there you
la Pues ese es ard de Troya familia ahí
have it Javi don't give him meat but yes
lo tenéis Javi no des carnaza pero si
But Manui what meat am I going to give him if he
Pero manui qué carnaza le voy a dar si
doesn't want to accept a call from me the
no me quiere aceptar una llamada el
loser has  [ __ ] myself but I know his
pringado se ha cagado pero se se le ha
face has broken down but if I don't I don't
descompuesto la cara pero si yo no no
want to have a debate I want to make a
quiero hacer un debate quiero hacer una
call a little
llamad una
chat for me to hear it come on How
charlita yo para que lo voorde vamos Qué
scary j
miedo j
eh people man I mean you have a
eh la gente tío O sea tienes tienes el
channel dedicated every day to one
canal dedicado todos los días a una
person and now that person calls you and you
persona y ahora esa persona te llama y
don't pick up you don't want to talk to that
no lo coges no quieres hablar con esa
person to whom you have so many things to
persona a la que tantas cosas tienes que
say every
decirle cada
day what a pain Well then maybe no no you don't
día vaya tela Pues entonces a lo mejor
have so many things to
no no no tienes tantas cosas que
tell me no how do you think it has
decirme no cómo lo pensáis ustedes
n't it been quite [ __ ] itself It
no se ha cagado bastante
wasn't a bald spot or something no no no no no no I
No era una calva o algo no no no no no
took it no no no no just as I came out
no yo cogí no no no no tal y como salí
of the operating room to get my hair done and I put
del quirófano de ponerme pelo y me puse
a canary on my head I started to dance
un canario en la cabeza me puse a bailar
Oh look at you
Ay mirate
well the canary dance not like the
bieno el baile de canario no como la
other one but with the r of pain Javi you were
otra pero con el r de dolor Javi te
missing with you didn't put r of pain we didn't
faltó con no pusiste r de dolor no te
believe you because you were missing the r of pain
creímos porque te faltó el r de dolor
boy What a shame I didn't see you it's that you're
chico Qué pena que no te vi es que eres
ridiculous kid you're ridiculous but come on
ridículo chaval eres ridículo pero vamos
I was mapping the channel come on those who have
yo de mapaba el canal vamos los que tien
wit all  everything everything everything let's go I would
salera todos todo todo todo vamos le
close him up to his house I would put a
cerraba hasta su casa le ponía fuera una
fence outside and lock him up to his house with Javi
valla y encerraba hasta su casa con Javi
inside
dentro
and stupidity the kids the rock and
y estupid ería la chavalería la
roller and the stupid please
rocanrolera y la estupida por favor
[Music]
[Música]
whatever I tell you whatever I tell you
un lo que yo te diga lo que yo te diga
a
un
little [ __ ] trano
poco mirdo trano
You're everything no everything no I haven't I haven't said
Eres todo no todo no he he dicho
bald on my knees bald on my knees no
calvo de rodill calo de rodilla no
head
cabeza
knee head knee if I can no
rodilla cabeza rodilla si puedo no
that's mine I don't know how many insults today there's
que mío yo que sé cuántos insultos hoy
head knee of course I said Oh Oh Oh Ay
est t cabeza rodilla claro he dicho Ay
head on my knees This
Ay Ay Ay cabeza de rodilla Es que esto
reminds me of a thread from Oh how funny How
me recuerda un hilo de Ay qué risa Qué
funny Well I don't know if you know that
risa Bueno no sé si sabéis esa
story about there was a forum for people like
historia la de había un foro de gente de
this with alopecia about people who were going to have
esta con alopecia de gente que se iba a
surgery I don't know if you know that story and there was
operar no sé si sabéis esa historia y
one who pretended to
hubo uno que se hizo pasar parce que me
clarify for me what I have when I have a
aclare qué tengo cuando tenga un
health problem I'm going to go to those three
problema de salud me voy a esos tres
channels let one have an endoscopy the
canales que me haga uno la endoscopia el
other the x-ray and the other the
otro la radiografía y el otro la
open heart surgery You're welcome
operación a corazón abierto De nada
Maite now I continue continue continue continue it's that
Maite ahora sigo sigo sigo sigo es que
taking advantage of the
aprovechando el
announcement yes fear I am look it smells  poop smells like
anuncio sí miedo estoy mira huele a
poop but it's not
caquita huele a caquita pero no es la
mine poop smells It's
mía huele la
that I go I go with my
caquita Es que yo yo voy yo voy con mi
truth Sofia
verdad Sofía
13 I go with my truth mine the one that I
13 yo voy con mi verdad la mía la que yo
believe according to what I see Hello love let's go
creo según yo veo Hola ama que vaya a
debate with Ricky stop the
dar a debatir con Ricky se deje de
nonsense there it is there it
tontería ahí está ahí
is Thanks Marisa Kraken for those 2 of I
está Gracias Marisa Kraken por esos 2 de
don't know what coin says Javi to
no sé qué moneda dice Javi que lo
call him call him right now
llame que lo llame s ahora
called him right now to
mismo lo llamado ahora mismo al
now I can't do anything Now I know another my
a ahora no puedo nada Ahora se me otro
mother who gave birth to me
la madre que me pari
from debating with the
de debatir con el
professor Yes of
catedrático Sí
course but you know what happens Mara
claro pero sabes lo que pasa María
Cantabrico is that I don't
cantabrico que es que no me
feel like it I don't feel like when the
apetece no apetece como cuando viene la
other one comes debate debate debate debate
otra debate debate debate debate tú
yourself what's the point I can
misma total de qué sirve Yo me puedo
waste all the saliva I have talking to
gastar la saliva que tengo hablando con
you and you're going to believe whatever you want
vosotros y v a creer lo que os dé la
then No man don't be like that choni top
entonces No hombre no sea así choni top
for him he doesn't leave anything for the others
para él no deja algo para los demás
too to be 61 years old my father
también para tener 61 años mi padre
is 60 he's [ __ ] great a hair of
tiene 60 está de [__] madre un pelo de
mine he's 80 80 and
el mío tiene 80 80 y
how much my father would have been 82 I think  82 and he's
cuánto mi padre tendría ya 82 creo 82 y
better than the one from the
está mejor que el del
flight Although I appear to be 80
vueno Aunque yo aparente eh tener 80
years old according to some who have a very
años según alguno que tiene el tupe muy
good toupee but my father is 82 bald he
bien puesto pero mi padre tiene 82 calvo
is also bald eh bald
también es calvo eh calvo
and a more rebellious man than ever very
y hombre más Rebelde que nunca muy
good night and he's better than the one from the
buenas noches y y está mejor que el del
flight the gito so handsome and all
vuelo el gito así guapete y tal le
a lot of girls write to him on Instagram but
escribe muchas tías por Instagram pero
my father says no that he doesn't want anything
mi padre dice que no que no quiere nada
well you have Instagram that's the first thing that's
bueno tu tiene instagr eso lo primero
the
eso lo
second now I'll call you Javi talking
segundo ahora te llamo Javi hablando
bebig gala I won't move a comma from my
bebig gala yo no muevo una coma de mi
truth I can believe in people Stop
verdad yo puedo creer en la gente Dejar
believing in them for whatever reason
de creer en ellos por lo que
and then realize that I could have been
sea y luego darme cuenta que me he
wrong that everything is not as they
podido equivocado que todo no es como lo
want to paint it or that the person who
quieren pintar o que la persona que me
made me change my mind with that message is
ha hecho cambiar de con ese mensaje de
not right for some
opinión no lleva la razón por algún
reason but what these people want is for
motivo pero lo que quiere esta gente es
me to explain why I said that
que yo explique por qué le dije yo eso
in the audio to gusi and not what those
en el audio a gusi y no lo y lo que esa
people want is for Lolly werta to get her
gente quiere es que Lolly werta saque su
medical report because no no no she
informe en médico por que no que no no
can't maintain she can't maintain it she's
no puede mantener no puede mantenerlo no
not going to go up  because he can't
va no va a subir porque no puede
keep the lie up in front of his
mantener la mentira delante de sus
followers he can't keep up the lie
seguidores no puede mantener La Mentira
when when we see this call we
cuando cuando vemos Esta llamada lo
understand
entendemos
perfectly the lady who came yesterday
perfectamente la señora que vino ayer
who came up eh with that mouth insulting the
que subió eh con esa boca insultando las
things she said and such it can't be any other
cosas que decía y tal no puede ser otro
way that that that type of person like
modo ese esa ese tipo de persona como
this lady that you're listening to are
esta señora que la estáis escuchando son
the followers of these people clo it can't
los seguidores de esa gente clo no puede
be any other way They're not going to be the ones from
ser de otra forma No van a ser los de
here obviously there are
aquí evidentemente
all kinds of people all over the
hay gente de todo tipo en todo el
planet and this person these people well they have to
planeta y esta persona esta gente pues
have these followers there's
tienen que tener estos seguidores es que
no more there's no more now he
no hay más es que no hay más ahora le
tells them they have a channel dedicated to you he
dice tienen un canal Dedicado a ti les
tells them come let's make a call I'm not
dice ven vamos a hacer una llamada no me
going to eat it Let's talk do you
lo voy a comer Vamos a hablar me
understand and he
entiendes y
does Why Well because the people he
hace Por qué Pues porque a la gente que
has here are deceived and they don't see
tiene aquí la tiene engañada y no ven
the clicks they don't see
los click no ven
anything they don't see
nada no ven
anything because of a bald guy putting a picture of
nada por un calvo poniendo una foto de
his knee I don't know if it sounds familiar to you I'll read you
su rodilla Es que no sé si os os suena
a little The story sounds familiar or
os Leo un poco Suena la historia esta o
not it's that story is a laugh I mean
no suena es que esa historia es una risa
that story is a laugh it was
o sea esa historia es una risa era Era
a forum for people with alopecia
un foro de esto de gente con alopecia
bald people Well bald people that  they go to
calvos Pues calvos que se van a operar a
Turkey for surgery because they get implants and
Turquía pueno que se hacen implantes y
all this and there was one, well, one who
todo esto y hubo uno pues un uno que les
trolled them And he posted a picture of his
pegó una troleada Y puso una foto de su
knee pretending it was his
rodilla haciéndose pasar como que era su
head that he was bald Look, I know, I
cabeza que era calvo Mira yo es que sé
read it later I think they
es que lo lo leí luego creo que en
posted a thread about it on Forocoche
forocoche lo pusieron un hilo sobre eso
I cried laughing at that topic eh
he llorado yo de la risa con ese tema eh
Because the troll he gave them on
Porque la troleada que les pegó al Foro
this Forum of the bald people It's okay Well, they
este de los de calvos No pasa nada Pues
were bald the troll he gave them doesn't
eran calvos la troleada que les pegó no
sound good one day I'll put it for you I'll put that one for you
suena un día os pongo la os pongo el ese
and I'll put the photo of the knee He posted
y os pongo la foto de la rodilla puso
a photo of his knee of his knee
una foto de la rodilla de su rodilla
then let's see if later after this I
luego a ver si luego después de esto lo
look for it in a bald forum and he put it put it or
busco en un foro de calvo y coló coló o
rather they thought it was his head
sea se pensaban que era su cabeza
So they told him Well, I see
Entonces le decían Bueno pues yo ahí veo
a problem there, it's not going to be enough for you with what happened in
un problema no te va a bastar con lo de
Turkey, with I don't know what you've
Turquía con no sé qué no lo habéis visto
never seen it before, well, I have to put it for you a
nunca pues os lo tengo que poner una
troll from someone who
troleada de alguien que le pegó una
trolled a  alopecia and
troleada a un foro de de alopecia y de
baldness forum and they took it And he posted a picture of his
calvos y cogieron Y puso una foto de su
knee and they swallowed it, let's say they
rodilla y se lo tragaron vamos se lo
swallowed it completely until I don't know
tragaron completito hasta que ya no sé
how much if on page 15 or 20
cuánto si en la página 15 o 20 ya la
people started to doubt but the photo
gente empezó a dudar pero es que la foto
seems fake it seems like I don't know what two
parece falsa es que parece no sé qué dos
or three photos he posted of his knee and he said
o tres fotos puso de su rodilla y coló
that it was eh an alopecia problem
de que era eh problema de alopecia
tomorrow I'll put it up for you if not that today I'll
mañana ma os lo pongo si no lo eso hoy
put it up for you tomorrow okay so you can have
mañana os lo pongo vale para que os
a laugh Gisela
echéis unas risas Gisela
beautiful come on let's go let's continue Oh
guapa venga vamos vamos seguimos Ay
head knee I'm pissing myself with that I'm pissing myself
cabeza rodilla me meo con eso me
look today you already got me on the rebound I
meo mira hoy ya me cogiste as de rebote
'm already bored of you man and I've been
ya estoy aburrida de ti tío y llevo 4
listening to YouTube [ __ ] for 4 years and I
años escuchando la [__] de YouTube y
'm only cu years 4 years you've been
solo estoy cu años 4 años hace que me
following me No, no, sorry to you, I've already
sigues No a ti no perdona a a ti ya te
reported some of you eh You've
tengo denunciado alguno eh A mí me has
reported my videos
denunciado los vídeos
[ __ ] that's why I have them all in
[__] por eso los tengo todos en
Yellow guys can you donate to me please
Amarillo chavales me podéis donar porfa
[ __ ] of course That's how I have everything in
[__] claro Así lo tengo todo en
yellow So you can see that when we see
amarillo Para que veáis que cuando vemos
the hate comments a lot  times in
los comentarios de odio muchas veces en
the live Elena honey send yourself an
los directos Elena cariño que mándate un
audio if you want send yourself an Audi quote
audio si quieres mándate un Audi cito
Elena whoever wants okay you can send
Elena quien quiera vale podéis mandar
audio
audio
but so you can see that many times
pero para que veáis que muchas veces
when they are or they call me if you want you
cuando están los o me llam si quieres
want to upload when you see the
quieres subir cuando veis los mensajes
hate messages when you see the hate messages
de Odio cuando veis los mensajes de odio
that they tell you brutal barbarities
de que te dicen barbaridades brutales
you say what the [ __ ] have I done to
que dices tú [__] que le he hecho yo a
this person that for them to write me such
esta persona que para que me escriba
things you know that I no longer say
unas cosas tan sabes que ya no decí
[ __ ] well I don't like your video well you're
[__] pues no me gusta tu vídeo pu eres
stupid I don't know no no no there are people who
tonto no sé no no no hay gente que te
write you things that are with hate and
escribe unas cosas que son con un odio y
something that seems like you've done
una cosa que parece que le has hecho
something to the family you know and it's
algo a la familia sabes y es
like no and what happens is that they use the
como no y lo que pasa es que usan
internet as a place to
internet como un sitio
vent hate channel it
donde desfogar el odio canalizarlo el
hate they live with resentment they live with
odio viven con rencor viven con
frustrations or whatever you know and they don't really know
frustraciones o lo que sea sabes y no
why they are
saben realmente Por qué te están
insulting you they don't
insultando no lo saben
really know I can't
realmente no me lo puedo
believe it wait now I'll put it sir here
creer espera ahora lo pongo señor aquí
Ah now I have all the videos in
Ah ahora tengo todos los vídeos en
yellow I don't charge a single buck of course that's
amarillos no cobro ni un pavo clar esa
another one that donates 50 to you who knows what
es otra que te dona 50 a saber lo que
you're doing there  kid you're going to 50 know
armas tú ahí chavalote te vaar 50 saber
what you're up to there he doesn't want to throw it to
lo que armas tú ahí no quiere echarla a
Elena Antonio is
Elena el Antonio está todos los días
talking about me every day now he doesn't want to talk
hablando de mí ahora no quiere hablar
to me and kid
conmigo y chavalote
says patelo stick you know he talks
dice patelo bastoncillo sabes que habla
very fast he talks very fast let's see who
muy rá habla muy rápido a ver a saber
knows what who knows what said
que a saber qué a saber de qué dicho
you donate a lot Look You're screwed
usted te donan mucho Mira Estás [__]
because he has let's go he has members to
porque tiene vamos tiene miembros para
take ass why Because he's a guy who does
tomar culo por qué Porque es un tío que
n't bother anyone he talks about his
no se mete con nadie habla de su
problem about his movies okay but it's that
problema de sus películas vale pero es
you eh you come up with this argument that
que tú eh te metes con este argumento de
you're burned because I don't know who has a
estás ardido porque no sé quién tiene
member I don't know who has visitors and that is
miembro no sé quién tiene visita y eso
such that it is that it is like Ricky Edi man I mean
tal es que es tipo Ricky Edi tío o sea
how am I going to wish anyone to have
yo cómo voy a desearle a nadie que tenga
less visitors less members how does that
menos visitas menos miembros a mí eso en
affect me man I mean every time they have
qué me afecta tío o sea yo cada vez que
put something like that to me I have said it I
me han puesto algo así lo he dicho yo le
tell everyone to have a
decir a todo el mundo que tenga un
lot to have a lot of
montón de que tenga un montón de de
visitors and to have a lot of members I mean what the [ __ ] that
visita y que tenga un montón de miembros
doesn't take away from me you
O sea que [__] eso a mí no me quita lo
understand
entiendes
Ruben I just saw it Ruben here on the
Rubén lo acabo de ver Rubén aquí en la
other
otra
screen I just  see here on the other
pantalla lo acabo de ver aquí en la otra
screen
pantalla
ah
ah
wait
espera
eh of course it is that it
eh claro
turns out that red just
es que Resulta ser que red acaba de
posted a tweet in which it states that
poner un tweet en el que afirma que
well that has already been the reason why
bueno que ya ha sido el motivo por el
delox has deleted its entire channel
que delox ha eliminado todo su canal
another stripe for the tiger in case you were
otra raya más para el tigre por si se
wondering why the biggest
preguntaban Por qué el máximo
criminal in the Spanish-speaking crypto world
delincuente del mundo cripto de habla
delox suddenly deleted
hispana delox borró de un momento a otro
more than 1000 videos from his YouTube channel
más de 1000 vídeos de su canal de
suddenly it turns out that the pathetic guy was
repente resulta que el patético venía
promoting yet another pyramid scam
promocionando otra estafa piramidal más
and this time it includes crimes against
y esta vez incluye de delitos en contra
the Spanish public treasury okay or so It
de la hacienda pública española vale o
turns out
sea Resulta ser
that delox was
que delox estaba
promoting this man doing a
promocionando a este hombre haciendo un
lot of podcasts with him and so on
montón de podcast con él y demás
okay Chatting with a
vale Charlando con un experto en
tax expert Chatting with the
fiscalidad Charlando con el director de
sales director time is running out millionaire eh
ventas se acaba el tiempo millonario eh
[Music]
[Música]
crp Pain crp Pain crp Pain and well
crp Pain crp Pain crp Pain y pues acaba
this news just came out the
de salir esta noticia cae la estafa
crypto Spain pyramid scam that promised
piramidal de crypto Spain que prometía
incredible returns falls I have all the evidence
increíbles tengo todas las pruebas
mate brutal this
compañero brutal esto
eh brutal this
eh brutal esto
brutal all the evil you and that piece of
brutal toda la maldad cu tú y la esa de
[ __ ] Eh Because she's an ignorant
[__] Eh Porque es una ignorante
man but pretty  well look tell her she's
hombre pero guapa buenoa Mira decirle es
pretty damn [ __ ] it may be crap but she's
guapa [__] [__] será una [__] pero es
pretty pretty to you kid don't you think she's
guapa guapa para ti chaval no te parece
pretty with others look I do a lot of
guapa con otras mira que yoce muchas
things eh olivella but a lot then you've
cosas eh olivella pero muchas entonces
reported the videos Yeah yeah yeah
me has denunciado los vídeos Sí sí sí
but don't do that to me anymore I don't get paid a
pero no me haga más eso que no cobro un
buck they put it on me in Yellow when you
pavo me lo ponen en Amarillo cuando me
report it on me What do you want What do you want me to
lo denuncias Qué quieres Qué quieres que
tell you well don't do it anymore you're going
te diga pues no lo hagas más te vas de
on vacation to Cancun with Fran you're going with Fran eh you do everything that little guy did I can't remember the name of the gre that's a wonderful guy That's a kid that S that's a kid says G pasta the one who went out the other day in a fight isn't true that G
otro día en bronca no es verdad ese G
pasta cloth too Yeah yeah sure but it's that I do
pasta tela también Sí sí claro pero es
n't read them Wait a they don't
que a ellos no leo Espera a a ellos no
report their videos G If you win them
le denuncian los vídeos G Si los ganas
well yes you win a thousand yes you win them You're
bueno si tú ganas mil si los ganas Eres
worse your problem that's not my problem
peor tu problema eso no es mi problema
friend well anyway it's over I don't know
amigo bueno en fin que se acabó que no
you but listen to me what's your Nick
te sopo pero escúchame cuál es tu Nick
my Nick Yeah what's your name they're calling me
mi Nick Sí cómo te llamas me están
say  hello what's up what's up who is
diga hola Qué pasa Qué pasa Quién es
a person who is not even Lena and
pues una persona que no ni ni Lena y
has not called to mess with you
tampoco ha llamado para meterse contigo
so a unicorn But it's that I
así que un unicornio Pero es que yo nada
only want people to mess with me
más que quiero gente que se meta conmigo
well I can mess with me LL to me
bueno Yo me puedo meter conmigo LL a mí
Miss
Señorita
gentlemen I could have sex with what conchi
señoreros me pude echar con quea conchi
oh conchi conchi I hope that at some
ay conchi conchi yo espero que en algún
point I said it for the ch I say conchi
momento yo lo dije por el ch digo conchi
when I change my mind the ladyship and the
cuando cambie de idea la señoría y la
kids will wait for you with the with The of
chavalería te esperaremos con los con
course the woman had not seen
Los claro es que la mujer No había visto
the clips but let's see how you
los clips pero vamos a ver tú cómo
can talk it's not anymore How can you
puedes hablar ya no es Cómo puedes
talk because you can be good fusc
hablar porque tú puedes estar bueno fusc
but you call a youtuber he shits on
pero tú llamas a un youtuber te caga en
everything shittable without having seen a clip
todo lo cagable sin haber visto un clip
it is exactly what contradicts what
es justamente lo que contradice lo que
you are saying that I do not understand Jai
tú estás diciendo que no lo entiendo Jai
but it is that you can believe it
pero es que tú te lo puedes creer por
please exactly Oh my son at least I
favor exactamente Ay hijo mío menos está
wanted to say hello I have never
que quería saludarte que nunca te he
called you much superchat nice to meet you who
llamado mucho superchat encantado quién
are I Victoria But if I have been
eres yo Victoria Pero si te llevo
following you since June Victoria that
siguiendo desde jun Victoria que que
Nick Victoria m Hey I have the lion Yes I have been a
Nick Victoria m Oye que tengo el león Si
member for like 40  months or so
llevo siendo miembre como 40 meses o así
eh but I haven't seen my story I haven't
eh pero yo no he visto mi historia no lo
seen it wait I'm going to write now
he visto espérate voy a escribir ahora
What happens is that I have the live stopped
Lo que pasa que tengo el directo parado
to Put
a Pon
Hello I put Hello Ha look look it's true it's
Hola pongo Hola Ja mira mira es verdad
true But it only says Victoria it does
es verdad Pero pone Victoria solamente
n't say Victoria m Ah well because I must have
no pone Victoria m Ah pues porque me lo
changed it Ah
habré cambiado Ah
pu delighted anyway I sometimes on
pu encantado igualmente Yo veces en
Twitter I send you stuff okay I mean
Twitter te mando cosilla vale O sea que
you pay attention because I send you salillo I'm
tú atento porque yo te mando salillo yo
always attentive Ah now I remember okay
atento siempre Ah ya me acuerdo vale
look do you remember one day you did it's that
mira te acuerd un día que hiciste es que
now it's that surely you're going to remember
ahora es que seguro que te vas a acordar
when we were watching something from
cuando estábamos viendo algo de
Fran something from the live with something like that that I
Fran algo del directo con algo así que
put you I say my mother when I told her to
te puse yo digo mi madre cuando le dije
send me a screenshot and she took
que me mandas un pantallazo y me hizo
a picture Ah okay okay okay Yes yes of course Well
una foto Ah vale vale vale Sí sí claro
nothing son that's it I'm not bothering you
Pues nada hijo que ya está no te molesto
Hello everyone kisses from
Hola todo el mundo besitos desde
V Thank you very much of to bye it's that they
V Muchas gracias de to adió es que me
just sent me something through here
acaban de mandar una cosa por por aquí
in private that of course we're not going to be able to
por privado que claro no vamos a poder
see the complete Carmen thing because if
ver lo de Carmen más completo porque es
not we don't see the rest of the gossip
que si no no vemos el resto del salseo
but they sent me a private that
pero me han mandado por privado que por
apparently the lady
lo visto la señora
but of course
pero claro por
why Let's see it's that the people here  can
qué A ver es que la gente de aquí puede
talk as well as talk me that I This
hablar además de hablar yo que yo Esto
was a space where all the
fue un space en el que estaban todos los
traumatized were with me practically okay I mean
traumados conmigo prácticamente vale o
everyone everyone not one is missing everyone everyone everyone not
sea todos todos no falta ni uno todos
one is missing well this girl no this girl is a
uno bueno esta chica no esta chica es un
Charm apart from being a
Encanto aparte de un bellezón vale pero
beauty okay but no no this capture is not good there was another capture where you could see everyone everyone everyone what do you say you [ __ ] not one is missing they are not there meeting of those affected by Javi Oliveira and they are telling me that here is the lady on the call but of course how how are
está la señora en la llamada pero claro
you going to know who the lady is
cómo cómo vas a saber quién es la señora
if the lady is called Conchi It's that the
si la señora se llama conchi Es que la
people here can talk as well as
gente de aquí puede hablar además de
talk me that I talk every day
hablar yo que yo alogo todos los días
Come on, the one I have the most crossed out is
Dale yo al que más atravesado tengo es a
Javi it's her it's her it's her all this is
Javi es ella es ella es ella todo esto
also being broadcast on YouTube and
se está emitiendo también en YouTube y
so on I say so that you also take it
demás digo para que lo tengáis también
into account it's her eh okay all this is
en cuenta es ella eh vale todo esto
also being broadcast on YouTube and so on that so
también se está emitiendo en YouTube y
that you take it into
demás que esto para que lo tengáis en
account it doesn't matter to me I have nothing
cuenta a mí me da igual yo no tengo nada
to cover up and just in case she doesn't
que tapar y yo por si acaso ella no que
have a lot to cover up it would be at a
tiene mucho que tapar sería en un
given moment you have Javi crossed out
momento dado tienes atravesado a Javi
By  what Javi for how he is for being
Por qué a Javi por como es por lo
manipulative for being a liar for how they
manipulador por lo mentiroso por como
deal with things And then what did you
transan las cosas Y entonces qué te
think of the debate between Gibel and Javi
pareció lo del el debate de gibel Y Javi
and such that he said directly that what do you
y tal que decía directamente que qué le
think that in this case well all The
parece que en este caso bueno tod La
talk directly that they had where he
charla directamente que tuvieron donde
said that in the end Well that he was
decía que al final Pues que que él era
that Gibel was Delox's dog that
que gibel era el perro de delox que que
he was that the other called
él era que el otro llamaba el perro de
Dallas's dog in this case do you think that in this
de Dallas en este caso crees que en este
case one of the two was more right
caso alguno de los dos tenía más razón
than the other both I The only thing I saw
que el otro los dos Yo lo único que vi
Is that Gibel was constantly making fun of him
Es que gibel le estaba tomando el pelo
and was laughing at him it's
constantemente y se estuvo riendo de él
not and then the other one on top of that makes a
no es y luego el otro encima te hace un
redirect of 5 hours to have his no no
redirecto de 5 horas para tener su no no
you were wrong It looks like it but it's not It looks
os habéis equivocado Se parece pero no
like it but it's not it would have been great
es Se parece pero no es hubiera sido un
eh it would have been great but it's not it would have been
puntazo eh hubiera sido puntazo pero no
great but it's not What's up
es hubiera sido puntazo pero no es Qué
my
pasa mi
racel rasel is writing to me there
racel rasel me está escribiendo por ahí
well let's see today there has been this
bueno a ver hoy ha habido esta
controversy
polemiques
you're going to love the video from the main Channel
os va a encantar el vídeo del Canal
you just tell you
tú solo os digo
that today there is a controversy molinero okay
eso hoy hay una polemiques molinero vale
for this story that uploaded  on her
por esta historia que subió en su cuenta
Instagram account in which basically
de Instagram en el que básicamente
someone is asking her it's a round
alguien le está preguntando es una ronda
of questions you know that there are some
de preguntas ya sabéis que hay algunos
influencers who do
influencers que hacen
this does your son go to a public school
esto tu hijo va al colegio público
private or subsidized and
privado o concertado y
private because it is a
privado porque es de educación
respectful education but no I don't understand this
respetuosa pero no no entiendo esto por
why adar has answered this private
qué adar ha contestado esto privado
because it is a
porque es de educación
respectful education What does she mean by
respetuosa A qué se refiere con con
respectful education is that I don't
educación respetuosa es que no lo
understand it, I mean, all schools have respectful
entiendo o sea todos los colegios tienen
education no or no Or they are not
educaciones respetuosas no o no O no son
respectful the others, let's see there is school and there is
respetuosos los demás a ver hay colegi y
school Of course obviously but but it
hay colegio Claro evidentemente pero per
could be that I mean no it's not because it is
puede que o sea no no es porque sea
private
privado
no I don't understand it the
no no lo entiendo No lo entiendo la
truth I mean what she meant with
verdad O sea lo que ha querido decir con
that is that I don't understand people are
eso es que no lo entiendo la gente le
giving her cloth my children's school
está dando tela el colegio de mis hijos
is public and it is also a respectful education
es público y también es de educación
she says I don't doubt that they try to give them the
dice ella no dudo que intenten darle la
best education Of course they do, they simply
mejor educación Claro que sí simplemente
use other methods when it comes to
utilizan otros métodos a la hora de
teaching or educating I have not criticized
enseñar o educar no he criticado los
public schools calm down Peace And Love
colegios públicos calma Peace And Love
Well, there are no rude people in
Pues anda que no hay maleducado en
private schools, I can't talk about this
privado no puedo hablar de de esto
because I really don't know
porque realmente no sé
if I don't know if
si no sé si
man I think that the schools that  They
hombre Yo creo que los colegios que
cost a fortune, I
valen una pasta
think that schools that cost a
yo creo que los colegios que valen una
fortune and that cost so much money and all that
pasta y que valen tanta pasta y todo el
nonsense, don't be
rollo ese no
quiet, let's see, I think they've made some change, I don't
calletanos a ver creo que algún cambio
know if it's because of involvement, I don't know if, I mean,
no no sé si involucración no sé si o sea
the truth is that I don't know, I couldn't tell you.
la verdad que no lo sé no podría deciros
In that sense, but I imagine that the
En ese sentido Pero me imagino que la
people who spend the money, it's not for a reason, no,
gente que se gasta la pasta No es por
also no, or what. Let's see, I understand
algo no también no o qué A ver entiendo
that it could, I understand that it could offend, no, I'm
que pueda entiendo que pueda ofender no
also telling you, I understand that it could
también te digo entiendo que pueda
offend,
ofender
but it's a method of, it's an
pero es un método de de es un método
educational method called
educativo que se llama educación
respectful education, that's what I imagined
respetuosa por ahí me me imaginaba que
was, I
iba la
mean, it's a
cosa o sea es un
method called respectful education, it
método que se llama así educación
's a method called that or what. I
es un método que se llama así o qué O
mean, it's not that I'm saying, it's not that I
sea no es que esté diciendo no es que
'm saying that his school is respectful
esté diciendo que el suyo sea respetuoso
and the other one, no, no, don't
y el otro no
turn it around. Javi, man, who
no no le des vuelta Javi hombre que lo
wants to
quier
understand, it depends on the money, it doesn't
entender depende la pasta no te
guarantee that he's more prepared than in a
garantiza que esté más preparado que en
public one, in that sense, I wouldn't know how to
público en ese sentido No sabría yo
tell you,
deciros
eh. Let's see, I wouldn't know how to tell you
eh A ver que No sabría
the
deciros la
truth, I wouldn't know how to say it, I went to a
verdad No sabría decirlo yo fui al
private school and in the public school, it
privado y al público
's a method. Javi says Anika Anik, I mean, it
es un método Javi dice anika anik o sea
's a method  that's called that right? But
es un método que se llama así no Pero
why are some of you telling me that it
por qué algunos me estáis diciendo que
's a method and others not
es un método y otros que no
clarifying that respect is taught at home
aclararos el respeto se enseña en casa a
let's see what Javi de Hoyo says
ver vamos a ver lo que dice Javi de hoyo
Adara criticizes public education This
adara critica la educación pública Esta
is a question that many of us are asking ourselves
es una pregunta que muchos nos estamos
after the messages that she has
haciendo después de los mensajes que ha
published on her social networks but I have
publicado en sus redes sociales pero he
to tell you that I think she has expressed herself
de deciros que creo que se ha expresado
very badly and thanks to my sister-in-law who
muy mal y gracias a mi cuñada que yo no
had no idea about the types of Education to
tenía ni idea de los tipos de Educación
know what
conocer a qué se está refiriendo
exactly Adara is referring to and I'm going to explain it to you
exactamente adara y os lo voy a explicar
in this video before following me to stay up to
en este vídeo antes seguirme para estar
date with the latest gossip
al tanto de la última hora del salseo le
nadara asks her Does your son go to a
pregunta nadara Tu hijo va a colegio
public, private, or subsidized school And she says
público privado o concertado Y ella dice
private because it is for
privado porque es de educación
respectful education, of course seen So you say that
respetuosa claro visto Así tú dices
public and
qué que los colegios públicos y
subsidized schools are not for
concertados no son de Educación
respectful education in reality it is because she has
respetuosa en realidad se debe a que se
expressed herself badly then another
ha expresado mal luego le escribe otra
person writes to her my children's school is
persona el colegio de mis hijos es
public and it is also for
público y también es de educación
respectful education and she answers I do not doubt that they
respetuosa y ella contesta no dudo que
try to give them the best education Of course they
intenten darle la mejor educación Claro
simply use other
que si simplemente utilizan otros
methods when teaching or
métodos a la hora de enseñar o
educating calm down peace and love but of course for
educar calma paz y amor pero claro para
those who  we are not up to date on the
los que no estamos puestos en los
existing education methods the
métodos de Educación que existen la
way you write your adara sounds
manera en la que escribes tu adara suena
disrespectful or Nuri says my son goes to the
irrespetuosa o Nuri dice mi hijo va a la
salle but Nuri you are from Seville
salle pero Nuri tú eres de Sevilla coleg
public school but really He is already
públ pero realmente Ya se está
referring to the fact that there is a method
refiriendo a que hay un método que se
called respectful education and that
denomina educación respetuosa y que lo
only some
tienen implantado tan solo algunos
private schools have implemented it if we search for it on
colegios privados si lo buscamos en
Google it is explained it says the
Google se explica dice el modelo de
respectful education model bases all its
Educación respetuosa basa todas sus
teachings I knew that the
enseñanzas sabía que iban por aquí los
shots tutors were going in this direction it seemed very
tiros tutores es que me parecía muy
beastly to say something like that I mean it sounds like Of
bestia decir algo así o sea es que suena
course if you don't know like me who just found
a a Claro si tú no lo sabes como yo que
out it sounds like No no it's that
me acabo de enterar suena como a No no
there they give him in that school they give him
es que ahí le dan en ese colegio le dan
respectful education not in
educación respetuosa no en los Colegios
public schools they give him respect they give him
públicos le dan respeto que le dan
education so that children go around
Educación para que los niños vayan por
there pulling bags you
ahí pegando tirones de bolso me
understand teachers and the boy or girl
entiendes profesorado y el niño o niña
in this sense there are no punishments or
en este sentido no existen castigos o
bad
malas
words an attitude of respect with everyone
palabas una actitud de respeto con todoo
who answers Likewise with respect
que responde Igualmente con respeto
let's go that it is a teaching method and he is not
vamos que es un método de enseñanza y no
referring to the fact that his son for going
se está refiriendo a que su hijo por ir
to a private school will receive a
a un colegio privado vaya a recibir una
respectful education as such but that's what the
educación respetuosa como tal sino que
teaching method
se denomina así al método de enseñanza
that your child receives is called and it's a new method
que recibe su hijo y es un nuevo método
that is being implemented in some
que se implanta en algunos colegios
private schools. I knew that was the way things were going.
privados lo sabía que iban por ahí los
La Salle also has it in Bilbao,
tiros La Salle también la hay en Bilbao
the s is all over Spain. Oh, I didn't know, I did
la s está en toda España Ah no lo sabía
n't know. Let's see. I know that mine, which
no lo sabía a ver yo sé que el mío que
was the Irish, yes, there are
eran las irlandesas sí que lo hay en
several in various parts of Spain. Yes, I know that.
varios en varios puntos de España eso sí
Look, it seems to me to be a tremendous mistake that they
lo sé mira me parece un error tremendo
brought Aida into
el hecho que hayan metido a la Aida en
this "slvame" thing, man. It seems to me to be a
esto del sálvame tío me parece un
complete mistake. Huh. It
completo error
seems to me to be a complete mistake. No, I don't
eh Me parece un completo error no no le
see the grace in this. No, it's
veo la gracia el tema de No no es que es
very provocative, I don't know what. I see that there is a
muy provocadora no sé qué Yo veo que
lack of respect, it's not funny, it's just that it does
falta el respeto que no tiene gracia
n't make me laugh, I don't understand it, I don't
es que no me hace gracia no lo
understand it. Well, now you're all going to tell me,
entiendo Bueno ahora me vais a decir
all of you, the city of D is La Salle. Now
todos todos la ciudad de D está la salle
what are you sending me? You're
aara qué me estás mandando me estás
sending me. Where are the s? You really are so
mandando Dónde están las ses de verdad
annoying many times. Huh. You're so
que pesados ponéis muchas veces eh
annoying many times. It's not like
pesados os ponéis muchas veces eh Ni que
I was going to buy shares in La
yo fuera a comprar ahora acciones en La
Salle right now.  It's really called the method, leave me
Salle de verdad se llama método dejarme
now With the s and the
ya Con la s y el
Sayo, this has been this has been Marta's gold
Sayo esto ha sido esto ha sido oro de
Eh This has been Marta's gold,
Marta Eh Esto ha sido oro de Marta
kid Marta has been the best
chaval Marta sí que ha sido el mejor
signing that he could have, not that we
fichaje que que ha podido tener el ni
were eh no, the nisar idea I mean the
que fuéramos eh no la ida nisar O sea la
nisar ID was a mistake mistake mistake
ID nisar ha sido
but Marta is the best Jos
error pero Marta es de lo mejor José
Mara Jos is still smoking I can't
María José sigue fumando no me lo puedo
believe it he pulled up next to me in the car
creer se ha puesto al lado en el coche
Jos Hello, where are you going in case I get
José Hola dónde vas por si me
lost Tell me more or less where you're going, it's
pierdo Dime más o menos dónde vas está
really comfortable Well,
comodísimo Pues
nothing and in the end he managed eh look in the
nada y al final ha conseguido eh mira
end he managed he stops with Look
al final ha conseguido se para con Mira
Well, nothing, I simply told him
Bueno nada simplemente que le he dicho
that we were leaving that I wanted to say goodbye
que ya nos íbamos que me quería despedir
to him How lucky for tomorrow that you
de él Que suerte para mañana que lo
take it as best as you can and you wanted to
lleves lo mejor que puedas y querías
say hello No, well, thank you very much See you
saludarnos No pues muchas gracias Hasta
later Good afternoon Greetings for a
luego Buenas tardes Un saludo para un
greeting and thank you Give me two kisses Jos
saludo y gracias Dame dos besos José
Mara Ah This is for what the mother
María Ah Esto es para lo que la madre
who gave birth to her is cu that everything goes well for you,
que la parió son cu que se te de bien
thank you Goodbye Well, nothing,
todo gracias Adiós Bueno nada
simply the mother
simplemente la madre
stopped Hey, but now you're all there
paro Oye pero ahora estáis ahí todo el
time if the salle my daughter studied
tiempo que si la salle mi hija estudió
in the salle my daughter had a
en la salle mi hija le robaron un
sandwich stolen eh but please how tiresome you
bocadillo eh pero por favor qué cansinos
are eh sometimes let's see let's see
sois eh algunas veces a ver vamos a ver
this This is an interview with Yuji on
esto Esto es una entrevista de yuji en
a television in Thailand What
en una televisión de Tailandia Lo que
happens is that I think it is a I think it is a
pasa que creo que es una creo que es una
television that broadcasts only on YouTube
televisión que emite solo en YouTube
so I don't know if we are going to be able to understand
entonces no sé si vamos a poder entender
the entire interview I am going to do everything
completa la entrevista voy a hacer todo
possible okay eh but I don't know if the
lo posible vale eh pero no s si la
transcription is going to be very good
transcripción va estar muy bien
eh At the moment it's going well before watching the
eh De momento va bien antes de ver el
interview program Don't forget to press
entrevistas No olvides presionar el me
like and share and press subscribe
gusta y compartir y presiona suscribirte
with us too Yi alisa Yi a
con nosotros también Yi alisa Yi una
young model it's so hot that today I will
joven modelo hace tanto calor que hoy le
propose to my girlfriend okay I mean it
propondré matrimonio a mi novia vale o
was hot the girlfriend was hot and
sea tenía calor la novia tenía calor y
said well since it's very hot I'm going to
dijo pues como hace mucha calor le voy a
put I'm going to propose to
poner Le voy a proponer matrimonio a
arruga and she's ready to reveal that
arruga y está lista para revelar que el
love doesn't require love It's not just
amor no se requiere el amor No solo son
5 minutes and then you disappear okay
5 minutos y luego desapareces vale el
love requires a lot of time invested in
amor requiere mucho tiempo invertido en
the person you
la persona que
love is it too soon to get married
amas es demasiado pronto para casarse
Well who knows it's a
Bueno quién sabe es un evento
shocking event and has joined and they are going to fight
impactante y se ha unido y van a luchar
with life in life  holding
con la vida en la vida tomados de la
hands
mano
are soulmates in past lives okay I do
son almas gemelas en vidas pasadas vale
n't know if this is like a belief or
No sé si esto será como una creencia o
something so today I would like to
algo por eso hoy me gustaría darle la
welcome Yuji and his
bienvenida a yuji y su
girlfriend
novia
elegant elegant the girlfriend's nickname
elegante elegante el apodo de la novia
is elegant I don't know if it's the translation
es elegante no sé si será la traducción
of rat as
de rata como decía el el
Fran said. Hello viewers How are you How are you
Fran Hola espectadores Qué tal Cómo
today we have a very
estáis hoy tenemos un programa muy
hot program We have Aisa here and
candente Tenemos aquí aisa y
our interview show Hello Hello
a nuestro program de entrevista Hola
How are you
Hola Qué tal
Good well viewers are you Here
Buenas bueno espectadores estáis Aquí
watching us also on Facebook and on
mirándonos también en Facebook y en
TikTok So nothing share like
tiktok Así que nada compartir dle like
all those little things well we have
todas esas cosillas bueno tenemos
news you just proposed to each other you just got
noticias os acabáis de pedir matrimonio
engaged congratulations
os acabáis de comprometer felicitaros
first of all okay thank you very much thank you we
antes que nada vale muchas gracias
are going to talk about the moment when they
gracias vamos a hablar del momento en el
proposed to her What happened that
que le pidieron matrimonio Qué pasó ese
day We want to know what is the
día Queremos saber cuál es el punto de
starting point for you to decide to propose to her
partida para que decidas pedirle
Well I have to tell you Let's
matrimonio Bueno tengo que decírtelo A
see let me tell you first that it has to
ver déjame decirte primero que tiene que
be like this we should have known each other a
ser así deberíamos habernos conocido
long time ago but well we have
hace mucho tiempo pero bueno nos hemos
known each other for a short time but we have a
conocido hace poco pero tenemos una
very intense relationship we know each other as
relación muy intensa nos conocemos por
Top The younger brother he is the
top El hermano menor él es el hermano
younger brother I am a younger version of Top
menor soy una versión más joven de Top
eh pa Top pa Top and nothing well  I have a lot of
eh pa top pa top y nada pues tengo mucha
trust it's a close relationship
confianza es una relación cercana
I know the family all the fishing and
conozco la familia toda la pesca y
divine us
divino nos
this has been a thing of destiny we were
esto ha sido cosa del destino estábamos
at an event for the opening of a
en un evento de una inauguración de una
store that my brother opened and I
tienda que inauguró mi hermano y me
liked the aunt she was quite good
gustó la tía estaba bastante buena las
things like
cosas como
[Music]
[Música]
are well look I heard her story
son pues mira escuché su historia
State I
State
thought it had been a mistake I thought we had
pensé que había sido un error pensé que
n't seen each other and And well when I
no nos veíamos y Y bueno pues yo cuando
saw him when I saw her really it was
lo vi cuando la vi realmente sí fue fue
strange
extraño
everything look That is the day It seems to be there is
todo mira Ese es el día Parece ser ahí
everything he knows about the matters I don't know why
tod él sabe de los asuntos no sé por qué
the translation says masculine But I
la traducción sale masculino Pero me
imagine it will be feminine no Or maybe
imagino que será femenino no O a lo
Thai when conjugating the pronouns I don't
tailandés al conjugar los pronombres no
know
sé
transcription like no
transcripción como que no
True that the first thing is that there isn't the
Verdad que lo primero que ni la hay lo
first thing that there isn't
primero que ni la hay
r
r
[Music]
[Música]
happ
happ
here they are talking about their relationship
aquí están hablando sobre su relación
because this is the first time that she
porque esta es la primera vez que ella
is with a
está con una
woman the
mujer la
feeling for I feel very comfortable I can
sensación por me siento muy cómoda puedo
talk she makes me laugh I can talk to
hablar me hace reír puedo hablar con
her and I feel very good I am very
ella y me siento muy bien Estoy muy a
comfortable with her no
gusto con ella no
when we are
cuando estamos
together it is like we have very
juntos es como que tenemos cosas muy
similar things have you ever been in a
similares has estado alguna vez en una
relationship in in another lgbt relationship and she says
relación en en otra relación lgtb y dice
well it is  that all the names
bueno es que como que todos los nombres
sound very similar right since they are
suenan muy similares verdad como son
monosyllables you know they sound very similar a
monosílabos sabes suenan muy parecidos
lot
mucho
[Music]
[Música]
[Laughter]
[Risas]
to
to
no the brother the brother hasn't said top
no el hermano el hermano no ha dicho top
the brother has said
el hermano ha dicho
payop Javi has been to Thailand twice
payop Javi ha ido dos veces a Tailandia
and he speaks fluent Thai But because I
y habla tailandés fluido Pero porque
'm used to it but apart from that it's that I
estoy acostumbrado pero aparte es que me
can communicate right now Even if you
puedo comunicar ahora mismo Incluso si
want with a cap bara I mean right now I'm
queréis con una capí bara o sea yo ahora
going to start chatting with a
mismo me pongo aquí a charla con una
cap paraa well I just tried to
capí paraa bueno acabo de intentar
actually talk to a rat and it didn't
hablar de hecho con una rata y no me la
get me but let's say
ha cogido pero vamos que tranquilamente
I can easily relate to anyone eh we
me puedo relacionar con cualquiera eh
've always seen each other he
siempre nos hemos visto a los
wanted his two younger brothers to
dos quería que sus dos hermanos menores
have him I really hope
lo tuvieran Realmente espero
that it's that I think it
que es que yo creo
fits It's that I think the pronunciation
quepa Es que creo que la pronunciación
makes the subtitle appear wrong and I
hace que el subtítulo aparezca mal y
think that before he said p and
creo que antes cuando ha dicho p y
when he said top and when he said
cuando ha dicho top y cuando ha dicho
Now top you see that it says top I think that
Ahora top lo veis que pone top creo que
in reality it's the same person and it's the
en realidad es la misma persona y es el
older brother okay
hermano mayor vale
So I don't know why an told you that
Entonces no sé porque an te ha dicho que
a person gtv It would be for top this is very
una persona le gtv Sería para top es muy
complicated and the translation
complicado esto e la traducción
eh  that I think if I'm not mistaken This
eh que creo que si no me equivoco Este
is the
es el hermano
older brother I think the older brother is this one
mayor creo que el hermano mayor es este
and I think he's a long time friend of the family
y creo que es amigo de la familia de
or something like that Or at least of
siempre o algo así O por lo menos de
hers but it's always like it's like very
ella pero siempre es como es como muy
nice
agradable
of
de la
wealth a family a lot of
riqueza una familia mucha
wealth them first see a
riqueza tem primer ve una
ch Energy
ch Energy
Energy I'm hallucinating because this
Energy yo que alucino porque que esta
woman is great eh 50 tacos
mujer está estupendamente eh 50 tacos
is that she's great
es que está genial
Eh are you going to put me in the chat the
Eh ya me vais a poner en el chat los
Asians the Asians [ __ ] Well I don't
asiáticos los asiáticos [__] Pues yo no
see that all the Well yes Actually
veo que todos los Bueno sí En realidad
yes there was one once we went to a
sí había uno una vez que fuimos a una
gas station and I said to Fran damn why are
gasolinera y le dije a Fran [__] porque
the people who serve you
la gente que te sirve la
gas 13 14 years old not 15 I don't know
gasolina tienen 13 14 años no 15 no sé
something like that aren't they super young to be
algo así no son son super joven para
working and he says no no he says
estar trabajando y dice no no me dice
Fran no no yes those people must be 30 and
Fran no no si esa gente tendrán 30 y
long what happens is that here
largo lo que pasa que aquí la
people but but it's that it's that Look at the
gente pero pero es que es que Mirad la
skin Look at the skin Look at the the thing
piel Mirad la piel Mirad la la lo de
under the jaw and the neck you can see it
abajo de la mandíbula y el cuello lo ves
's brutal s apart from that she's pretty she's pretty she
está brutal s aparte es que es guapa es
has great hair but [ __ ] it's that
guapa tiene un pelazo pero [__] es
we sign anyone eh  for arriving like this
que firmamos cualquiera eh por llegar
eh For keeping us like this at 50
así eh Por mantenernos así en 50
Jai, there is makeup already but
Jai existe el maquillaje ya pero es que
she always looks like this eh I mean she has
ella siempre se ve así eh o sea tiene
videos in the sanctuary and she is like this she is
vídeos en el santuario y está así está
spectacular But oh well the physique is the
espectacular Pero buo el físico es lo
too
too
let us stop for a moment to do a
permítenos frenar un momento hacer una
pa it is said that the proposal was very
pa se dice que la propuesta fue mu
sweet there is a pause have you seen the
dulce tiene una pausa habéis visto la
pause the typical commercial break and
pausa la típica pausa de publicidad y
then it is as if there was no pause
luego es como si no había ninguna pausa
this is because it is a reuploaded program
esto es porque es un programa resubido
that will be broadcast on TV it has 2 and a
que lo emitirán en la tele tiene 2
half million subscribers this the
millones y medio de suscriptores esto el
channel This will be a program that will be broadcast
canal Esto será un programa que lo
on TV and then they upload it to
emiten en la tele y luego lo suben a
YouTube like they often do
YouTube como como muchas veces que hacen
with some programs
con algunos programas
[Music]
[Música]
plan
plan
m
m
here if I'm not mistaken she mentioned what we
aquí si no me equivoco ha mencionado lo
were talking about that she is going to
que estuvimos hablando de que ella va a
be the first
ser la primera
wedding
boda
moment Well look precisely
momento Pues mira precisamente me acaba
Fran just spoke to me that he
de me acaba de hablar Fran que se ha
woke up and he just woke up in
despertado y se acaba de despertar por
the morning and he said to me and he said what the
la mañana y me ha puesto y ha dicho qué
hell is this guy watching that is watching
[__] está viendo este que está viendo la
TV from Thailand Hey well here I am
tele de Tailandia Oye pues aquí estoy
seeing if they give you the green light or not the
viendo a ver si te ponen verde o no la
truth is that it seems to me  a little difficult
verdad que se me hace un poco difícil
because this doesn't have a translation or anything,
porque esto ni tiene traducción ni tiene
look, this was uploaded the day
nada fíjate que esto está subido de
before yesterday, so if it was uploaded the day
antes de ayer entonces si está subido de
before yesterday, if this generated the
antes de ayer si esto generase la
transcription it would have already come out, but of
transcripción ya ya habría salido pero
course,
claro
damn, but it seems really beastly to me
[__] pero es que me parece muy bestia
40 minutes talking about this, eh, a
40 minutos hablando de esto eh una
cake These are like, like, some
tarta Estos son como una como unos
gifts Look at some beans, can you
regalos Mira unos frijol puedes
try them I want to eat them, it's very
probarlos quiero comerlo está muy
chopped up, he wants to
cortado quiere
try it, I want to eat them, I want to eat some
probarlo quiero comer quiero comer
fat balls, he says to her, it
bolitas gorditas le dice
makes me feel like I'm
me hace sentir como si estuviera
exercising, who knows, the translation is this, I
ejercicio vete tú a saber la traducción
mean, how the hell do I want to eat some
esta o sea cómo [__] quiero comer
fat balls? It ends up being
bolitas gorditas se acaba
translated or it ends up feeling like I
traduciendo o se acaba sintiendo como si
'm
estuviera haciendo
exercising? I think I shouldn't have
ejercicio creo que no tenía que haber
read this sentence.
leído esta frase
Fran said stop, but he should talk and
Fran dijo stop pero debe hablar y
report it, no, but maybe he's not
denunciar no pero es que a lo mejor no
talking about Fran, let's see, they told me to
habla de Fran a ver a m me han dicho que
look at it because it was supposed to be talking about
lo mire porque se suponía que hablaba de
Fran, but maybe he's not talking about Fran, he
Fran pero a lo mejor no habla de
always caresses her on the
Fran siempre la caricia la
head. Look, the photo is a gift in the
cabeza Mira regalado la foto que los
newspapers, but it doesn't talk about Fran, this,
periódicos pero no habla de Fran esto
eh, they don't talk about the relationship,
eh no hablan de la relación de
the moment was right and the
ello el momento era el adecuado y el
event was, let's see, maybe there's
evento era a ver que a lo mejor hay
some plla, eh  I mean maybe there's
alguna plla eh o sea a lo mejor hay
some hint of some pick but
alguna indirecta de alguna pua pero
of course We're not going to catch her
claro No la vamos a pillar
during the time of
durante la época de
covid she's already here on video calls
covid ya se pone aquí en videollamada
with her
con los
relatives, no, she's not talking about Fran eh
familiares esto no no habla de Fran eh
well let's see this we already knew more or
bueno a ver esto ya lo sabíamos más o
less
menos
she now apparently it's going to be a
ella ahora por lo visto va a ser una
movie
película
and And then well Well she'll have to
e Y entonces bueno Pues tendrá que
go her way the truth is that I was hoping to
seguir su camino la verdad que esperaba
find something but but there's nothing
encontrarme algo pero pero no hay nada
What's up
Qué pasa
Pili
Pili
Ah
Ah
ah they just sent me that where
ah me acaban de mandar que donde el
Antonio is is
Antonio
the lady from
este está la señora de la llamada de
yesterday's call but what do you see that of saying
ayer pero que que te ve la esa de decir
but if that person has the pleasure
pero si esa persona tiene el gusto yo
when I have the pleasure of giving
cuando tengo el gusto de regalar
something away I'm not a big fan of being
algo no soy mu partidario de de que me
refuted yes or no It's not that I do it and that's it you
rebatan sí o no No es que lo hago y
understand If I have the pleasure of
punto entiendes Si yo tengo el gusto de
doing something then when they do it
hacer algo entonces cuando lo hacen
with me I suppose they do it with all the
conmigo Supongo que lo hacen con todo el
pleasure in the world nothing this is
gusto del mundo nada esto para nada no
never going to be uploaded in life he's a
va a subir nunca en la vida es un
coward a Spanish gypsy confesses that he
cobarde un gitano español confiesa que
was with Shakira and they cheated
estuvo con Shakira y le pusieron los
on Piqu have you seen this
cuernos a Piqué habéis visto esta
viral news were you with Shakira or something or
viral tú estuviste con Shakira o algo o
not I
no
already said it  No No but
ya lo dije No No pero yo es que algunas
sometimes they would come out to you but I don't
veces me salían para ti pero no lo
know I was with her that's what
sé estuve con ella yé es lo que ha
happened eh what happened
pasado eh que qué es lo que ha pasado
but no seriously let's see I was
por pero no serio vamos a ver yo estaba
in a hotel in Barcelona okay I already told it I've
en un hotel en Barcelona vale Ya lo
told it before but well
conté lo hab contado otra vez pero bueno
I was in a
yo estuve en un
hotel I was with a girl she was
hotel estaba en una chavala estaba
doing a gig there Go out a gig it's not
haciendo allí un bolo Sal un bolo no s
clear Okay so nothing they paid me they
claro Vale pues nada a m me pag me lo
paid me everything well that this in the hotel and
pagan todo bueno que esto en el hotel y
nothing I was going to buy something for tobacco or
nada iba a comprar algo por tabaco o
something I don't know and in the hallways I
algo no sé y por los pasillos me la
find Shaquira I
encuentro la Shaquira
see her
la veo lo
normally she looks at me she says I don't know something she said to me I
normal me mira me dice no s algo me dijo
say man yeah I don't know yeah What's up
digo hombre dio sí no sé dio Qué pasa la
Shaquira no and she said to me go to the
Shaquira no y me me dijo vete para el
room to my room the typical thing well I
cuarto para mi habitación lo típico pues
saw her in her room And you know I'm a
me vi para su habitación Y sabes soy
man Man cl the typical thing no you
hombre Hombre cl lo típico no esta que
're buying tobacco you're
estás comprando tabaco esta que estás
buying tobacco and and you run into
comprando tabaco y y te encuentras con
Shakira at the same machine you know and And
Shakira en la misma máquina sabes y Y
then Shakira
entonces Shakira le le
says nothing to her Hey you're Shakira no yeah yeah let's
dice nada Oye tú eres Shakira no sí sí
go and I'm here having a gig Ah well
vamos y estoy aquí en un bolo Ah pues
come  for the
vente para el
room look at you that at first I said it
cuarto fíjate tú que al principio digo
will be you'll see
será verás
Well I
Pues yo le
believe him but whatever it is that he doesn't tell you not
creo pero sea que es que no te lo cuenta
even I who know adore him a little
ni siquiera yo que sé adorándolo un poco
no yeah no no eh I arrived I was I
no sio no no eh llegué
was buying
estaba Estaba comprando
tobacco [ __ ] Don't
tabaco hostias No
[ __ ] with me it's that I'm without the spectators
jodas es que estoy sin los espectadores
and they just told me that we are here
y me acaban de avisar que estamos aquí
almost 2000
casi 2000
people I didn't know that we are
personas Yo no sabía eso que estamos
here almost 2000 people eh we are here
aquí casi 2000 personas eh estamos aquí
to
de
chill you were with Shakira or something or not I
chill tú estuviste con Shakira o algo o
already said it No No but I
no Ya lo dije No No pero yo es que
sometimes they came out for you but I don't
algunas veces me salían para ti pero no
know I'm cool with her I love it I
lo sé yo chve con ella
love it but it's that I
encanta me encanta pero es que me
love it as she says if I was with her Yes
encanta como dice si estuve con ella Sí
the
la
truth
verdad
yes eh what has happened for sure
sí eh que qué es lo que ha pasado por se
but no seriously let's see I was in a
pero no serio vamos ver yo estaba en un
hotel Barcelona okay I already told it I'm going
hotel Barcelona vale Ya lo conté lo voy
to tell it again but well I was
a contar otra vez pero bueno yo estuve
in a
en un
hotel this girls I was doing
hotel esta una chabalas estaba haciendo
a gig there a gig comes out no Yes of course
allí un bolo sale un bolo no Sí claro
Okay well nothing the hotel pays me they
Vale pues nada a m me paga el hotel me
pay me for everything I'm in the hotel and
lo pagan todo que estoy en el hotel y
nothing I was going to buy something tobacco something I don't
nada iba a comprar algo tabaco algo no
know and  in the hallways I find her
sé y por los pasillos me la encuentro la
Shaquira I
Shaquira
see her she looks at me she says I don't know something she told me I say
veo me mira dice no s algo me dijo digo
man pas laqu and she said Come to the
hombre pas laqu y me dijo Vente para el
room to my room well I saw her
cuarto para mi habitación pues me vi
to her room and I am a man man
para su habitación y soy un hombre
of course let's see the aunt was
hombre claro vamos a ver la tía estaba
she was with Piqu there I say it clearly
ella estaba con Piqué ahí lo digo claro
I already said it because since Piqu
yo ya es que lo dich porque como Piqué
has done what he has done to her man [ __ ] him
le ha hecho lo que le ha hecho hombre
now clearly
que le den por culo ahora claramente
now that he [ __ ] her Piqu Piqu whenever
ahora que le por culo Piqué Piqué cuando
you want and I tell you piqu whenever you
tú quieras y te lo digo piqu cuando tú
want he comes he hits me or something no I mean
quieras viene me pega o algo no o sea
this is tremendous no this is
esto es tremendo no esto es
tremendous but what I don't understand is
tremendo pero lo que no entiendo yo es
Mediterranean digital giving that news
mediterráneo digital dando esa noticia
no let's see here we have several things to
no a ver aquí tenemos varias cositas que
comment on
comentar
and with one you are going to
y y con una os vais a
laugh your asses off it has been collected in a place
descojonarse ha recogido en un sitio
where a channel already informed us no that it had been
donde ya nos informó un canal no que se
sold and they are foreigners very
había vendido y son extranjeros mu
foreigners Ah okay these are the
extranjeros Ah vale estos son los
very foreign foreigners okay they are
extranjeros muy extranjeros vale son
very foreign foreigners eh eh They are very foreign foreigners
extranjeros muy extranjeros eh
they are
eh Son extranjeros muy extranjeros son
very foreigners eh those who have taken
muy extranjeros eh los que han cogido la
Loli's lawsuit and have signed in their
demanda de Loli y han firmado a su
name Eh from Ukraine from Ukraine and
nombre Eh de Ucrania de Ucrania y
so we think it's there I can't
entonces creemos que está allí no lo
confirm 100% not to confirm see
puedo confirmar 100% no confirmar ver
you but we think it's there the thing
tú pero creemos que sí está ahí la cosa
can only be there No everything else no
solo puede estar ahí No todo lo demás no
So it doesn't come out until 10 between when it
Entonces hasta las 10 no sale de entre
comes and goes to let us
que sale y llega para dejar que
see I think it's going to get a little
veamos creo que se va a hacer un poco
late but
tarde pero
tomorrow we have another
mañana tenemos otro
live so Yeah anyway we don't have what
directo para qu Si total no tenemos lo
but I don't have Hey he said something already about
que pero no teng Oye ha dicho algo ya de
whether the Ukrainians have given him the demand
si los ucranianos le han dado la demanda
or what Eh I have to go from other people but I
o qué Eh tengo que ir de otra gente pero
don't have the one from
no tengo el de
Alande Uy Karim Look maybe if it's
alande Uy Karim Mira a lo mejor si está
around
por
here they're having a party here
aquí aquí se están haciendo una fiesta
eh there's a
eh se está haciendo una
party going on Look listen to me go ahead let's see
fiesta pues Mira escúchame adante a ver
alne there's one thing I want to tell you watch
alne hay una cosa que te quiero decir
like Jorge Javier okay
ojo como Jorge Javier está bien
that's we'll see each other of course and since you don't
eso nos vemos por supuesto y ya que no
have anything to show your audience
tienes nada para enseñar a tu audiencia
to send it to your friend so they can put
para mandarle a tu amigo para que ponga
the moment I hope you have it where you have to have it
el momento Espero que lo tengas donde lo
wait a second
tienes que tener espera un segundo que
Lorena is calling me just a second You're
me está llamando Lorena un segundito De
welcome
nada
eh
eh
al al
al al
I hope you don't go it's that I don't know
Espero que no vayáis es que yo no sé
why this lady says
porque esta señora dice
[Music]
[Música]
that she says that  that we have not put here
que dice que que no hemos puesto aquí
anything of what she has done to us, whether she
nada de lo que ella nos ha hecho sea que
repeats this constantly, not that
esto lo repite constantemente no que
all those things that we
todas esas cosas que nosotros
mentioned that she has told us as if it
mencionamos que ella nos ha dicho como
were a fantasy, I mean, let's see
si fuera una fantasía o sea vamos a ver
here. What is a fantasy and that does not
aquí Lo que sí es una fantasía y que no
exist and that they have never put are their
existe y que no han puesto nunca son los
clicks where well
click de ellas donde bueno los c
our c where we crush her for
nuestros donde la machacamos a ella por
not
no
going or for not donating or for anything, I mean,
vamos ni por no donar ni por nada o sea
we have asked for that actively and
eso lo hemos pedido por activa y por
passively because it is a mantra that they have
pasiva porque es un mantra que ellas han
created, her and her little friend that her
creado ella y su amiguita que su
little friend has now done like this, I don't know if you have
amiguita ahora ha hecho así no sé si lo
seen it but you are going to see it
habéis visto pero lo Vais a ver ahora
again now okay, but they created a mantra, I
otra vez vale pero crearon un mantra o
mean, let's see practically a moment
sea vamos a ver prácticamente un momento
that I have to choose a title for the
que tengo que elegir título para el
video of the main Channel
vídeo del Canal principal
Elena you are
Elena estás
here Elena, wait
aquí Elena
a moment, wait a moment I am, I am
un momento un momento estoy es que estoy
thinking about the title, man, I had not
pensando el título tío que no lo había
thought about it yet, the thumbnail like this but the
pensado todavía la miniatura así pero el
title, don't give me a second
título no dame un segundo
that this man is projecting, he
que está está proyectando esta señor
is saying it backwards, I mean, as if
está diciéndole al revés o sea como si
the clips of her insulting us
los clips de ella insultando a nosotros
were a
fuera una
fantasy, you know, as if the clicks in which
fantasía sabes como si los click que en
she insults us as if it were
los que ella nos insulta como si fuera
a fantasy  that we have created
una fantasía que nosotros hemos creado
that does not exist lady the entire internet has
que no existe señora todo internet ha
seen and you know her by your mouth
visto y se la conoce usted por la boca
that you have had with us I mean I do
que que ha tenido con nosotros
n't
O sea no
understand I don't understand the entire internet with
entiendo no entiendo todo internet con
the clowning the lies The tricks that you have
la payasada las mentiras Los trucos que
done eh what we don't see is clearly the
habéis hecho eh lo que no vemos es claro
mirror effect but anyway but
efecto espejo pero total pero es que
apart from that when you lie or when I know
aparte yo cuando se miente o cuando se
about things that are not known or that are
sobre cosas que no se saben o que se
lived in private or whatever or you
viven en privado o lo que sea o tú
have an opinion I have another one of
tienes una opinión Yo tengo otra per
course It's that this is about something public I mean it
claro Es que esto sobre algo público o
is public and there are hundreds of tweets
sea es público y hay cientos de tweet en
all over the internet with clips of this
todo internet con los clips de esta
lady saying outrageous things but outrageous outrageous things
señora diciendo barbaridades pero
however
barbaridades barbaridades sin embargo
I am still here two years waiting for them to
todavía estoy yo aquí dos años esperando
show me the beating that I have
que me enseñen el machaque que yo le he
done to this lady these Peppa people
hecho a esta señora esta gente la Peppa
to grab this one and to earn money
para trincar a esta y para ganás dinero
from this one or to take her wallet okay eh
de esta o sacarle el monedero vale eh
with super chat what she did was
con super chat lo que hizo fue
heat her head heat the Coco
calentarle el coco calentarle al Coco
so that it would be her the one who ate the
para que fuera ella la que se comiera la
lawsuit and not her How good we will see
demanda y no ella Que bueno ya veremos
but heat her heat her heat her
pero calentarla calentarla calentarla
telling her that we would get her out of
diciéndole que nosotros la a sacábamos
course and in reality  I'm sure she
claro y en realidad seguramente le
was showing her other people's TTs, I do
estaría mostrando pues TT de otra gente
n't know. I don't know what they were
no lo sé No lo sé lo que le estaban
showing her, comments from the chat of people
mostrando comentarios del chat de gente
who criticize her. And then she got carried
que la criticas Y entonces esta se vino
away and believed that she was justified in
arriba y se creía que estaba justificado
crushing us and telling us all the
machacar noos y decirnos todas las
slander that she's been telling us. What's
calumnias que nos ha estado diciendo qué
going on? Well, now you have it
es lo que pasa pues que ahora lo tienes
very easy. Loli. Now you go to court and the
muy fácil Loli Ahora vas al juzgado y el
Well, the answer to the lawsuit.
Bueno ya la contestación de la demanda
No, because the deadline has passed and you
No porque se te ha pasado el plazo y no
haven't answered, you can go to the
has contestado puedes ir a la audiencia
preliminary hearing, which I don't know what date
previa que que no sé qué fecha la
we will have. But I imagine that at the end of the
tendremos Pero me imagino que finales de
year, beginning of the next, you can go to the
año principio del otro puedes ir a la
preliminary hearing and Dec. Look, I've
audiencia previa y dic Mira es que yo he
insulted because I've received all this
insultado porque he recibido todo este
beating while I had cancer, you
machaque mientras que yo tenía cáncer tú
present that roli and you will surely win the trial.
presentas eso roli y ganas el juicio
Then do it,
seguramente entonces
do it and let everyone who
Hazlo hazlo y que todo el mundo que te
is still defending you from the
está defendiendo todavía de lo del
cancer thing see that you're
cáncer y eso pues vea que tienes la
right. Of
razón
course, in a live broadcast on November 4th,
Claro en en un directo del 4 de novi
eh? I
eh
hope that today this live broadcast is going to be
al Espero que hoy este directo va a ser
short because those who
cortito porque igual cortitos son los
are still defending you may be short. Loli,
que te están defendiendo todavía Loli
because you started dancing with  a
porque te has puesto a bailar con una
pigeon saying that you just had
paloma diciendo que te acaban de de
surgery that you just had surgery
operar que te acababan de operar por
front and back Loli short there's someone who
delante y por detrás Loli cortito hay
still believes your
que sepa creerse todavía tu
lie okay damn now you're going to know
mentira vale [__] que ahora vais saber
what you were saying to the one from Troy and you're
lo que estabais diciendo al de Troya y
going to tell me if it's short or not
me vais a decir si es cortito o no
then things arrive and I have to open
después llegan cosas y Tengo que abrir
another one depending because I want to open it when
otro según porque quiero abrirlo cuando
I have it in my hand I want to show it
lo tenga yo en mi mano quiero enseñarlo
and I want to
y quiero
open it
abrirlo
okay And it could be that it arrives after
vale Y puede ser que llegue después de
10 because the truth is that eh The
las 10 pues es la verdad es que eh El
Lord is far away and it could take a while Well at
Señor está lejos y puede tardar Pues a
10:30
las 10:30
11 hello gu sure but look from here
11 hola gu segura pero al mira dde aquí
from all my tranquility mm you look
dende toda mi tranquilidad mm se te ve
calm Loli you look
tranquila Loli se te ve
calm stop acting like a clown we
tranquila deja de hacer el payaso que
were going to see each other You already knew it You just like
nos íbamos a ver Ya lo sabías Tú igual
me mm but the difference
que yo mm pero la diferencia que hay
between you and me is that eh mine goes
entre tú y yo es que eh lo mío va
eh Through the means that have to go through it will go through the
eh Por las vías que tocan ir pores irá
blood through the
por la vía sanguíneas por las vías
nasal passages through the oral passages I don't know
nasales por las vías orales No lo sé por
why through criminal means I
qué vía penal
remind you what you told
te recuerdo lo que le has dicho al
Anne that the other one tells him he's leaving  who
Anne que el otro le dice que se va que
tells the other one that his pants are going to
le dice al otro que se va el pantalón
come take off your pants I'm going to
ven bájate el pantalón que te voy a
lick your ass good I
lamer el culito bien que te voy a dar
'm going to give it to you here pim Pam trash you are trash I don't know what trash you go around rubbing against one and the other of course Yes yes I see you I see you traveled through the criminal route Loli just shat Anne in her panties right now with the
en las bragas ahora mismo con la vía
criminal route alne just freaked out but
penal se acaba de acojonar alne pero
right now brutally I'm telling you
ahora mismo brutalmente ya te lo digo
we are thinking about dropping the lawsuit
estamos pensando en quitarte la demanda
and not putting the second one on you not with a
y no ponerte la segunda no con un
lawyer asking to see if you can go
abogado pidiendo a ver si puedes ir
even as a witness okay Mrs.
aunque sea de testigo vale Señora
Alanne Mrs. Alanne I repeat myself
alanne señora alanne vuelvo a repetir
I think
pienso
Exactly the same thing I said in that
Exactamente lo mismo que dije en ese
live broadcast you Mrs. Alne went channel
directo usted señora alne se fue canal
by channel to that night channel with
por canal al Canal ese nocturno con
malice aforethought
alevosía
to beg for help to crush you
a suplicar que la ayudaran para machacar
Mrs.
señora
Alanne Well this you have As
alanne Bueno pues esto lo tien Tan
simple as showing it in court
sencillo como mostrarlo en el juzgado
Loli
Loli
eh Look she got on here to this
eh Mira se subió aquí al Canal este
night channel I don't mean that I imagine she
nocturno no me refiero que me imagino
is referring to the flight and look she begged for
que se refiere al vuelo y mira suplicó
help to crush me
que le ayudara a machacarme
So if you have a call from
Entonces si tú tienes ahí una llamada de
Alanne on the fly where you're
de alanne al vuelo donde estás
begging to be crushed, I don't see the
suplicando que te machaquen yo no veo el
problem you have by showing up
problema que tienes tú por presentarte
in court Loli but the thing is that this
en el jugado Loli pero es que esto esta
nonsense is as simple as having
tontería es tan sencilla como haber
responded to the lawsuit at the time
respondido a la demanda en el momento
that you haven't responded to the lawsuit It
que no has contestado a la demanda Me
seems to me that I don't know who this is going to
parece que esto ya no sé a quién le
stick to I think if there are 100 200
cuela Yo creo que si hay 100 200
people in these people's chat it
personas en el chat de esta gente
's still to see what nonsense they're going to
todavía es para ver qué barbaridad van a
say and laugh and get rid of the
decir y reírse y descar ya de la cosa
surreal thing they say because it's that they haven't
surrealistas que digan porque es que no
responded to the lawsuit it's that they've
ha contestado la demanda es que se le ha
missed the deadline and they haven't responded to the
pasado el plazo y no ha contestado la
lawsuit having it since July not
demanda teniéndola desde julio no
responded to the lawsuit now what's left
contestado la demanda ahora lo que queda
is the
es la audiencia
preliminary hearing and if a trial is held because of course
previa y si se hace juicio porque Claro
if they don't show up either At the
si no se presenta tampoco Al audiencia
preliminary hearing I don't know if that trial is eh
previa yo no sé si es ese juicio eh
Because defending yourself is not defended
Porque defenderse no se defiende
then you have nothing to
entonces que no tiene nada que
contribute look at your call look at
aportar mírese usted su llamada mírese
The eh no no no Alne doesn't have to
La eh que no que no que alne no tiene
look for the call that you have to
que buscar la llamada que la tienes que
present it You Loli you present it in the
presentar Tú Loli la presentas tú en la
answer to the  demand that you have not
contestación a la demanda que no has
made and there there if it is as it says Well of
hecho y ahí ahí si es así como dice Pues
course one thing is that alne says
claro una cosa es que alne diga por
please you have to crush Loli
favor tenéis que machacar a Loli por
please I beg you Okay and another thing is
favor os lo suplico Vale y otra cosa es
that alne has gone up there to give an
que alne haya subido ahí para dar una
opinion of Go away everyone knows What a thing and
opinión de Vete tod sab Qué cosa y
you come out Loli saying that she has lowered her
salgas tú Loli diciendo que se ha bajado
pants or that she has lowered the
el pantalón o que le ha bajado el
other's pants so that he gives her that he
pantalón al otro para que le dé que se
roosa over here that she goes like a kitten in
roosa por aquí que va como una gatita en
heat over there then of course I think that
celo por allá entonces claro yo creo que
there you have it a little complicated Loli you
ahí lo tienes un poco complicado Loli
know what happens Loli that they have used you what they have
sabes qué pasa Loli qué te han usado qué
used you so that the demand is
te han usado para que la demanda te la
eaten by you and you That call you have not even
comas tú y tú Esa llamada ni ni la has
heard it you say that the demand You have not
escuchado dices que la demanda No la has
seen it but what you have not seen is the
visto pero lo que no has visto es la
call that you are mentioning But neither the
llamada que estás mencionando Pero ni la
call nor the supposed crushing and the
llamada ni el supuesto machaque y lo
worst thing is that there are still fools
peor es que todavía hay tontos
repeating over and over again that you were
repitiendo una y otra vez que a ti se te
crushed and it was justified that you
machacó y estaba justificado que tú te
opened a channel to defame the worst thing
abrieras un canal para difamar lo peor
is that to this day there are people knowing
es que a día de hoy hay gente sabiendo
that this does not exist and being  8000 clicks
que eso no existe y estando 8000 clics
that prove How things were that
que demuestran Cómo fueron las cosas que
still cheer you on more why because the
todavía te jalean más por qué porque las
lawsuits you are eating it all Now
demandas te la estás comiendo toda Ahora
when they start to eat it each one
cuando se la empiecen a comer cada uno
will go like this eh I don't know anything about Loli I don't
van a así eh Yo no sé nada de Loli Yo no
know anything about Loli See you later Loli you
sé nada de Loli Hasta luego Loli te
invented a c that's what they will tell you Loli
inventaste un cá eso te van a decir Loli
V I'm glad I know what's going to happen I've been
V alegro sé lo que va a pasar llevo
here for many years I know what's going to happen
muchos años aquí sé lo que va a pasar
calmly okay And that's it and when you
tranquilamente vale Y ya está y cuando
have
se la haya
read it let's see this it is okay possible
leído a ver este es es vale posible
possible that it went
posible que fuera por
that way and when you have read it you
ahí y cuando se lo haya leído usted
madam when it is done well it's that we don't
señora cuando se haya bueno es que no
know if you listen with your ears
sabemos si usted escucha por las orejas
or you listen with your eyes that you have
o escucha por los ojos que al no tiene
nothing to do with it or Listen or or anything or
que ver nada ni Escuchar ni ni nada o
rather c no that Loli that we have
sea c no que Loli que nosotros hemos
sued and we have filed a lawsuit
demandado y hemos presentado una demanda
for what you have said if you think you
por lo que tú has dicho si tú crees que
can justify it throw it away and defend yourself and
lo puedes justifica tira y defiéndete y
go with your ears okay alanne So yes
ve por los oídos vale alanne Así que sí
madam we will see each other wherever we have to
señora nos vemos donde nos tengamos que
see each other but with all the consequences
ver pero con todas las consecuencias
because Madam you have used to your
porque Señora usted ha utilizado a a sus
misfortunes the things that have happened
desgracias las cosas que le haya pasado
to you in  You have used your life to
a usted en su vida las ha utilizado para
come and say that I am things that
venir a decir que soy yo cosas de las
you supposedly, Mrs. Alanne,
que supuestamente usted señora alanne
say you had never spoken about on YouTube
dice que nunca había hablado en YouTube
and I with my magic ball and I
y yo con mi bola mágica e
spoke okay Alanne You find out Contreras
hablaba vale alanne Te enteras Contreras
you find out
te enteras
girl This is what he is going to say in
chica Esto va a decir en el
court This is what he is going to say in court
juzgado Esto va a decir en el juicio
this can be fixed I'm telling you it can be
esto tiene arreglo ya te lo digo tiene
fixed and it is not whitewashing the ass of a
arreglo y no es blanquear el culo de un
guy who has been convicted twice for the
tío que dos veces ha sido condenado por
same thing okay why For
lo mismo vale por qué Por
insults for insults with people with
insultos por insultos con gente con la
whom I was
que me estaba
fighting It's that I find it very
peleando Es que a mí me hace mucha
funny because he has been convicted they
gracia porque ha sido condenado
confuse the word conviction with a
confunden la palabra condena con una
sentence
pena
you know he has been convicted he has been
sabes ha sido condenado ha sido
convicted twice madam that has the
condenado dos veces señora que tiene la
same validity as if they give me a
misma validez que si me ponen una multa
traffic ticket they are asking me for a
de tráfico que me están pidiendo una
financial amount for
cuantía económica por
having violated someone's image
haber vulnerado la imagen de
madam that it is not a conviction it
alguien señora que no es una condena que
is not a crime stop talking as
no es un delito que dej de hablar como
if I were talking about a criminal
si estuviera hablando de un delincuente
of a convict madam they confuse the
de un penado señora que confunden los
terms and that it will be so many
términos y que va a ser otras tantas
but what so many If I do not have another
pero qu otras tantas Si yo no tengo más
demand what
demanda qué otra
so many I will confirm it to you I will tell you
tanta ya te lo confirmo ya te lo digo
Come on then that's it for you  says Loli
Venga pues ya está que te lo dice Loli
Although there are resources in between Ah okay okay well
Aunque hay recursos por medio Ah vale
okay if there are
vale bueno vale si hay
resources How can you be channel by
recursos Cómo podéis estar canal por
channel FJ you eh all these rabble rabble
canal FJ tú eh toda esta gentuza gentuza
because you are rabble it's not
porque sois una gentuza no
done today man seriously I mean the
es hecho hoy tío en serio o sea la
second lawsuit is a
segunda demanda se una
past surto is that you are rabble
pasada surto es que sois una gentuza
and applauding just because I know I
e aplaudiendo solo porque
think so
se yo creo que sí
eh
eh
tell me Hello Good night good night
dígame Hola Buenas noches buenas noches
What's up with who Good night with
Qué pasa con quién Buenas noches con
who I have the
quién tengo el
pleasure with orus Ah what's up the one from Twitter
gusto con orus Ah qué pasa la de Twitter
no the one from Twitter yes the one from the flight if
no la de Twitter sí la del vuelo si no
you don't mind me saying it okay Ah okay if
te importa que lo diga vale Ah vale si
you're from the flight I don't care it's your
tú eres del vuelo no me importa es tu
problem What's up How are we all
problema Qué pasa Cómo estamos todos
have a one we all have some defect
tenemos un un todos tenemos algún defeco
name no no no to m I get along with
nobre no no no a m Yo me llevo bien con
Jordi man No my life with Victoria I
Jordi hombre No mi vida con Victoria le
send you both a kiss
mando un beso a los
thanks I wanted Okay I want to
dos gracias yo quería Bueno te Quiero
congratulate you on your birthday even if it's
felicitar por tu cumpleaños aunque sea
late I congratulated you for But well
[__] te felicité por Pero bueno que
if you want to follow me eh follow me if you
si me quieres seguir eh que me sigas si
want it's been a month eh it's
quieres te ha pasado un mes eh te ha
been a month now but well I also
pasado un mes ya pero bueno también te
congratulated you live eh in  the flight I
felicité en directo eh en el vuelo Te
congratulate you When was yours Oh my God it's
felicito Cuándo fue el tuyo Ay Dios mío
going to be now eh if you want to
va a ser ahora eh que si me quieres
congratulate me on the 24th Well come on I'll
felicitar el día 24 Pues venga ya me lo
get it out of the way I congratulate you now look
quito del medio ya te felicito yo mira
almost Thank you almost like your daughter yes what a
casi Gracias casi como tu hija sí qué
joy she is Libra We are almost the
alegría es Libra Casi casi somos los
best we are very good people
mejores somos muy buenas personas los
Libras The truth of course Yes I think that your
Libra La verdad claro Sí yo creo que tu
daughter Is going to be a grown woman
hija Va a ser una mujer hecha y derecha
and a very good person What do you want me to
y y muy buena persona Qué quieres que te
tell you it's true we are very good because
diga es verdad somos muy buenos porque
we have that scale you know that e
tenemos esa balanza sabes ese
about weighing the pros and cons and
e sobre pesar los pros y los contras y
no we don't have an ugly mouth we think
no no tenemos una boca fea pensamos
Before speaking do you believe in that thing about the
Antes de hablar tú crees en en eso de
zodiac signs no I
zodiaco no yo
No I don't even understand much I see for you know it
No ni entiendo mucho veo por tú sabes lo
's normal that I know I'm a Libra But I
Es lo normal que sé que soy Libra Pero
don't understand these things about the
no entiendo de cosas de estas de las
astral charts and all that no Look don't
cartas astrales y todo eso no Mira no me
make me too nervous I want okay tell me to
pongas muy nerviosa que quiero vale dime
give all my support to the ass to Elena
darle todo mi apoyo al asne a Elena
especially to my Elenita but my to
sobre todo a mi Elenita pero mi al
lasnes that for me is a weakness that I
lasnes que para mí es una debilidad que
have
tengo
and I suffer a lot every time I hear something
y sufro mucho cada vez que escucho algo
about her mm I know that here on
sobre ella mm Yo sé que aquí en las
social networks it is very  It's hard to
redes sociales es muy difícil
understand that there are good people
e entender que hay buenas personas
because after all the blows
porque después de todos los palos que
we've taken And everything, especially you who have
nos llevamos Y todo lo sobre todo tú que
been here for so many years, I can understand that
llevas tantos años lo puedo entender que
you, as you say many times, no, you
tú como dices muchas veces no que te lo
take it on your back. Maybe the same thing happens to me, Jordi,
echas a la espalda a lo mejor a mi Jordi
no, he takes it on his
le pasa lo mismo no que se lo echa a la
back. But those of us who listen from
espalda Pero los que lo escuchamos desde
outside suffer more, you know, we suffer
fuera sufrimos más sabes lo sufrimos
as our own, so I feel
como nuestro entonces pues yo lo paso
really bad. I just want you to hear her
muy mal Solo quiero que escuchen sus
calls in flight. Let's see if
llamadas al vuelo A ver si alguna vez
she ever asked for
ella pidió
that, as the magpie says, I call her the magpie.
que eso como dice la hurraca yo la digo
No, don't insult please, no,
la hurraca no no insultes por favor no
the magpie is not. No insult. Javi,
la hurraca no es Ningún insulto Javi es
she has a dove. No, well, instead of
ella tiene una paloma No pues en vez de
Paloma for M it's one, her name is Loli, please. Well,
Paloma para M es una se lama Loli por
let's tell her. Okay, well, I
favor Bueno pues vamos a decírselo Vale
'm going to respect you because Loli, well,
pues te voy a respetar porque Loli pues
Loli, Mrs. LoL. Well, madam, what I
Loli la señora LoL Bueno señora lo que
had to do is, as you say, watch the
tenía que hacer es como dices tú Mirar
live shows, but since she's been
los los directos pero como ha sido
poisoned, poisoned for so many
envenenada envenenada desde muchísimos
months, it's going to be very difficult. Javi, I want to
meses va a ser muy difícil Javi quiero
give you all my support, let's tell you that this is
darte todo mi apoyo deciros que esto es
very long, they're processes, you know.  better
muy largo son procesos tú lo sabe mejor
than anyone and that's why I want you to
que nadie y por eso quiero que lo
explain it Sometimes I put it in
expliques Algunas veces te lo pongo en
the chat explain it because people when they
el chat explícalo porque la gente cuando
say demand or report they think it's
dice demanda o denuncia se creen que es
from today to tomorrow you know they think this
de hoy a mañana sabes se cree que esto
is reporting and that's it and tomorrow we have to
es denunciar y ya está y mañana ya hay
schedule by the way Tell Elena to
que minutar por cierto Dile a Elena que
pass you something I want her to
te pase una cosa que quiero que te lo
pass it to you privately But this private thing is worth it
pase por privado Pero esto privado vale
for you you remind her and she can
para ti tú se lo recuerdas y ella que te
pass it to you and And what I want tell me
lo pase y Y eso que quiero dime ropa
underwear or something like that
interior o algo así
noo with much secrecy dna it will be something
noo con mucho secretismo dio sera algo
strange clear I don't know no no no no no don't
raro claro No sé
take me there because I'm
no no no no no no me lleves por ahí que
really embarrassed those a I tell her the
a m me da mucha vergüenza esos a le digo
same thing and Well and what am I going to tell you about
mismo y Bueno y qué te voy a decir de
yesterday I applaud you how you treated
ayer que te aplaudo que cómo trataste a
the lady like Carmen said this
la señora yo como ha dicho Carmen esta
morning You wouldn't have
mañana No hubieras
held out it happens to you like like Jordi you
aguantado te pasa como a como a Jordi de
really have a temper when
verdad tenéis un Temple cuando llaman
certain people call Javi I
ciertas personas de verdad Javi Te
congratulate you on your change let's go I've
felicito por tu cambio vamos a mí
always liked me I say it clearly I
siempre me ha gustado lo digo claramente
can't deny it you saw whatever it
Es que no puedo negarlo tu visteis lo
was with the flight I was on the
que fuera con el vuelo yo estaba en el
flight but I can't
vuelo pero yo no
feel what I feel You know that I
puedo sentir lo que siento Sabes que me
like a person neither I have nor
guste una persona tampoco ni te he
insulted you nor can nor will anyone ever have
insultado ni puedo ni jamás me habrá
seen me write in anyone's chat
visto nadie escribir en el chat de nadie
about you or anyone else I mean I
de ti ni de ninguno O sea me refiero en
was on the flight and that's it but what
el vuelo estaba y punto pero no que
can they get out of me they wanted to
pueden sacar de mí quisieron
hurt me by putting a tweet that I had
hacerme daño poniéndote un tweet que yo
put up with a sign about the flight
había puesto con un cartel del vuelo
but that's the most they can get out of
pero eso es lo máximo que pueden sacar
me two signs that I've put up about
míos dos carteles que haya puesto sobre
you but nothing in the chat or anything but I don't care what I've been
ti pero ni algo en el chat ni nada pero
going through is that I
que me da igual que llevo que es que
understand a lot about adne Javi I
entiendo muchísimo a adne Javi la
understand her a lot because what she's been going through
entiendo mucho porque lo que ella lleva
without telling you half of the
pasando sin contarte la mitad de las
things I've been going through but well I
cosas lo llevo pasando yo pero bueno que
didn't come here to talk about myself I
no he venido a hablar de mí que he
came here to give you my my my support and and I
venido a darte mi mi mi apoyo y y esta
also dedicate this call to you just to go crazy RG
llamada se la dedico también a pirar RG
one day she wanted me to call but I
que un día quería que llamara pero yo
was a little nervous and I told her I'll
estaba un poquito nerviosa y le dije ya
call and today I think it's been the
llamaré y hoy creo que ha sido el
time to call you animated ar it's really
momento de de llamarte animado ar está
up yes
bien arriba sí
Yes because I
Sí porque
want to because I really want to
quiero porque quiero de verdad
show you in public that you can
demostraros en en público que que
count on me for whatever you need
contéis conmigo para lo que necesitéis
both Elena and you as well  lasne Carmen
tanto Elena como tú como al lasne Carmen
from teleindiscreta And by the way FJ who
de teleindiscreta Y por cierto FJ que
said today that he has reported him in
hoy ha dicho que le ha denunciado en
those clicks that you are going to put also
esos clics que vas a poner también lo
says that he has reported FJ I just want to
dice que ha denunciado FJ Yo solo quiero
tell you the same thing that I put in the
deciros lo mismo que he puesto en el
tweet that only justice will stop her
tweet que solamente la parará la
the LoL has said that he has reported FJ
la LoL ha dicho que ha denunciado al FJ
yes he has reported FJ are you going to put it
sí que ha denunciado a FJ lo vas a poner
in those if he has to present
en esos si se tiene que presentar los
his trials first That at the moment he has not
juicios suyos primero Que de momento no
presented himself neither in mine nor in
se ha presentado ni en la mía ni en la
Johana's still in the appointment already but but
de Johana todavía en la cita ya pero
but
pero pero
Javi they play with that they continue to
Javi ellos juegan con eso ellos siguen
play with that then they say is that Javi
jugando con eso luego dicen es que Javi
talks about let's see that you can
habla de vamos a ver que tú puedes
speak even if you have reported them
hablar aunque los tengas denunciados
because you have always said it, they are not the
porque siempre lo has dicho ni son los
same terms of course, much less the
mismos términos claro ni mucho menos
same as on the flight that they put something on
igual que en el vuelo que pongan algo en
the flight some kind of insult some what
el vuelo algún tipo de insulto alguna lo
what above all my wasi brand that you already
quei sobre todo mi marca wasi que ya la
know it, well, it has exposed its lies
conocéis pues ha expuesto sus mentiras
but we have not insulted nor have we let's go
pero ni hemos insultado ni hemos vamos
the terms that
los términos que nos
they refer to us towards us I have
nos refieren ellos hacia nosotros Yo he
been exposed Javi they have said where I
sido expuesta Javi a mí han dicho dónde
live in those in those
vivo en esos en esos
channels they go saying where  I live in the
canales van diciendo dónde vivo en los
chats because you can read barbarities that
chat pues puedes leer barbaridades que
I don't even
ni me
expose in x What happens is that since I
las expongo en x Lo que pasa que desde
said it the other day on the flight Javi
que lo dije el otro día en el vuelo Javi
when one day he said the pppa Beltrn
cuando un día dijo la pppa Beltrán
Javier Oliveira the T who put the
Javier oliveira el T que ha puesto el
coman of this my lawyer
coman de lo de la esto mi abogado me ha
told me that it is viogen that day I said up to
dicho que es viogen ese día dije hasta
here that was I don't even know what he talks about the
aquí eso fue no sa ni lo que habla la
gravity that things have that c but in
gravedad que tien las cosas quec pero en
that I mean that like a you know and I
ese me refiero que ese como un sabes y
said can I need to expose these things
dije pued necesito exponer estas cosas
in x I no I can't remain silent in the face of so
en x yo no no puedo callarme ante
many lies so much damage
tanta tantas mentiras tanto daño un daño
gratuitous damage that I really if you don't
gratuito que yo de verdad si no te
mind I have asked
importa yo se lo he preguntado a
Victoria a thousand times privately But I
Victoria mil veces por privado Pero te
want to ask you too you
lo quiero preguntar también a ti tú lo
understand That hatred let's see eh In the case
entiendes Ese odio a ver eh En el caso
of ladies like this I think it is a
de señoras como esta Yo creo que es
lack of lack of education I say this with
falta de falta de educación lo digo con
all due respect in the world eh I mean not all
todo respeto del mundo eh o sea no todas
people who do not have education that have
las personas que no tengan educación que
not been able to have eh study come on no no
no hayan podido tener eh estudi vamos no
when in education we refer
no cuando en la educación nos referimos
not only to study subjects it can be
no solamente temas de estudio puede ser
education that they can give you very well at
educación que te pueden dar muy bien en
home And this lady has lacked
casa Y a esta señora le ha faltado
obviously the way to behave
evidentemente la forma de comportarse
with society is not to have education
con la sociedad no es de tener educación
and apart from the lack of education is that you
y aparte de la falta de educación es que
live a little for me in the worlds of
vive un un poco para mí en los mundos de
Yupi ignorance also of not knowing
Yupi ignorancia también de no saber
where the line is and then yes yes to
dónde está la línea y entonces si si a
that you mix it with
eso lo mezclas con
and one thing is to have money and another thing
e una cosa es tener dinero y otra cosa
is to have class you know So I class
es tener clase sabes Entonces yo clase
I think that we should not discuss it no that he does
Yo creo que no hay que discutirlo no que
not have it and and the issue of money I do not know
no lo tiene y y tema de dinero yo no sé
if he ever has it on some occasion the
si la llega a tener en alguna ocasión la
truth is there are times that I think that he does have it
verdad hay veces que pienso que sí lo
and there are other times that I think that he does
tiene Y hay otras veces que pienso que
not but anyway he would have it or he would not
no pero de todas maneras lo tuviera o no
be a person who does not know how to have it
sería una persona que no sabe tenerlo
because
porque
but I am not referring only to
pero yo no me refiero ya solamente a
this lady I mean Well you
esta señora me refiero a Bueno tú lo
said it very recently they have like a
dijiste hace muy poco tienen como un
false ego you know they need to move
falso ego sabes que necesitan seguir
forward as you see hatred of
hacia delante como ves odio de de
people in x towards the flight or towards
personas en en x hacia el vuelo o hacia
you that I do not understand, I mean I what I
ti que yo no lo entiendo o sea yo lo lo
have blocked them of course eh
yo las tengo bloqueadas por supuesto eh
me what happens is that some of them do not have me
yo lo que pasa que algunas no me tienen
blocked and you click on them and you see what they
bloqueadas y tú les das al ver y ves lo
write to you and you say why I mean why do
que te escriben Y dices por qué O sea
you leave a place well  see you
por qué tú te vas de un sitio pues hasta
later no I mean there's no need to insult
luego no O sea no hace falta ni insultar
or say hate you can't comment
ni decir un odio no puedes comentar
negative things you can criticize but of
cosas negativas puedes criticar pero
course they do it with a with a
claro es que lo hacen con un con un
clear or what the [ __ ] have I done to you Of course you
claro oa que tu [__] que te he hecho
look yesterday you look clear I mean
Claro tú fíjate ayer tú fij claro o sea
you can say well Hey I didn't
tú puedes decir pues Oye a mí no me ha
like it today jav I found it very
gustado hoy jav me ha parecido muy
boring to give you an example not to
aburrido por ponerte un ejemplo no para
not put it now You're welcome or say yesterday on
no ponerme ahora De nada o decir ayer en
the flight Well the flight What
el vuelo Pues el vuelo Qué música más
ugly music they had yesterday or how bad it was Jordi
fea tuvo ayer o qué mal estuvo Jordi
okay or Victoria It seems great to me but
vale o Victoria Me parece muy bien pero
one day no but Day after day from
un día no pero Día tras día desde por la
morning to night with
mañana hasta por la noche con cuentas de
hate accounts how did they put you on
odio cóm a ti te llegaron a poner en
instagram that they were going to shoot you I
instagram que te iban a dar un tiro O
mean look at what it gets to is that you
sea fijaros a lo que se llega es que
say you have with a lady of course to m to
dices tú tengo con una señora claro a m
me That a lady comes up here and
a a mí Que suba aquí una señora y me
calls me a clown is the least that is dispatched you
diga payaso es lo mínimo que se despacha
know to me that a lady comes up here
sabes a mí que que que suba aquí una
and starts yelling at me one night
señora y se ponga a gritarme una noche
permalink but look at her level
per fíjate pero fíjate su nivel
Forgive me Ha you look at her  level you
Perdóname Ja tú fíjate a su nivel tú
only said clo the level the level
solamente dijiste clo el nivel el nivel
is the level that they can they can see There ca
es el nivel que pueden que pueden a ver
n't be any other way for there to be
No puede haber otro modo de que haya
people who watch those channels and
gente que que vea esos canales y que
support those channels There can't be other
apoye a esos canales No puede haber otra
people who aren't like the ones who upload to the
gente que no sea como la que sub a el
youtuber the one who is the youtuber
youtuber el que lo es que es el youtuber
who makes that hate happen to the
el que hace que ese odio se haga a las
people who watch him there we saw
personas que le ven allí vimos el nivel
the lady's level didn't go up looking insulting
de la señora no subió mirando insultando
cursing at everything and then it turns out to be
cagándose en todo y luego resulta ser
when she shuts up and lets me tell her
cuando ya se calla y me deja decirle
but lady yes what you
pero señora que sí que está muy bien lo
're saying is very good but what is it that
que ú estás diciendo pero que es que
these people have invented a cancer Yes
esta gente se han inventado un cáncer Sí
but who says that lady who
pero eso quién lo dice señora que lo
says it Loli says Antonio I haven't
dice Loli lo dice Antonio eso no lo he
seen that of course then you
visto yo claro entonces ahí te das
realize Of course What are we
cuenta de Claro Con qué estamos
debating you know exactly there can't be
debatiendo sabes exacto no puede haber
other people who support this group of
otra gente que apoye este grupo de
channels because there are no more it has to be
canales porque es que no hay más tiene
that way But you look but that's why I
que ser así Pero tú fíjate pero por eso
want to tell you look for two
te quiero decir tú fíjate por dos
insults Well I already said it on the flight a
insultos Bueno yo ya lo dije en el vuelo
long time ago and I dedicated it to
hace mucho tiempo y te lo dediqué hacia
you because one day before  Christmas
ti porque un día antes de navidades
you said one day because one of
dijiste un día porque te llamó uno de
them called you called you an idiot or something like that And you
ellos te llamó idiota o algo así Y tú
said That's the level and I said it's hours it's
dijiste Ese es el nivel y dije son horas
hours you really should look
son horas tú de verdad deberías de mirar
I know you have a lot of work but you
Yo sé que tienes mucho trabajo pero
should look back many months ago it
deberías de mirar muchísimos meses atrás
's hours offending me
son horas ofendiéndome
of your work
de tu trabajo de ti
you despise yourself and as brave you know
despreciáis e como valiente sabes
in front of a microphone brave you know and
delante de un micro valiente sabes y
then many put them for private
luego muchos los ponen para privados
others have
otros los han
hidden them why aren't they so
ocultado que por qué no son tan
brave they insult everyone at
valientes insultan a a troche moche a
every turn well be brave stop stop and then confront yourself don't hide it eh Don't go against the communities they have exposed everyone really Javi they have exposed thugs to flyers in a thousand ways you despise let's see I know I know what we see here what we see here in what what I
vemos aquí lo que vemos aquí en lo que
know for example other things I don't
lo que sé yo ya por ejemplo otr cosas no
know Yesterday he mentioned to me if I fall asleep
sé Ayer me mencionó al si lo s me duermo
this one that I didn't even know that he continued
este que yo no sabía ni que seguía
making YouTube videos and if
haciendo vídeos de YouTube y si está
the man is awake or
despierto el hombre o
not Yeah that's the one who has allowed himself
no s ese ese es el que se ha permitido
that's the one who has allowed himself and Sorry
ese es el que se ha permitido y Perdona
if I use  your channel but I'm going to say it like that
que utilice tu canal pero lo voy a decir
threaten me twice where I live that one has
así amenazarme dos veces donde vivo ese
allowed that Look It's that you know
se ha permitido eso Mira Es que sabes
what happens that I'm not saying this as
qué pasa que que esto no lo digo yo como
arrogant or anything, I mean this is
sobrada ni como nada o sea esto es que
literally you guys search on
literalmente ustedes buscáis en el
YouTube you put Javi Oliveira and you put
YouTube ponéis Javi oliveira y ponéis
sort by upload date not so that you
ordenar por fecha de subida no para que
get out of the last hour
salgas de lo lo de la última hora
first and it goes day and every day well
primero y vaya pasando día y cada día
if not there
pues si no
are 10 15 channels that upload a video
son 10 15 canales los que suben un vídeo
about me every day of course and it makes me
sobre mí cada día claro y a mí me hace
Thank you very much because they talk like
Muchas gracias porque ellos hablan como
talking to me like I'm
hablando conmigo como que yo lo estoy
watching it and it's like Of course you imagine one
viendo y es como Claro tú imagínate una
or three hours the other 2 hours the other one the other one a
o tres horas el otro 2 horas el otro cu
15 minute video
el otro el otro un vídeo de 15 minutos
the other 20 I don't see it I'm
el otro 20 yo no lo veo yo estoy
carrying on three channels no and
llevando para adante tres canales no y
the accounts that you have of enx against you they
las cuentas que tienes de enx contra ti
all really believe that you are
todo se creen de verdad que estás
attentive to everything I mean as if you don't
pendiente a todo o sea como si tú no
have a life You know You know what happens they
tuvieras vida Sabes Tú sabes lo que pasa
treat you and the same thing happens to me Jordi
que te tratan y a mi Jordi le pasa igual
eh It's not to bring it up But it's
eh No es por traerlo a colación Pero es
true they think they are that you are
verdad se creen que están que estáis
attentive to everything and it's not impossible no, they don't
atentos a todo y no imposible no no
understand that you do have a
entienden que vosotros sí tenéis una
life beyond YouTube apart from
vida más allá de YouTube aparte de
your families you have your other
vuestras familias tú tienes tus otros
channels the content of the three channels
canales el contenido de los tres canales
reflects that there is no exact kiss time
refleja que no hay tiempo de beso exact
if you see any if you see any
si tú ves cualquier si tú ves cualquier
video for example from the main Channel you
vídeo por ejemplo del Canal principal tú
see that there are a few hours that are not
ves que ahí hay unas horas que no son en
live and they are obviously not watching a
directo y no son viendo evidentemente un
Peppa video you know Oh well you had
vídeo de la Peppa sabes Ah bueno tenías
Look I'm going to tell you the last one since the
Mira te voy a contar la última ya que
good thing is that I haven't been able to put it
eso bueno es que no lo he podido poner
on x the other day the day before yesterday they gave her
en x el otro día antes de ayer la dieron
a bizum of 100 and she says thank you very much
un bizum de 100 y dice gracias graas
because this is what it is for the work that I
porque esto es lo que es por el trabajo
do Look I couldn't stop laughing I
que hago Mira yo no podía parar de reí
say but what a job but what a job
digo pero qué trabajo pero qué trabajo
if you have sat down it was the day that she exposed
si te has sentado fue el día que expuso
all your haters you know they were
a todos tus odiadores sabes le iban
sending her the videos and she was
mandando los vídeos y ella lo iba
putting it up and she says what she does sit down
poniendo y dice ella lo que hace sentar
she assumed that her function on YouTube
ella asumido que su función en YouTube
the way that she is going to have sa cape is Javi has
la forma que va a tener sa capa es Javi
not been for good or is it going to be for
no ha sido por las buenas o va a ser por
bad I am very sorry
las malas yo yo lo siento mucho de
really because I know that on the flight they
verdad porque sé que en el vuelo te
warned you I already  I knew what she was like
advirtieron yo ya sabía cómo era ella
okay but everyone has to make
vale pero cada uno se tiene que
mistakes alone too and I also
equivocar solo también y también te
understand you eh that it's your business that's
entiendo a ti eh que es tu negocio que
your job that you took her I
es tu trabajo que tú la llevase a ella o
mean me with the other youtuber I remember I
sea yo con el otro youtuber me acuerdo
saw that this girl comes from
Yo que veíamos que esta tía viene de
Big Brother you can see the feather duster you know she
gran hermano se ve el plumero sabes
comes from this you can see that she's
viene de esto se le ve que está
trying to interact with us to
intentando interaccionar con nosotros
do here but well one thing to
para hasar aquí pero bueno una cosa a la
another yes it's true that she brought me two
otra sí que es verdad que me trajo a dos
or three from Big Brother I think it was she didn't
o tres de Gran hermanos creo que fue no
bring me interviews then when I when I
me trajo entrevis luego cuando yo cuando
chatted with her I threw her away and what that Well we
yo la char la tir de ella y qui que Bien
also went to the ones from cad and she accompanied me she had I
fuimos también a los de cad y me
'm an idiot I can't I'm not
tuvo yo soy [__] no te pued no te
going to give you another explanation No no don't say
voy dar otra explicación No no no digas
that don't say that because you looked out for
eso no digas eso porque tú miraste por
your business that's what you have to do
tu negocio que es lo que tienes que
you thought that I was going to bring you
hacer tú te creíste que te iba a llevar
more people and that's it and you do very well but
más gente y punto y haces muy bien pero
if it's normal This is your job
si es que es normal Este es tu trabajo
That's what I don't understand I don't I wasn't
Eso es lo que no entiendo yo no me yo no
going to fight with her or anything because it was
me iba a pelear con ella ni nada porque
clear that she's a person who  Ia you
se veía leua que es una persona que te
know she's got it in for me and what I
la lía sabes que se la trae y yo lo que
did was and apart from this there's click
hice fue y aparte de esto hay click
even from her saying it Day after day it
incluso de ella diciéndolo Día tras día
's that my Javi is not a tomboy ask
es que mi Javi no machona preguntarle a
you Why doesn't he mention me because
usted Por qué no me menciona porque yo
what I did was I didn't stop following her
lo que hice fue yo ni la dejé de seguir
or blocking her or anything I just
ni la bloqueé ni nada yo simplemente
stopped counting on her and I had her there by my
dejé de contar con ella y y la tenía ahí
side but without fighting You know why she's
al lado pero sin pelearme Sabes porque
the typical one who messes things up with you And well that
de la típica que te la lía Y bueno pues
's how I didn't give it to her like I didn't notice her I didn't notice
así fue como ya yo no le daba como no le
her I didn't notice her
echaba cuenta no le echaba cuenta no le
well she stopped saying eh It's
echaba cuenta pues ya pasó de decir eh
not that Javi doesn't mention me no no
No es que a mi Javi no me menciona no no
Javi has never said anything to me he hasn't
a mi Javi nunca me ha dicho nada no me
done anything to me but he doesn't mention me
ha hecho nada pero no me menciona
ask you guys all of a sudden
preguntarle a ustedes a de repente Ya
Start with him he's a cheapskate I don't know what Of
empezar con el es un pesetero no sé qué
course because his mission was to get
Claro porque ya su misión era calentarla
Loli hot and getting Loli hot
a la Loli y calentar a la Loli
meant two things like insulting us a
significaba dos cosas que nos insultara
lot and for her to turn the
saco sí y que ella transformara el el
heat on into a superchat because I don't know
calentón en superchat porque no sé por
why Loli turned the fight with
qué Loli transformaba la pelea con
us into giving superchats to people in
nosotros en darle superchat a gente de
fact she
hecho ella
assumed she was  that giving money to Peppa
e asumía que e darle dinero a a Peppa
was like attacking me that There was a long
era e atacarme a mí eso Hubo mucho
time that he assumed that giving
tiempo que lo asumió que que darle
money you know these channels was like
dinero sabes a estos canal era como
attacking him he continues to assume it Javi
atacar lo sigue lo sigue asumiendo Javi
continues to assume it she has it stuck
lo sigue asumiendo ella lo tiene metido
like injected she has it stuck You know
como inyectado lo tiene metido Sabes
why she said it again in this that
porque lo ha vuelto a decir en este que
I in that clip for example I have not
que yo en ese clip por ejemplo no lo he
put it but she said it again yes I
puesto pero lo volvió a decir sí yo yo
passed it to Elenita I have the director
le pasé a Elenita yo tengo el director
but it happens to me Like Elenita I don't know how to
pero yo me pasa Como Elenita yo no sé
download it So I recorded it
descargármelo Entonces yo me lo grabé de
10 minutes at a time 10 minutes you know then she
10 minutos en 10 minutos sabes luego lo
deleted it eh I mean she removed it I don't know why I have to
borró eh o sea lo quitó no sé por
check why she
tengo que comprobar por porque ha
removed the chat in the chat right Hey
quitado el chat en el chat enta Oye
Isabel I'm going to continue I'm going to keep giving this a
Isabel voy a segir voy a seguir dándole
hard time if it's not worth my life because if
caña esto si no vale mi vida porque si
not I'll get involved here because I'm very happy Thank you
no me enrollo aquí que me alegro mucho
very much thank you very much really and
gracias muchísimas gracias de verdad y
a kiss to the whole chat Elenita I love you
un beso a todo el chat Elenita Te quiero
a lot my life and you know it a kiss really
un montón vida mía y lo sabes un beso re
transcends Elenita has a Javi
ella traspasa Elenita tiene un Javi
Elenita has a look and a voice
Elenita tiene una mirada y una voz que
that transcends the  good person who is it
que traspasa lo buena persona que es lo
transfers it thanks thank you very much Pili that I have
traspasa gracias muchas gracias Pili que
fulfilled what I told you eh that I
te he cumplido con lo que te dije eh que
have called Thank you Javi a kiss a
me he llamado Gracias Javi un beso un
big kiss from me what good people are people
fuerte mío qué buena gente son la gente
What good people you all are
Qué buena gente sois todos
eh What good people you all are
eh Qué buena gente sois todos
not what is moving let's see this what
no queé esta moviendo vamos a ver esto
is it that says I want to see what about
qué es lo que dice que quiero ver lo de
Troy we open it directly when I have it
de Troya abrimos directo cuando la tenga
and if not tomorrow okay open it
y si no mañana vale abierto ya el
live now So when I have it when
directo Entonces cuando la tenga cuando
when I have it I'm going to talk but in the
cuando la tenga voy a hablar yo pero al
end when I have it we open it directly he
final cuando la tenga abrimos directo lo
opens it now or he doesn't open it if it arrives
abre ya o o no lo abre si llega
too late tomorrow or I'm not on
demasiado tarde mañana o no estoy en
screen
pantalla
and we really know the second person
y de verdad sabemos la segunda persona
the second person says it the lawyer is
la segunda persona la dice el abogado se
called Teresa I don't know
llama Teresa no sé
what supposedly I think that I don't know if I should
qué supuestamente creo eso ya no sé si
say it I think she's tough but I have no
decirlo creo que es tesa pero no tengo
[ __ ] idea I can't confirm it okay
ni [__] idea no lo puedo confirmar vale
the lawyer in that video and it's there since we're
el abogado en ese vídeo y está ahí
not going to see it Nor
puesto que no lo vamos a ver Tampoco
because we're going to see it together with when
porque lo vamos a ver junto con cuando
I have my things eh Because when I
yo tenga mis cosas eh Porque cuando yo
have my things then I know what I
tenga mis cosas entonces sa lo que ya
can already put but well that's what I was going for that's that it's
puedo poner pero bueno eso es que iba
only we've seen everything we haven't
eso es que está solo hemos visto todo no
seen the video where he calls me
hemos visto el vídeo donde me llama
lawyer, well that's what the lawyer says there,
abogado pues ahí es que ahí lo dice el
the lawyer, it says there, ma'am. So
abogado el abogado lo dice ahí señora
I found out the other day,
Entonces que me enteré el otro día
just the other day they sent me a
justamente el otro día me mandaron un
message, it said, pum. Sorry, Rosa, r,
mensaje dici pum Perdón Rosa r
meaning s s. Yes, yes, even I have to,
significando s s Sí si incluso yo tengo
it's like I've been seeing everything, if it
que es que como lo estado viendo todo si
's s that guy. Hello, guy, 85. Yes, yes, I believe,
es s esa pana Hola pana 85 Sí sí creo
like
como dice
Teresa says, what they sent me, they tell me it's
Teresa lo que me han mandado me dicen
Tesa, but since I don't have
que es tesa pero como yo no tengo
100%, I can't solar it, I can't
100% no lo puedo solar no lo puedo
confirm it. They say they haven't told me. Well, whatever,
confirmar dicen no me han dicho pues
Tesa, daughter, well, I
anda que como sea tesa hija pues te
have the folder. Well, whatever,
tengo la carpet Pues anda que como sea
Tesa, Tesa, what are you going to do? You're going to
tesa tesa qué te vas a hacer te vas a
join the fourth, the fifth, the sixth, the
unir a la cuarta a la quinta la sexa la
seventh. If you're a pack of cowards,
séptima si sois una manada de cobardes
if you need three, what what? Okay, what's Tesa going to
si necesitáis tres qué qué Va qué va a
do? She's going to join the heat cat.
hacer tesa se va a unir a la gata del
Someone
alguien me
explain to me what she said, I think she
explica ha dicho lo que creo que ha
said, fifth, the sixth, the seventh. If you're
dicho quinta la sexta la séptima si sois
a pack of cowards, if you need
una manada de cobardes si necesitáis
three, what what? Tesa is going to do? She's going to
tres qué qué va a hacer tesa se va a
join  the cat in heat to the cat that
unir a la gata en celo a la gata que se
left alberdo menec and alberd menec being
fue alberdo menec y alberd menec siendo
Who is there was a live messing with
Quién es había un directo metiéndose con
our channels just because the lady
nuestros canales solo porque las señora
had gone to eat the car and
le había ido a comer el carro y está
the thing is guaranteed because look how he's
garantizado el asunto porque mira como
back doing mu mu mu where did he
ya ha vuelto a hacer mu que mu que dónde
put me that he let me eat the car that my
me metio que me dejó comer el carro que
pinp was seen and and and and I being
se me ha vió la pinp y y y y yo siendo
Who is Ah I am I have commented on
Quién es Ah estoy estoy he comentado
this This is not normal
esto Esto no es normal
eh al la yes you are that's what you did you left
eh al la sí eres eso hiciste te fuiste
on the fly and that's what I meant I didn't
al vuelo y a eso me refería no me
mean you went throwing yourself at
refería que te fueras tirando a todo el
everyone you have I already after what
mundo tenéis yo ya después de lo que
Javier oliveira has posted
Javier oliveira ha puesto en los últimos
lately about a lady I think that you
tiempos sobre una señora yo creo que ya
have something here inside that of what
es que tenéis algo aquí dentro que de lo
are issues issue that you see everything out
que son temas tema que todo lo veis por
there eh that your life is governed only by
ahí eh que vuestra vida se rige solo con
that
eso
okay it is governed solely and exclusively only
vale se rige única y exclusivamente solo
by that
con eso
but not to Anne no it's not worth it I have that
pero no al Anne no no te vale tengo ese
live where they talk about the of mine
directo donde se habla de la de del mío
of mine to Anne and where you are
de los míos al Anne y donde tú estás
laughing and applauding Anne and
riéndote y aplaudiendo al Anne y de
where  I mean mine not any of yours
donde me refiero al mío no a nadie tuyo
eh that you wanted to take out for a walk
eh que hayas querido sacar a pasear
because every time
porque a vosotros cada vez que se os
something is said to you, yes, you have an ingrown toenail, you take it
dice algo si si tenéis un uñero Lo
out
sacáis
eh What you are accusing others of,
eh De eso que estáis acusando los demás
you every time you have it I don't
vosotros cada vez que tenéis Es que no
even understand what he is explaining, if he
entiendo ni lo que está explicando si es
is trying to, if he is trying to
que está queriendo si está intentando
explain something I really don't understand it, I'm
explicar algo No lo entiendo de verdad
not saying it in an offensive way or anything like that
no lo digo de manera ofensiva ni nada
eh but I
por el estilo eh pero es que no lo
really don't understand it eh No, it's not
entiendo de verdad eh No no es de manera
offensive or anything like that but it's that no, I do
ofensiva ni mucho menos pero es que no
n't understand what he is saying, what he is
no no entiendo lo que está diciendo lo
trying to
que está queriendo
explain, well here it comes, there is
explicar bueno aquí viene hay por aquí
a statement here in which he practically states that he is
una afirmación en la que prácticamente
not going to go, that the trial is not going to be
afirma que no va ir que no se va a
presented Look, FJ put a tweet that gave that I
presentar juicio Mira FJ puso un tweet
understand that it is a joke
que daba que entiendo que es de broma
because you obviously can't go to the trial,
porque al juicio no se puede ir
okay, the trial No, it's not a
evidentemente vale el juicio No no es un
theater, okay, It's not a summer cinema you ca
teatro vale No es un cine de verano al
n't go to the trial then FJ put
juicio no se puede ir entonces FJ puso
a t as if to say Oh yes, I am going to go to the
un t como diciendo Oh yo sí que voy a ir
trial to see it I don't know which one no And
al juicio a verlo No sé cuá no Y
then Loli answers
entonces Loli responde
This yes, yes, yes, even I have to, it's
Esto sí sí sí si incluso yo tengo que es
that  as I've been seeing everything if it is
que como lo he estado viendo todo si es
yes it is tesa viciana Hello viciana
sí es tesa viciana Hola viciana
85 Yes yes eh I believe as Teresa says
85 Sí sí eh creo como dice Teresa
in what they have sent me they tell me that it
en en lo que me han mandado me dicen que
is tesa but since I don't have it
es tesa pero como yo no lo tengo
100% I can't solar it I can't
100% no lo puedo solar no lo puedo
confirm it it is very cautious the woman is
confirmar es es muy prudente la mujer es
very cautious the woman This is not
muy prudente la mujer Esto no es
the woman is very cautious and until she is
la mujer es muy prudente y hasta que no
sure of things she will not let it go let them
esté segura de las cosas no lo suelta
sue you know well the
vayase que la demanden sabes bueno lo de
AR of Troy this is tremendous look at it
AR de Troya esto es tremendo miradlo
well This is the FJ Wait he says I'm
bueno Esto es lo del FJ Espera que dice
not going to Ah I don't know what but I'm going
no voy a ir a Ah no sé qué per voy a ir
to Corua LFJ the
a Coruña lfj el niño
traitorous child But clown you know that I'm going to
traidor Pero payasete tú sabes que voy a
go or I or
ir yo o y o
what you know that I'm going to go
qué sabes que voy a ir
But clown you know that I'm going to go or I or
Pero payasete tú sabes que voy a ir yo o
what But you You have it with a guarantee
qué Pero tú Tú lo tienes con garantía
what does it say that it's not going let's go that it's not going that
qué dice que no vaí vamos que no vaí lo
of Troy You're going to freak out okay attentive Oh
del Troya Vais a flipar vale atentos Oh
a magnifying glass Javier Oliveira Look this is a
una lupa Javier oliveira Mira esto es un
review that the head knee is going to give me
repaso que el cabez rodilla me va a dar
okay this is a  I review that the head
vale esto es un repaso que el cabez
knee is going to hit me in the mouth
rodilla me va a dar en toda la boca
he said something that he shouldn't have I
ha contado una cosa que no debería me
've been laughing since yesterday when I saw it I
estoy riendo desde ayer que lo vi me
'm laughing at this
estoy riendo de este
tweet maybe I'm laughing in a stupid way
tweet a lo mejor me río de manera tonta
because I am ignorant and I
porque yo soy un ignorante y de leyes no
know nothing about laws but in the time that I was with
sé nada pero en el tiempo que estuve con
someone who did handle the laws and in
alguien que sí manejaba las leyes y de
fact continues to make a living from it
hecho se sigue ganando la vida en ello
listening to reciting
escuchando recitar
uh laws out loud learning them
eh leyes en voz alta aprendiendo las
for
para los
exams and later when he started
exámenes y posteriormente cuando se puso
working in the part when you
a trabajar en la parte de
finish law or you are a
cuando terminas derecho o eres
solicitor or you are a lawyer well he stayed
procurador o eres abogado bueno se quedó
in the part when you finish law or you
en la parte cuando terminas derecho o
are a solicitor or you are a lawyer okay You can't
eres procurador o eres abogado vale No
be a teacher you can't be a judge you can't be a
puedes ser profesor no puede ser juez no
prosecutor you can't
puede ser fiscal no puede
be an administrator okay I mean either you are a
ser administrativo vale o sea o eres
solicitor or you are a
procurador o eres
lawyer or you have this face that you look like
abogado o tienes esta cara que pareces
the egg that is hanging here from the
el huevo que está aquí colgado de
Attorney General's Office eh you ca
Procuraduría eh
n't judge a person
no se puede juzgar a una persona dos
twice for the same crime Javier
veces por el mismo delito Javier
Oliveira Well more than not being able to
oliveira Bueno más que más que no poder
judge the person for the same crime
juzgar a la persona por el mismo delito
twice of course for the same crime I
dos veces claro por el mismo delito Yo
understand that if you understand me I mean what you ca
entiendo que sí me entiendes o sea lo
n't judge the person is
que no se puede juzgar a la persona es
twice  for the same fact the res
dos veces por el mismo hecho la cosa
judicata Okay, you can't just
juzgada Vale no puede [__] y volver a
sue a person again for something that has already
demandar a una persona por algo que ya
been
ha sido
judged, that HM
juzgado eso HM
if what you're saying here
si es verdad lo que está diciendo aquí
about Troy is true, it's true okay, what you're
de Troya es verdad vale lo que está
saying here about Troy is exactly like that if they
diciendo aquí de Troya es tal cual si a
report you once for stealing this
ti te denuncian una vez por robar este
remote and you lose the trial, you can't
mando y pierdes el juicio no puedes
report them again for the same thing to
volver a denunciarte por lo mismo para
see if it turns out better the second time
ver si en la segunda ocasión sale mejor
okay If you don't believe me, go to Google and put it, yes, we
vale Si no me crees Vete a Google y Pon
can, we believe you, we believe the one from
se puede te creemos te creemos al de
Troy, there's no need to see it on
Troya no hace falta que lo veamos en
Google twice, the
Google dos veces
same person for the same crime and they're
a la misma persona por el mismo delito y
going to tell you no and you'll get a series of
te van a decir no y te sale una serie de
articles that will explain why the
artículos que te van a explicar por qué
same person can't be judged
no se puede juzgar a una misma persona
for the same
por el mismo
crime
delito
So if there's
Entonces si tiene
something, I'm sorry, but these people are good. They are, they are what they are. They are what they are. They are what they are. They are what they
algo Lo siento pero esta gente son bueno
are. They don't give any more, let's
que son son lo que son no dan para más
go but we're going to laugh a lot, I
damos para pero vamos a reí un montón yo
don't give any more, we don't give any more, we don't give any more
no damos
so that the
no damos para más no damos para que la
lawsuit is true, I hope it's
demanda sea cierta espero que sea
true and I hope that other lawsuit from
cierta y espero que esa otra demanda de
someone who challenged him because later we're
alguien que lo retaba porque luego lo
going to hear it be for  me and that it
vamos a escuchar que sea para mí y que
also reaches me that you don't
también me llegue que a ti no te llega
even have blood reaching your brain what lawsuit am I
ni la sangre al cerebro qué demanda te
going to file against you so that you don't pay me
voy a poner para que no me pagues
loser that it reaches me or that it reaches me
pringado que me llegue ni que me llegue
if you don't even get what you have to
si no te llega ni lo que te tiene que
reach your head we are going to laugh at each
llegar la cabeza nos vamos a reír otr
other because this is thought that they are
una porque esto se piensa que están
giving you that we do
dando con
n't know where our face is
que no te sabemos donde tenemos la cara
or we don't have access to a lawyer or we
ni tenemos acceso a un abogado ni
can't pay ourselves or anything this is thought I'll eat this
podemos pagarnos ni nada esto se piensa
with potatoes eh make it
Esto me lo como yo con patata eh hac ser
possible that he doesn't find out about the trial so
posible que no se entere del juicio así
if they publish it in the official bulletin
si lo publican el boletín oficial
I'm hardly going to find out that I
difícilmente yo me voy a enterar que
have a
tengo un
trial how am I going to have any
juicio cómo voy a tener Yo ningún
interest in not being notified and that you don't
interés en que no os notifiquen y que no
find out about the trial loser if
os enteris del juicio pringa si a la
we send the lawsuit to Loli even by
Loli le mandamos la demanda hasta por
WhatsApp if the one who doesn't want to take it is
WhatsApp si la que no quiere cogerlo es
really her what loser and or stupid or whoever it is
de verdad qu pringado y o lerta o quien
happens that the good thing is that the
sea lo pasa que lo bueno es que el
court does search The thousand ways before
juzgado si busca Las mil maneras antes
publishing in the official bulletin that you
de publicar en el boletín oficial que tú
have a trial they look for you
tienes un juicio te buscan por todos
everywhere in any way that is the only
sitios de la manera que sea es lo único
good thing about it
bueno que
thank you very much dear Solangel Thank
tiene muchas gracias cariño solangel
you very much  Sorry, it's just that today
Muchas gracias Perdona es que hoy está
this is broken, neither the
estropeado esto no salen ni los
viewers nor the chat appear,
espectadores ni el chat
people think they're stupid, these
gente se piensa que son tontos esta
people think we're stupid. Hey
gente se piensan que somos tontos Eh
then, Mr. Oliveira, if you have these,
entonces señor oliveira si tienes Estás
save yourself the preparation of that second
ahórrate esa preparación de esa segunda
lawsuit for the same reasons. Oh, let's
demanda por los mismos motivos Ah que la
not file the second lawsuit against Loli
segunda demanda no se la pongamos a Loli
Huerta for the same
Huerta por los mismos
reasons since you just notified
motivos puesto que acabas de notificar
this and what you have to do is an
esta y lo que tienes que hacer una
extension of the lawsuit. Oh, what Troya tells me, I mean,
ampliación de demanda Ah lo que me diga
Troya is practically telling me to
el Troya o sea el Troya me está diciendo
extend the lawsuit to
prácticamente que le amplíe la demanda a
his friend.
su amiga
Troya is telling me to extend the
el Troya me está diciendo que amplíe la
lawsuit to his
demanda a su
friend, free advice,
amiga consejo gratis gratis consejo
free advice, and now if I get any, Loli
gratis y ya si a mí me llega alguna Loli
Huerta already knows what to do,
Huerta Ya sabe lo que tiene que hacer
but if I get any from you
pero si a mí me llega alguna de tu parte
or from whoever's side, I already know what to
o de la parte de quien sea yo ya sé lo
do. Don't
hacer Tú tranquilo no
worry, don't worry, but for now, instead of
sufras pero por lo pronto en vez de
deceiving your people that you're
engañar a tu gente con que estás
preparing a second lawsuit to
preparando una segunda demanda para
continue this for another year, a
seguir esto otro añito más de tema
recurring theme, to continue making
recurrente para seguir haciendo
money, money, this is what you wanted to do with
caja caja es la que tú querías hacer con
Loli, you haven't done it, you've made the
Loli no has hecho que has hecho el
fool of yourself.  and you've humiliated yourself and you've left
pringado y te has humillado y has dejado
your digital footprint for life on the
tu huella digital para toda la vida en
internet in a mess and they haven't
internet hecha una [__] y no te han
given you anything despite the fact that you put yourself there
dado nada a pesar de que te ponías ahí
saying don't tell Loli that I also
decir no le digáis a Loli que yo también
have the yellow videos you were
tengo los vídeos amarillos te has
wrong because I'm telling you from
equivocado porque ya te digo yo desde
here that you can't play a person
aquí que no se puede jugar a una persona
twice for the same
dos veces por la misma
reason, that is, ard de Troya what he has
causa o sea ard de Troya lo que ha
interpreted ard de Troya what he has
interpretado ard de Troya lo que ha
interpreted okay We already have the we already have
interpretado vale Ya tenemos el ya
the premiere of the
el estreno del Canal
main Channel in nothing we have it
principal en nada lo
in nothing we have the premiere
tenemos en nada lo tenemos el estreno
of the main Channel family vaer be there
del Canal principal familia vaer ser ahí
in a pl pl okay to the one from Troya what
en un pl pl vale al de Troya lo que ha
Elena has interpreted is that since in Spain you ca
interpretado Elena es que como en España
n't play the same
no se puede jugar dos veces la misma
thing twice, the same crime to the one from Troya what he
cosa el mismo delito al de Troya lo que
interprets the first thing is that a right
interpreta lo primero es que un derecho
to honor is for civilians it is a crime
al honor es por los civiles es un delito
okay that is the first thing that
vale eso es lo primero que ha
the creature has interpreted the head
interpretado la criatura el cabeza
knee but the second thing that
rodilla pero lo segundo que ha
the buffoon has interpreted is that they can't
interpretado el mamarracho es que no te
judge you twice for the same
pueden juzgar dos veces por el mismo
crime or so practically
delito o sea prácticamente
Imagine that if I steal from a store
Imagínate que si yo robo en una tienda
I have a trial and they don't condemn me and now
tengo un juicio y no me condenan y ahora
the next day I go and  I rob another
el día siguiente voy y robo en otra
store and they can't report me because they ca
tienda y no me pueden denunciar porque
n't try me again for the
no me pueden volver a juzgar por el
same crime, that's how
mismo delito eso es lo que ha
the Trojan has interpreted it. Imagine
interpretado el de Troya tú Imagínate
that now I kill someone, they condemn me
que yo ahora mato a alguien me condenan
and in three or four years I kill
y dentro de tres o 4 años vuelvo a matar
another person again but they can't
a otra persona pero ya no me pueden
report me because you can't play
denunciar porque no se puede jugar dos
the same crime twice,
veces el mismo delito
that's how the creature has interpreted it.
eso es lo que ha interpretado la
And on top of that he's telling us that
criatura Y encima nos está diciendo que
we believe he's
nosotros nos creemos que es
stupid with all his balls or in the same
tonto con too su huevo o en la misma
store but another day it could also be
tienda pero otro día también podría ser
Mara caballero once
María caballero una vez que te una vez
you have a trial for stealing they
que tú tengas un juicio por robar ya no
can't report you again for
te pueden volver a denunciar más por
stealing whether you win or lose the trial. Ah,
robar lo ganes o lo pierdas el juicio Ah
that crime has already been judged for you
ese delito ya ha sido juzgado para ti
creature, I'm going to
criatura yo le voy a poner a Loli una
sue Loli every time it's necessary, then it's
demanda cada vez que haga falta entonces
me. Why have the same person sent me
a mí Por qué me and dem mandado la misma
twice, do you understand? We have so much to
veces me entiendes tenemos tanto que
learn, says Elena, Elena. But that's not
aprender dice Elena Elena Pero eso no es
learning law or anything, that's because this
aprender derecho ni nada eso es que este
man wasn't born with law. He doesn't even walk with law, he doesn't even walk with
hombre no nacio ni derecho él No anda ni
law, or you, really, are you
derecho el mismo o sea tú de verdad tú
really, when you see it on Google, no, it's not
de verdad cuando ves en Google no no se
possible.  judge the same thing twice you
puede juzgar la misma cosa dos veces tú
understand that you can not judge
entiendes que no se puede juzgar por el
a person for the same crime several times,
mismo delito a una persona varias veces
that is, if that person is a repeat offender
o sea si esa persona es reincidente
then the word resident What does
entonces la palabra residente Qué
Juanca mean in comparison to an
significa juanca en comparación una
eminence no no but totally but it's not that he is an
eminencia no no pero totalmente pero es
idiot that he is no but on top of that he
que encima ya no es que sea idiota que
boasts of
lo es no sino que encima presume de
being one and talks to you like with that he talks to
serlo y te habla como con esa
you like with that thing of saying
te habla como con esa cosa de decir
Javier Oliveira who do you think you
Javier oliveira con quién te crees que
're talking to you with one of
estás hablando tú con un pringado de
those losers look on Google like no I'm
esos mira en Google como noos estoy
lying the guy on top of that talks to you like
mintiendo el tío encima es que te habla
that don't worry tomorrow he will say the
así no te preocupes mañana dirá lo
opposite like in
contrario como en
Anything goes in nothing it is already
Todo vale en nada ya está
programmed or the video is already here
programado u ya está el vídeo aquí canal
main channel it lasts 50 minutes it is
principal dura 50 minutos está
programmed if I'm not mistaken it doesn't
programado si no me equivoco ya [__] no
appear to me yet Wait I'm going to close and I'm going to come
me aparece todavía Espera voy a cerrar y
back it doesn't appear to me
volver no me aparece
yet grab some pipilla
todavía [__] unas pipilla
no it doesn't come out damn wait I'm going to come back I do
no no me sale [__] espérate voy a volver
n't see the
no me sale la
Ray
Ray
now okay There we have the right I'm going to
ahora vale Ahí tenemos la right voy a
put a tweet
poner yo un tweet
no salsera no
no salsería ya no
now with this we go to
ya con esto nos vamos a la
bed it appears to you
cama os aparece
now the video appears to you in this
ya os aparece ya el vídeo en este
eno
eno
Yeah yeah  that the video is already appearing but
Sí sí que aparece ya el vídeo pero la
people have to enter Okay, I'm
gente tiene que entrar Vale yo desde
going to do a raid from here there are 5
aquí voy a hacer una raide quedan 5
minutes left 5 minutes left yes it appears now Eh yes it appears now the video there are 5 minutes left until it starts yes it appears There are 5 minutes left until it starts okay Anyways I've done a raid I've done a raid of this So You're going to fall there automatically as
que Vais a caer ahí automáticamente en
soon as we close the live I'm going to wait I'm
cuanto cerremos el directo voy a esperar
going to wait with you the 4 minutes
voy a esperar con ustedes los 4 minutos
left okay so that you fall there and
que faltan vale para que caigáis ahí y
so that you don't touch anything eh I mean if for whatever reason if for whatever reason
para que no toquéis nada eh o sea si por
the raid doesn't work
sea si por lo que sea no funciona la
And no and it doesn't fall
raide Y no y no caé
there please go to the video on the
ahí por favor iros para el vídeo del
main Channel immediately
Canal principal inmediatamente
okay if for whatever reason the raid doesn't work go
vale si por lo que sea no funciona la
there
ra iros para allá
automatically because the video has been
automatiquement porque el vídeo ha sido
a lot of work
un curro
eh the video has been a [ __ ] lot of work man
eh el vídeo ha sido un [__] curro tío
Well the video is a response to
Bueno pues el vídeo es una respuesta a
a few defamations that have been
unas cuantas difamaciones que me han ido
made to me in the last few months okay there
haciendo en los últimos meses vale
's even a lawsuit for it there's a
incluso hay una demanda por ello hay una
lawsuit for one by one by one of these
demanda por uno por una por una de estas
things are involved here okay
cosas están aquí involucradas vale
eh They pulled one on me,
eh Me la han colado
dude  they've fooled me, dude, they
cabrón me la han colado cabrón el audio
charged me for the audio they've fooled me, man, I'm going to [ __ ]
me la han cobrado me la han colado tío
in 10, two minutes, fam, fam, 2
me cago en 10 dos minutos famil fam 2
minutes, 2 minutes, two minutes, I want you all
minutos 2 minutos do minutos os quiero
here, destroying the Live, okay. Okay, as I
por aquí reventando el Live vale Bueno
said, family, tomorrow, Friday, tomorrow, I don't
lo dicho familia mañana viernes mañana
know if I'll stop by here, honestly,
no sé si me pasaré por aquí la verdad
eh, tomorrow, I don't know if I'll stop by here,
eh mañana no sé si me pasaré por aquí la
honestly, because tomorrow is Friday, tomorrow I'm
verdad porque mañana es viernes Mañana
going out with the family
salgo con la familia
and, and yes, tomorrow I'm going to try to get my act together to
y Y sí que mañana me me voy a intentar
do the news, okay,
poner las pilas de hacer noticieros vale
Elena, I know I have to send the message
Elena sé que tengo que mandar el mensaje
on WhatsApp, I know,
en el WhatsApp lo sé vale
okay, 60 seconds, okay. I'm closing the
Ok 60 Segundos vale Voy cerrando el
live, don't touch anything. And if the ra, no, the
directo no toquéis nada Y si la ra no la
Ray, the Ray, I always say the Ray, conf with
Ray la Ray siempre digo la Ray conf con
the Ray, if the Ray doesn't go well, and V
el Ray si la Ray no sale bien y V
manually go to the main Channel, and by
manualmente al Canal principal y por
the way, check the subscriptions, man,
cierto revisar las suscripciones tío que
we're nowhere, nowhere, I mean, like
estamos a nada pero a nada o sea en
200 to reach 600,000, I mean, we're arriving
200 para llegar a 600.000 o sea llegamos
tonight, okay, we're arriving
esta noche vale llegamos esta
tonight, you go at your own pace. Yes, I have
noche tú a tu ritmo Sí ya ya lo tengo
to send it, Elena, I have to send it
que mandar Elena lo tengo que mandar
tomorrow, let's see it during the afternoon and evening,
mañana a ver durante la tarde y noche
I'm going to be with the family for  whatever
voy a estar con la familia por lo que
they go to bed early or
sea ellos se acuestan temprano o lo que
whatever I want to get on the salsa bar I
sea me quiero poner yo en la salsería me
'll get on the salsa bar but it's
pondré en la salsería pero sí que es
true
verdad
that I don't think I'll do live shows tomorrow or the day
que no creo que haga directos mañana ni
after now
pasado ahora
Well I'm going to try to get my act together because I
Bien voy a intentar ponerme las pilas
always say it and I never do it with
que siempre lo digo y nunca lo hago con
the news man I mean newscasts Yes or yes they
los notis tío o sea noticieros Sí o sí
have to come out now
tienen que salir ya
eh the newscast has to come out now I have to
eh noticiero tiene que salir ya me tengo
get my act together What happens is that
que poner las pilas Lo que pasa que
many times I get hooked on one thing I get
muchas veces me ligo con una cosa me
hooked on another and maybe it's not
ligo con la otra y a lo mejor no me
worth it for me to get going because I'm already
merece la pena ponerme hiciero porque ya
late and it'll take me less time to
voy tarde y voy a tardar menos en
go live
ponerme en directo
okay adelo said twice the thumbnail
vale puso adelo dos veces la miniatura
tells me
me dice
one family I hope you enjoy the
uno familia Espero que disfrutéis del
video on the Main Channel and that you have
vídeo del Canal principal y que os
a laugh see you there I'll
echéis unas risas nos vemos por allí que
be in the chat I'll be eating
estaré en el chat voy a estar comiendo
okay I'm not going to be talking but I
vale no voy a estar hablando pero os
'm reading you a kiss don't touch
Estoy leyendo un beso no toquéis
anything an
nada an